FROM THE DESK OF MR.MUHAMED BELLO AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING MANAGER , BANK OF AFRICAN B.O.A OUAGADOUGOU-BURKINA FASO. DEAR FRIEND , I AM THE MANAGER OF AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING AT THE FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPARTMENT OF BANK OF AFRICAN) HERE IN OUAGADOUGOU, BURKINA FASO. IN MY DEPARTMENT WE DISCOVERED AN ABANDONED SUM OF US$12.5M DOLLARS (TWELVE MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THAUSAND US DOLLARS) IN AN ACCOUNT THAT BELONGS TO ONE OF OUR FOR EIGN CUSTOMER (MR. ANDREAS SCHRANNER FROM MUNICH, GERMANY) WHO DIED ALONG WITH HIS ENTIRE FAMILY IN JULLY 2000 IN A PLANE CRASH. SINCE WE GOT INFORMATION ABOUT HIS DEATH, WE HAVE BEEN EXPECTING HIS NEXT OF KIN TO COME OVER AND CLAIM HIS MONEY BECAUSE WE CANNOT RELEASE IT UNLESS SOME BODY APPLIES FOR IT AS NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION TO THE DECEASED AS INDICATED IN OUR BANKING GUIDLINGS AND LAWS BUT UNFORTUNATELY WE LEARNT THAT ALL HIS SUPPOSED NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION DIED ALONGSIDE WITH HIM AT THE PLANE CRASH LEAVING NOBODY BEHIND FOR THE CLAIM.IT IS THEREFORE UPON THIS DISCOVERY THAT I NOW DECIDED TO MAKE THIS BUSINESS PROPOSAL TO YOU AND RELEASE THE MONEY TO YOU AS THE NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION TO THE DECEASED FOR SAFETY AND SUBSEQUENT DISBURSEMENT SINCE NOBODY IS COMING FOR IT AND WE DON'T WANT THIS MONEY TO GO INTO THE BANK TREASURY AS UNCLAIMED BILL.THE BANKING LAW AND GUIDLINE HERE STIPULATES THAT IF SUCH MONEY REMAINED UNCLAIMED AFTER FIVE YEARS, THE MONEY WILL BE TRANSFERED INTO THE BANK TREASURY AS UNCLAIMED FUND. THE REQUEST OF FOREIGNER AS NEXT OF KIN IN THIS BUSINESS IS OCCASSIONED BY THE FACT THAT THE CUSTOMER WAS A FOREIGNER AND A BURKINABE CANNOT STAND AS NEXT OF KIN TO A FOREIGNER. I AGREE THAT 30% OF THIS MONEY WILL BE FOR YOU AS A RESPECT TO THE PROVISION OF A FORIEGN ACCOUNT ,10% WILL BE SET ASIDE FOR EXPENSES INCURRED DURING THE BUSINESSAND 60% WOULD BE FOR ME THEREAFTER, I WILL VISIT YOUR COUNTRY FOR DISBURSEMENT ACCORDING TO THE PERCENTAGE INDICATED THEREFORE, TO ENABLE THE IMMEDIATE TRANSFER OF THIS FUND TO YOU ARRANGED,YOU MUST APPLY FIRST TO THE BANK AS RELATION OR NEXT OF KIN OF THE DECEASED WITH A TEXT OF APPLICATION THAT I WILL SEND TO YOU,SO I WILL LIKE YOU TO SEND TO ME YOUR PRIVATE TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBER FOR EASY AND EFFECTIVE COMMUNICATION AND LOCATION WHERE IN THE MONEY WILL BE REMITTED.UPON RECEIPT OF YOUR REPLY, I WILL SEND TO YOU BY FAX OR EMAIL THE TEXT OF THE APPLICATION. I WILL NOT FAIL TO BRING TO YOUR NOTICE THIS TRANSACTION IS HITCH-FREE AND THAT YOU SHOULD NOT ENTERTAIN ANY ATOM OF FEAR AS ALL REQUIRED ARRANGEMENTS HAVE BEEN MADE FOR THE TRANSFER. YOU SHOULD CONTACT ME IMMEDIATELY AS SOON AS YOU RECEIVE THIS LETTER WRITING ME TO MY PRIVATE EMAIL ADDRESS:MUHAMED_BELLO7@LATINMAIL.COM, TRUSTING TO HEAR FROM YOU IMMEDIATELY. YOURS FAITHFULLY, 1. FULL NAME 2. YOUR TELEPHONE NUMBER AND FAX NUMBER 3. YOUR CONTACT ADDRESS. MR.MUHAMED BELLO _________________________________________________________________ Testez Windows Llive Mail Beta ! http://www.msn.fr/newhotmail/Default.asp?Ath=f

My Dear Friend in the Lord, In a brief, I am Mrs Teressa Stevens, Wife of late Mr Stevens James, a white farmer, murdered by unknown assailants 2003 in Zimbabwe. My husband was a white farmer in Zimbabwe who was brutally murdered in the land dispute in Zimbabwe by the agents of the ruling government of President ROBERT MUGABE for his alleged support and sympathy for the opposition MDC PARTY led by the minority white farmers. My husband was among the few white rich farmers murdered in cold blood by the war veterans backed by the government. Before the death of my husband, he deposit the sum of US$20.5M (Twenty Million Five hundred thousand United State Dollars) with one of the Financial Institution, as if he knew the looming danger in ZIMBABWE. We were married for twelve years and God blessed us with two children. Presently this money is still with the Financial Institution. Recently, my Doctor told me that I might not last for the next Eight months due to an inflammation of my liver. This has led to my being on 24 hours intensive care, in a private clinic here in Cotonou Rep. of Benin. I am tired of living like this. I have decided to donate part of this fund to an individual, group or a charity organisation that will utilize this money the way I am going to instruct herein while half of the money shall be kept for the betterment of my children. I want an individual, or Charity Organisation that will use this fund for orphanages, widows, and helping land mine victims worldwide. I took this decision because my husband's relatives are Trouble Makers and I don't want my husband's efforts to be used for trivialities I do not want a situation where my husband's sweat will be used in material pursuits. This is why I am taking this decision. As soon as I receive your reply I shall give you the contact name of my lawyer, telephone number and email address who will issue you a letter of authority that will prove you the present beneficiary of this fund. Please ensure to contact me immediately to enable me direct you to my lawyer. Any delay in your reply will give me room in sourcing another person for this same purpose. Please assure me that you will act accordingly as I stated herein. Hope to receive your reply. Remain blessed. Yours Sister, Mrs Teressa Stevens.

From:Mr. Esau Chirwa, Dear Sir/Madam, URGENT BUSINESS PROPOSAL Email: MgChirwa@katamail.com Tel:+221 4409966 Firstly I must solicit your confidence in this transaction, this is by virtue of the nature as being utterly confidential.Hence i have decided to contact you due to the urgency of this transaction. I am Mr. Esau P. Chirwa from the African Development Bank Senegal,On June 6, 1999, an American Oil contractor, Mr. Charles Ball made a fixed deposit for twelve months,valued at €5,500,000.00 Euros Five million, Five hundred thousand Euros)in my branch upon maturity, we sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply.A month after, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers,the Petroleum Corporation that Mr.Charles Ball died in the plane crash On October 31, 1999,(an Egypt air Boeing 767 Flight 990)with other passengers on board. Upon this discovery, I seek your permission to have you stand as next of kin to Mr. Charles Ball so that the funds Five million, Five hundred thousand Euros) can be released and paid into your account as the next of kin otherwise the fund will be returned to the treasury as unclaimed funds which will subsequently be reverted to the ownership of the Senegal government and will be donated to the trust fund for arms and ammunition to further enhance the course of war in the World. Consequently, in return for your service and assistance you will be entitled to 30% of this money, 10% will go to settle all expenses incurred during the process of this transaction,while the balance 60% will go to us Please acknowledge receipt of this message in acceptance of our mutual business endeavour by furnishing me with the following; 1)Your Full Name and Official Mailing Address 2)Your private / official telephone and fax number. The paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and my position as the branch manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction.Upon your response, I shall provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction.I advice that a healthy degree of caution be exercised before conclusions are reached by your good self. Please if this proposal is acceptable by you, do not take undue advantage of the trust I have bestowed on you. I will appreciate your sincere response. Warm Regards, Mr. Esau P. Chirwa. Tel+221 4409966

Office of the Principal Accountant Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation {NNPC} Falomo Office Complex- Lagos - Nigeria Tel.: +234-802-2329001 Email: mu2018@yahoo.com Dear Sir, STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL REQUEST FOR URGENT BUSINESS TRANSACTION I am CHIEF MAXWELL UDOKA, the Principal Accountant with the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation {NNPC}, Headquarters Lagos. I am writing on behalf of my colleages in the Nigerian National Peretroleum Corporation {NNPC} and have been assigned to seek for the assistance of a reliable Foreign Company through which we can transfer the sum of Thirty One Million Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars {USD$31,500,000.00}. This money is now depostied in the NNPC Treasur Accorunt with the Central bank of Nigeria {CBN}. ORIGIN OF THE FUND This sum arose from the deliberate over-invoicing of a contract awared by the NNPC to a Foreign Firm in the twinlight days of the last military regime. This contract has been completely executed and commisoned and the contractor that handled this contract has collected his full and final payment thus leaving behind the above stated amount which represent the over-invoiced sum. We have been safe-guarding this money waiting for conducive time for its transfer out of the country for our personal use. However, the code of employment does not allow us {civil servants} to own and operate foreign accounts and because the contract was handled by a foreign firm and the payment made in Dollars, we now need a foreign partner that will present himself as the sub-contractor so that the money will be transferred into his company's or personal account. Your address was made abailable to us by a very good friend who works with the Nigeria Chambers of Commerce and Industry. He assured us of your company's viability and capability in business transactions. This assurance gave us the courage to link you up in this pareticular transaction and I hope it will be of mutual benefit to all of us. Note that the nature of your business is not particularly relevant to the success of this transaction. All we require is your willingness to present yourself as the sub-contractor by providing your bank informations so that the fund will be transferred into your account. SHARING RATIO For your assistance in this business, your share will be 25% of the total money. I and my colleagues will take 65% while 10% has been mapped out for any expenses that might be incured in the course of this transaction. If you are willing to assist us in this business, send the following informations: 1.} Name of your Bank and address 2.} Your account number/beneficiary's name 3.} Your private telephone and fax numbers for easy communication This information will enable us put an application for payment approval to the concerned ministries and final to the Central Bank of Nigeria {CBN} and it is going to last for 10 to 14 banking days, starting from the day we recieve the above informations. All modalities for the take off of this business transaction has been worked out and further action will commence immediately we hear from you. I am waiting for your reply by the above email. Thanks for your understanding and due co-operation. CHIEF MAXWELL UDOKA.

Zulberg Closeoff Ernest Oppenheimer Road Bruma Lake, Johannesburg, 2196 South Africa. Kind Time of the day Please forgive my indignation if this message comes to you as a surprise I got your contact from a database found in internet while searching for a reliable and honest person that will assist me. I was divinely inspired to pick your name among other names found in the Internet database. My name is Duru Nbeki,and I work in the International operation department in a Local Bank here in South Africa. On a routine inspection I discovered a dormant domiciliary account with a BAL. Of 36,000,000 (Thirty Six Million USD) on further discreet investigation, I also discovered that the account holder has long since passed away (dead)leaving no beneficiary to the account. The bank will approve this money to any foreigner because the former operator of the a/c is a foreigner and from Iraq in particular and I am certainly sure that he is dead, and nobody will come again for the claim of this money A foreigner can only claim this money with legal claims to the account Holder;therefore I need your cooperation in this transaction to get this money transfered into your safety hand. I will provide the necessary information needed in order to claim this money, But you will need to open an account where this can be transferred. If interested send your private Telephone No. And Fax number including full details of the account to be used for the Deposit I wish for utmost confidentiality in handling this transaction as my job and the future of my family would be jeopardized if it were breached. I want to assure you that the transaction is without risk if due process is followed accordingly. Finally,I will give you 35% for your corporation after a successful competion of the business. I look forward to a favorable response from you through this email :durunbeki@myway.com Thanks. Mr,Duru Nbeki.

-- Good day Private Message to you, This is an important message to you.The lord directs me to share this with you. As you read the mail, you should sympathize with my current situation and assist me. My name is Isabella Carmel the only survivor from family of four. I was narrowly escaped from the tsunami disaster which affected my spinal cord and also my ear drum and claim the lifes of my entire family, husband (Denis caromel) and two sons (Ugo and Tom) who went for holidays in Sri-Lanka. Right now I am currently in Kuala Lumpur Malaysia. After staying a week in my family hospital, I was disabled by the catastrophe and now on a wheel cheer after all the treatment.This has defiled all forms of medicine and right now I have only about a few months to live, according to medical experts.I have not lived my life so well as my primary interest and focus was only on my late fathers business. Though my father is very rich and was never generous. But now I regret all this, as I know that there is more in life than just wanting to have or make all the money in the world.The bible says what shall it profit a man to wine the whole world and loose his soul. I believe when God gives me a second chance to come to this world I will live my life a different way from how I have lived before. I have willed and given most of my fathers properties to the less privileges because I want God to be merciful to me and accept my soul. I have decided to give arms to charity organizations and give succor and comfort to the less privileged in our societies. I want this to be one of the last good deeds I do on earth since my father has never recognized that. So far I have to distribute money to charity organizations now that my health has deteriorated so badly,I cannot do this myself anymore that is why am soliciting your assistant to make this donation through you. The last of my late fathers money that am willing to donate to the less privileged right now is the huge sum of $10.6M USD that is concealed in a consignment and deposited in (OVERSEA CREDIT COMMISSION ABROAD) for safekeeping which he intends to invest on profitable factory. I want you to help me claim this funds where is deposited and disburse it to charity organizations and the less privileged in the society.Please I will appreciate you to indicate interest for the disbursement and also include your contact telephone/fax numbers that I will forward to the(OVERSEA CREDIT COMMISSION ABROAD) to be able to contact you as the appointed beneficiary. I will provide you the certificate of deposit and the letter of authority to enable you claim the consignment of the funds. If you are willing and ready to assist with this project,please e-mail me at mrslsabellacaromel_1950@yahoo.it without delay, while I wait to hear from you.Thanks once again for your kindness may God guide and reward you in all your endeavors as you make me realize my last dreams and wishes. Remain blessed, Mrs.Isabella Caromel ________________________________________________ Cristina Fusi WebMail - Message sent using UebiMiau 2.7.2

Content-Type: text/plain Content-Transfer-Encoding: 8bit Sussan Art World Inc. 112 st. Mary's road, Liverpool L192 JG, UNITED KINGDOM Send Your Reply To: sussan_bryant10@yahoo.co.uk Dear Sir/Madam, My name is Sussan Bryant,I am an artist with my husband Tommy Bryant,We own Sussan Art World in London(United Kingdon) I live in London United Kingdom,with my two kids,four cats, one dog and the love of my life my husband (Tommy Bryant). It is definitely a full house, I have been doing artwork since I was a small child, that gives me about 23 years of experience I majored in art in high school and took a few college art courses, most of my work is done in either pencil or airbrush mixed with color pencils. I have recently added designing and creating artwork on the computer,I have been selling my art for the last 3 years and have had my work featured on trading cards, prints and in magazines,I have sold in galleries and to private collectors from all around the world. I am always facing serious difficulties when it comes to selling my art works in your country,they are always offering to pay with MONEY ORDER OR CASHER'S CHEUQES,which is difficult for me to cash here in London United Kingdom. I am looking for a representative in your country who will be working for me as a partime worker and i will be willing to pay 10% for every transaction,which would'nt affect your present state of work, someone who would help me recieve payments from my customers in your country,i mean someone that is responsible and reliable,because the cost of coming to your country and getting payments is very expensive,i am working on setting up a branch in your country,so for now i need a representative in your country who will be handling the payment aspect for our company. These payments are in money order or casher's cheuqes and they would come to you in your name if you are willing to assist as a representative, so all you need to do is cash the money order, deduct your percentage and Western Union Charges then wire the rest back . The problem i have is trust,but i have my way of getting anyone that gets away with our money,i mean the F.B.I branch in Washington gets involve It wouldnt cost you any amount, you are to receive payments which will be sent to you by fedex or ups from my business patners, which would come in form of a money order then you are to cash it and send the cash to me via Western Union or Money Gram. NOTE:All charges will be deducted from the money so you are rest assured that you would'nt send a dime out of your personal money. If you are interested,please get back to me. NB:Endeavour to send your reply through my alternative e-mail address: (sussan_bryant10@yahoo.co.uk) Regards Sussan & Tommy Bryant.

Dear Sir, (Assalamalaikum) My name is Halima Abdulrahman,am 24 years old from Sierra-Leone, the only daughter of Dr.Usman Abdulrahman.Former Personal Assistance to the present Minister for Mines and Natural Resources in-charge of the diamond production sales in my country Sierra-Leone. Unfortunately some months ago before the peace pact in my country, my father and his colleagues were killed by rebel group of Mr. Dunga Sankibo during an inspection visit to the rich diamond mining area in the village of Izumba, where the rebels laid an ambush and open fire on the convoy killing my father and some of his colleagues who where on their way to the diamond mining zone. Following the peace pact that was introduce by the united nation keeping force some months back,my mother deem it fit to say that it is right time for us to leave the country for safety and for europe or any other stable economic bloc with the 6.3.million us.dollars six.three million dollars deposited by my late father in a finance house on my name as the next of kin or beneficiary, I want you to assist us so that we can transfer this money to your account for safe keeping pending our arrival to your country, to start up an investment in your country through your wise advice. You will act as our international business representative and also my family business associate,so that we can transfer this money to your account for safe keeping. We are now in Dakar-Senegal for the facilitation of this transaction.Please kindly communicate your acceptance or otherwise of this proposal through email address for us to discuss the modalities of seeing this transaction through. However, if you are not disposed to assist kindly destroy the letter in view of the families interest and personal security. I count on you greatly for your assistance. Please,if How i contacted you is not okay with you,do not hesitate to tell me and provide another address where i will be contacting you.A good percentage awaits you for your assistance. Expecting to hear from you soon. Yours Faithfully, Miss Halima.

Greetings from Mrs. Estella  PLOT 23 Felix Avenue  Abidjan -Cote d.Ivoire    Dear,    It is my pleasure to contact you for a business venture which I and my  Son,intend to establish in your country. Though I have not met with you  before but I believe, one has to risk confiding in someone to succeed  sometimes in life. There is this amount of Eight million, five hundred  thousand United State Dollars($8.500,000) which my late Husband deposited  with a security company in Abidjan Capital city of Cote d.Ivoire which he  wanted to used for his political reason in our Country before he was  assassinated.     Now I and my son have decided to invest these money in your country or any  wheresafe enough outside Africa for security and political reasons. We want  youto help us claim and receive the consignment which will be sent to you  through diplomatic meansto your address to avoid any traces of the funds and to enable you plan for theinvestment in your Country: I will like to invest  part of the money into these three investment in your Country but, if there  is any other business that is better thanwhat I am suggestion, I will be  very glad to follow your advice.    1). Real estate  2). The transport industry  3). Five star hotel    If you can be of an assistance to us we will be pleased to offer to you 20%  Of the total fund while the balance will be invested by you.  I await your soonest response.  Respectfully yours,      PLEASE CONTACT ME THROUGH THIS  EMAIL ADDRESS estellarichard2006@yahoo.ca       Mrs Estella Richard   ________________________________ Free POP3 Email from www.gawab.com Sign up NOW and get your account @gawab.com!!

>From The Desk of Mr. Gary Fredricks Head of Foreign Operations 5, mall London Road, Swanley Kent BR8 7WL London EC2R 8BP, United Kingdom. TEL: +44-704-0185-556 FAX 44-7005-921-605 E-mail: mrgary_fredricks@yahoo.de Dear Partner, Do accept my sincere apologies if my mail does not meet your personal ethics. For i know this may seem like a complete intrusion to your privacy but right about now this is my option of communication. This note might seem strange or probably untrue considering the amount of junk mails we receive daily, but i believe this is still the most genuine way of contacting a true character. I will introduce myself as the Head of Foreign Operations Department in the accounts management section this well-known bank here in the United Kingdom as Stated above. I am seeking your cooperation to present you to my bank as the Next of kin to LATE ANDREA SCHRANNER. A Germany property Magnate Andreas Schranner, 64, his wife Maria, 62, their daughter Andrea Eich, 38, her husband Christian, 57, and their children Katharina, eight, and Maximilian, 10, all perished in the jet. Please click here below for verification. http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479.stm PROPOSITION: One of late Andrea Schranner's accounts with holding balance of £15,000,000(Fifteen Million British Pounds) has been dormant and has not been operated for the past 5 years and the DEPOSIT will be converted to UNCLAIMED DEPOSIT and therefore forfeited if nobody comes forward to lay claim to the deposit before the end of this financial quarter, as is the practice and also indicated in the EU banking guidelines. >From my investigations and confirmation, the owner of this account a foreigner by name Late Andrea Schranner's died on MONDAY, 31 JULY,2000 in a plane crash with his family. After going through the deceased records and files, I discovered that: (1) No one has operated this account since 2000; (2) He died without a heir; hence the money has been floating. (3) No other person knows about this account and there was no known beneficiary. And if we do not remit this money urgently, it would be confiscated and forfeited for nothing. I have secretly discussed this matter with account officer and we have agreed to find a reliable foreign partner to deal with. We thus propose to do business with you, standing in as the next of kin of these funds from the deceased and funds released to you after due processes have been followed. This transaction is totally free of risk and troubles as the fund is a legitimate and does not originate from drug, money laundering, terrorism or any other illegal act. On your interest, let me hear from you. On your interest, let me have your private/direct contact numbers including fax and a copy of your International Passport or driver's license for easy communication, identification and trust. I must be reached only on my private contact details for confidential reasons. Regards, Mr. Gary Fredricks TEL: +44-704-0185-556 FAX 44-7005-921-605

Greetings from Dubai, This letter must come to you as a big surprise, but I believe it is only a day that people meet and become great friends and business partners. I am Mr. Khalifa Al Abuhail, currently Head of Coporate affairs with a reputable bank here in U. A. E. I write you this proposal in good faith, believing that I can trust you with the information I am about to reveal to you. I have an urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. On November 6, 2000, an Iraqi Foreign Oil consultant/contractor with the "SAUDI ARAMCO", MR. Khalil Al Nasser made a (Fixed deposit) for 36 calendar months, valued at US$17,500, 000.00 (Seventeen Million Five hundred Thousand Dollars only) in my bank and I happen to be his account officer before I was moved to my present position recently. Upon maturity in 2003,as his account officer and as well the bank manger, it is my duty to notify him on the maturity date so I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but the letter was returned undelivered. After sometime, I tried sending back the letter,but it was again returned and finally I discovered from his contract employers, Chevron Petroleum Corporation that Mr.Khalil Al Nasser died as a result of torture in the hand of Saddam Hussein (former Iraqi President) during one of his trips to his country Iraq, as he was accused of leaking information to the Americans. On further investigation, I discovered that Mr. Khalil Al Nasser family wife and two sons died during the Gulf War in Iraq and was the reason why he did not declare any next of kin or relation in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank and did not leave any WILL.This sum of US$17,500,000.00 have been floating and placed under dormant/unserviceable account by my bank management since no one have heard from the owner since 2003.I wish to let you know that all the investigation I have made so far, my bank management is not aware of it, I am the only one that have the information. With the recent change of government in my country and with their efforts to support the United Nations in checkmating terrorism aid in the U.A. E. By end of this year, the government will pass a new financial control law which will give the government authority to interrogate account owners of above $5,000, 000.00 to explain the source of the funds, making sure it is not for terrorism support. If I do not move this money out of the country immediately, by end of the year the government will definitely confiscate the money, because my bank cannot provide the account owner to explain the source of the money. I cannot directly transfer out this money without the help of a foreigner and that is why I am contacting you for an assistance. As the Account Officer to late Khalil Al Nasser , coupled with my present position and status in the bank as Head of Retail Banking Group , I have the power to influence the release of the funds to any foreigner that comes up as the next of kin to the account, with the correct information concerning the account, which I shall give you. All documents to enable you claim this fund will be carefully worked out and there is practically no risk involved, the transaction will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of law, beside U. A. E is porous and anything goes. If you accept to work with me, I want you to state how you wish us to share the funds in percentage, so that both parties will be satisfied. If you are interested, contact me as soon as you receive this message so we can go over the details.Thanking you in advance and may God bless you. Please, treat with utmost confidentiality . I shall send you copy of the deposit certificate issued to Al Nasser when the deposit was made for your perusal. I wait your urgent response. Regards, Khalifa Abuhail.

FROM THE DESK OF MR.CHRIS BARHOLET. BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER, METROPOLITAN BOND AND FINANCE CO.LTD LONDON. 48 Moorfields, London EC2Y 9AL. DEAR Friend, I am the manager of bill and exchange at the auditing of METROPIOLITAN BOND AND FINANCE CO.LTD. in England In my department we discovered an abandoned sum of 27.5 Pound sterling (Twenty-Seven Million-five hundred thousand Pounds sterling) in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customer who died along with his entire family on Monday, 31 July, 2000 in a plane crash in paris.Please to confirm my story about the crash you can visit this site:http://news.bbc.co. uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479.stm Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless some body applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our financial guidelines and laws but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I now decided to make this business proposal to you and release themoney to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement sincenobody is coming for it and we don't want this money to go into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill.The banking and financial law and guide line here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed afterSEVEN years, the money will be transfered into the bank treasury as unclaimed fund. The request offoreigner as next of kin in this business is occassioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a national here cannot stand as next ofkin to a foreigner. I agree that 40% of this money will be for you as a respect to the provision of a foriegn account ,10%will be set aside for expenses incurred during the business and 50% would be for me Thereafter, I willvisit your country for disbursement according to the percentage indicated Therefore, to enable theimmediate transfer of this fund to your country ,you must apply first to our security firm here in London because of financial laws guiding this country,we have moved the money in question to our Security Company Vault here in London for easy transfer of this fund to any where in the world.So i will like you to send tome your NAME,TELEPHONE NUMBER and PHYSICAL ADDRESS for easy and effective communication and location where in the money is bound to. Upon receipt of your reply, I will get back to you on the next moves to make. I will not fail to bring to your notice that thistransaction is hitch-free and that you should notentertain any atom of fear as all requiredarrangements have been made for the transfer. You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this letter. Trusting to hear from you immediately. Yours Faithfully, MR.CHRIS BARTHOLET.

FROM THE DESK OF: Zhang He, Bank of China.. Shenzhen China. Dear Kathleen Crain, I am Zhang He, Bank Manager of the Bank of China, Shenzhen branch, China. I have an urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. On June 7, 2000, a consultant/ contractor with the Chinese Solid Minerals Corporation, made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at Twenty One Million Dollars (US$21,000,000.00) only in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to the forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the South Korea Solid Minerals Corporation that he died along with his wife from a plane crash. On further investigation, I found out that he died Without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that he did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$21,000,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Laws of China, at the expiration of eight (8) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the South Korea Government if nobody applies to claim the funds. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to assist me in receiving this money as I have every machinery set to enable you receiver this money via a Finance firm based overseas. I need your urgent assistance so that this money will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple, I will require you to send me your complete names, contact address and telephone and fax numbers so that I will be able to apply for the necessary documents to enable you receive the money via the Finance firm overseas in your name. After receiving the money, we will share in the ratio of 75% for me and 25% for you. Note that the project will be 100% risk free. Considering my position as the credit officer of the bank, I guarantee the successful execution of this transaction. I have the facilities to obtain relevant documents to enable me lift the money from the bank overseas. If you are interested, please reply immediately. Upon your response, I will then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. I will also let you have the contact details of the Finance Firm and the country it is located in Overseas. Please send me your confidential TELEPHONE and FAX Numbers for fast communication, as I will need to speak to you to personally. You should observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us. Awaiting your urgent reply. Thanks and regards. Zhang He.

FROM:Mrs Kathy Olds Johannesburg, South africa. Tel+27-738151680 Fax+27-11-5075944 email:kathyolds@gmail.com

Sir/madam,

With due respect, trust and humility, I write to you irrespective of the fact that you do not know me and i do not know you either, but please do consider this letter as a request from a widow and family in dare need of assistance.

You may be surprised to receive this letter from me since you don't know me personally. I am Mrs Kathy Olds,wife of Late Mr Martin Olds,a famous zimbabwean tobacco/cattle farmer who was murdered in a farmland dispute in Zimbabwe.Please gothrough:

http://www.rte.ie/news/2000/0418/zimbabwe.html

I got yourcontact through a search on the internet here in South Africa. I do not know your person but I am relying on faith to see me through. During the war waged against the farmers in Zimbabwe by the supporters and cohorts of President Robert Mugabe to claim all the white owned farms in our country, my late husband belonged to one of the classes of farmers also targeted by the ZANU-PF armed group,because he did not support theirideas and policies of taking white farmers land by force.

Blackwar veterans claiming tobe farmers, invaded my husband's house on April 17, 2000 at about 8.35pm in Macheke/Virginia district and murdered him because of his insistence that white farmers be allowed to retain their farmlands despite the  recently introduced land reforms"Act" in Zimbabwe by the head of state,President Robert Mugabe.

Until his death he was one of the prominent members of the Zimbabwean Farmers'Union (ZFU)But before my husbands death, he first escaped safely into neighbouring South Africa with his life time fortune of US$37m(Thirty-seven Million USdollars)cash, important documents of property title and other valuables which were concealed and secured in a trunk box, and transported to Johannesburg through diplomatic means.

The consignment box is currently safely lodged and secured in the vaults of a private security firm here in Johannesburg after which he returned to zimbabwe while he was killed. The fund was meant for the purchase of new tractors,machinery and agro-allied chemicals for our new farms acquired in Swaziland.

This land problem came when President  Robert Mugabe introduced a new land act"ModusOperandi" reform which wholly affected the rich white farmers. A lot of people were killed because of this land reforms "Act" of which my late husband was one of the main targets.Based on this,I had to flee the country with my two children and my only late husband personal assistance [PA] Mr Chris Mutembi who was his personal assistant{PA}. We are now in south africa as political assylum seekers/refugees.

We decided to contact you to assist us in removing this money my husband kept in a private security company here in south africa to your account or any part of the world for investments as the monetary/investment laws here in south africa prohibits refugees and illegal immigrants from operating bank accounts or be involved in any transaction/investment. Based on this, we are contacting you hoping that you will assist us with this transaction.

As a widow, I am saddled with the responsibility of seeking a genuine and an honest person who will assist us in investing this money in a highly profit yeilding ventures without the knowledge of my country(Zimbabwe)government who are bent on taking everything my late husband had after confiscating all his farmlands and investments in Zimbabwe .

We are absolutely left with nothing except the money he deposited in a private security company here in south africa. In recognition of investment opportunities that abound in so many contries in the world , I solicit for your assistance to us by moving my family money into your country/ bank account for safekeeping pending our future arrival for investments in your country or elsewhere you may wish.

The family has resolved to adequately offer a share of 15% of the money to you for your involvement and assistance to our family in moving the entire money out of SouthAfrica.

Please call  Mr Chris Mutembi on telephone number+27-738151680 [or] send him a fax on fax number +27-11-5075944 for further briefing on what you need to do, if my letter and request is of any interest to you. while I implore you to maintain absolute confidentiality required in this transaction considering our situation here in south africa. If not, then I humbly apologise for this infringement on your privacy.

Respectfully,

Mrs Kathy Olds. alternative email:kathyolds11@msn.com

Dear Sir, Naturally, this letter will come to you as a surprise since we have not met, permit me however, I am Mr. Alan Jack a Zimbabwean Farmer. I am contacting you as the need for me to have a foreign partner in your country has become necessary due to my plans to relocate and establish a private company in that region, as the present political instability in my country (Zimbabwe), does not encourage financial investment as the environment is not conducive for investment and most of all security is not guaranteed, just as reported by the International media. This problem started when the Zimbabwean government under the leadership of President Robert Mugabe announced a decree on May 31st 2001 to seize more than 6000 white-owned farms. So far, more than 5,400 white owned farms have been invaded, properties confiscated and farm lands seized. During these periods, as reported by the international media and C.N.N, more than 500 white farmers were killed; the government didn't stop at this, as just recently the government has asked all white-farmers to give up their farms to black farmers or risk going to prison. Having lived in this country (Zimbabwe) for more than 35 years, I have no other country to go to, nor can I trace any of my distant relatives. Therefore, I decided to contact you through my local Zimbabwean associate (Mr. Dennis Udongo) for your assistance so that I can establish a company in your country and relocate there. Also, I must re-iterate the importance of having a citizen of your country to front as the owner of the enterprise, due to the fact that I will be a foreigner in your country. For this purpose, I have deposited in a Security Company based in Amsterdam (Holland) all the funds realized from the sales of my farmland and other farming equipment which amounted to USD18, 500,000.00 (Eighteen million, five hundred United States Dollars). These funds was packaged in two metal boxes and declared as personal effects and photographic materials so as to avoid detection by immigration/security officials. For now, I stay in Asia, because Zimbabwe is highly unsafe for me and my family. Upon your immediate response, I will immediately arrange and send to you all the documentation that will empower your good self in finalizing the transaction with the Security Company in UAE Dubai. Let me use this opportunity to also inform you that this transaction is 100% risk free and genuine and should also be handled in the most confidential manner. This proposal is NOT and must NOT be linked to all the numerous SCAM letters flying around the internet world today. The money (USD18.5m) already stashed in the two boxes could be termed as consignment and I will not hesitate to link you to my safe contact in the security company for further discussion. Lest I forget, you should be entitled to 30% of the total funds for your support and cooperation in the transaction. It’s also your duty to assist me in investing my own share of the money in your company or in your country. I shall be counting on your unalloyed trust and immediate response. Best Regards and God bless. Mr. Alan Jack

Dear Friend, First, I must apologise to you for using this medium to communicate about this transaction, though it is my great pleasure in writing you this letter on behalf of my colleague and myself. I am Mr. Idrissa Diop the Director of Bill and Exchange at the Foreign Remittance Department in the bank where I work. I am writing to you this urgent proposal following the impressive information about you through one of my friends who runs a consultancy firm. Though, I did not disclose to him the nature of my proposal to you to avoid any leakage. My colleague and I have decided to contact you on a business transaction that will be very beneficial to both of us at the end. I would be brief and direct to ensure you understand everything properly. In my department we discovered an abandoned Sum of $13.7M USD (Thirteen Million, Seven Hundred Thousand US Dollars), in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customers, an American by name: Mr. John Schelpert who died along with his wife and other passengers in EgyptAir Flight 990 - October 31, 1999. Since we got information about his untimely death, the fund has been dormant in his account with my Bank without any claim, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased and the person must be a foreigner as indicated in our banking guidelines. Before our observation in this development, we discovered that the owner of the account died without a Heir/WILL hence the money is floating and if I do not remit this money out urgently it will be forfeited for nothing. The Banking law and guideline here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed after Six (6) years, the money will be transfered into the Bank treasury account as unclaimed fund. It is therefore upon this discovery that I and my junior colleague in the bank now decided to make this businness proposal to you and release the money to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we do not want this money to go into the Bank treasury as unclaimed Bill. Meanwhile the whole arrangement to put claim over these fund as the bonafide next of kin to the deceased and transfer this money to a foreign account has been put in place. Directives and needed information will be relayed to you as soon as you indicate your interest and willingness to assist us and also benefit from this great business opportunity. We could have done this deal on our own, but because of our position in this country operating a local account would eventually raise an eye brow on my side during the time of transfer because I work in this bank. This is the actual reason why it will require foreigner as second party that will forward claims as the next of kin to the Bank and also present a designated safe foreign account where he will need the money to be transferred into after due verification and clearification by the bank. May I at this point emphasize that this transaction is a successful arrangement, and as an insider of the bank I have the capacity to monitor that everything is smoothly perfected. On smooth conclusion of this transaction, you will be entitled to your own share of the total sum as gratification We have agreed that 20 % of this money will be for you as our foreign partner, in respect to the provision of a foreign account, 5% will be set aside for expenses incured during the business and 75% would be for me and my colleague. There after I and my colleague will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentages indicated. This share of yours is negotiable as long as it is reasonable. Please, you have been adviced to keep this information a topsecret as we are still in service and intend to retire from service after we conclude this deal with you. I will be monitoring the whole situation here in this bank until you confirm the money in your account and ask us to come down to your country for subsequent sharing of the fund according to percentages we shall agree upon. All other necessary information will be sent to you on your acceptance to champion this transaction with us. I suggest you get back to me as soon as possible, stating your wish in this deal. Please do call me on my direct line for more clearifications: 00221 688 8466 Thanks and best regards. Yours faithfully, Mr. Idrissa Diop Telephone: 00221 688 8466

PLEASE CALL ME +27836703988 OR REPLY TO MY PRIVATE EMAIL : temawilliams176@galmail.co.za Dear Sir/madam With due respect and to the glory of Almighty God whom we worship I call upon you to assist me. Please Permit me to inform you of my desire of going into business relationship with you. I must not hesitate to confide in you for this simple and sincere business. My name is Tema Williams,The only Son of late Chief PATRICK WILLIAMS .My father was a very wealthy cocoa merchant in Abidjan but we are from Siera Leone ,After my Father death I and my Family move to South Africa as a refugee. My father was poisoned to death by his business associates on one of their outings on a business trip. Before his death in a private hospital in Abidjan he secretly called me on his bed side and told me that he has the sum of ($12.000,000 MILLION US DOLLAR) keft with a security and finance company in South Africa,He also explained to me that it was because of this wealth that he was poisoned by his business associates, that I should seek for a beneficiary in a country of my choice where I will transfer this money and use it for investment. , I am honorably seeking for your assistance to transfer our fund out of South Africa and make arrangement for me and my mother and younger sister to come over to your country to further our Education and take care of our mother. More over, I am willing to offer you 20% of the total sum as compensation for your effort/input after the successful transfer of this money into your nominated account overseas, you indicate your options towards assisting me .you signify your interest to assist me. As we depend in God, and with God all things are possible Anticipating to hear from you today. Thanks and God bless. PLEASE CALL ME +27836703988 OR REPLY TO MY PRIVATE EMAIL : temawilliams176@galmail.co.za Best regards, Tema Williams (for the family)

My Dear, Good day to you, I hope fine, dear am writing this mail with due respect and heartful of tears,sorrow and pains in my heart, since we have not known or met ourselves previously I am asking for your assistance,i have gone through your profile and will be very glad if you can render me assistance to my situation now. I will make my proposal well known if I am given the opportunity. I would like to use this opportunity to introduce my self to you. I am Mr.Hassan Abdoulaye, A 23 years old young man from Cote' Ivoire, the only Son of Late ALH.Sammar Abdoulaye , my father and mother was Assassinated when i was 12 years old, i still in primary six in school and One of my fathers best friend rushed to our school and pick me with my younger sister to republic of Senegal were we are with him and his family and continue our study and after some years he was illed before he died, i was 18 years old then and he called me, give me all the document concerning my fathers properties and the deposit account, he corrected from my fathers lawyer in my country and directed me to his family lawyer. may his soul rest in peace.When Mr.Donard John, my father best friend died and his family started matreatig us, we left the family house to Refugee camp were we live now. My father is Former Assistant Director Of Cote'Ivoire Gold And Coco Mining Corporation before his death . The main reason why I am contacting you now is to seek for your assistance in the area of future investment and also my father left some huge amount of money for us,which i want you to help us and invested in country This money is Twenty Million Five Hundred Thousand US Dollars which was deposited some years ago by my late father, he made me the sole beneficiary/next of kin to the money. I am now asking you to stand on my behalf to make this claim for the finance company, I am a young man and too young in age i can't handle this can of transaction, i want you to stand as my foreign partner oversea and also to help me investment the money. I will give you details about the deposit as you respond to my request. I have all original copies of the documents concerning this money with me here, So please am expecting to hear from you soon. This are my Privet Emal hassan_abdoulayee@yahoo.co.uk Yours Truly, Hassan.

#45 Rue Grand Yorf, DAKAR, SENEGAL. Assalamaulakum. My Dear Friend, Compliments of the day.I did like to send to you the best wishes of good health and success in your pursuits particularly through my proposal as contained in this letter. After due deliberation with my son,I decided to forward to you this business proposal, we want you to assist us .I will give you more information. As to this regard as soon as you reply. I am Mrs.Estelle Mamadou . I am contacting you with the hope that you will be of great assistance to me, I currently have within my reach the sum of 7.3 million U.S dollars cash which I intend to use for investment purposes. I therefore personally appeal to you seriously and religiously for your urgent assistance to move this money in to your country where I believe it will be safe since I cannot leave the country due to the restriction of movement imposed on the members of my family by the Senegal Government. This money came as a result of a payback contract deal between my husband and a Russian firm in our country.The Russian partners returned my husbands share .Presently, the Government has intensified their probe in to my husbands financial resources which has led to the freezing of all our accounts, local and foreign, the revoking of all our business licences and the arrest of my First son. In view of this I want to acted very fast to withdraw this money from one of our finance houses before it will be closed down.My husband deposited the money in a finance firm for safe keeping . No record is known about this fund by the government because there is no documentation showing that we have such funds. Further more, my elder son have been in detention in the last four years following the death of my late husband for charges of State organized murder and corrupt practices. he was just been released by the Supreme Court after the president brokered a deal with my family regarding his freedom. and he is still under interrogation about my late husband's assets and some vital documents. Due to the current situation in the country and government attitude to my family,I cannot make use of this money within, thus I seek your help in transferring this funds out for investment than leaving the fund here and to invest the money to profit my family Bearing in mind that you may assist me.l have decided to part with 25% of the total sum. I am seriously considering to settle down abroad in a friendly atmosphere like yours as soon as this fund get into your account so that I can start all over again if only you wish. I shall ask my son Mohammade to come over to your country to liaise with you. If this proposal satisfies you. please do not let me out to the security as I am giving you this information in total trust and confidence. Please kindly reply by return mail and please include your personal telephone and fax numbers. Conclusively,we have decided part with 25% of the total sum. of the total sum,10% will be for expenses incurred during thecause of this transaction, while 65% is to be held on trust by you until we can decide on a suitable business investment in your country subsequent to our free movement by the Senegal Government. I will greatly appreciate if you accept my proposal in good faith. Your URGENT response is needed. Regards and God Bless you. Mrs.Estelle Mamadou . _________________________________________________________________ Découvrez Windows Live Messenger : le futur de MSN Messenger ! www.windowslivemessenger.fr

FROM: BENSON EKO. CHIEF AUDITOR MINISTRIE OF FINANCE ECONOMICS COTONOU-BENIN REPUBLIC. Dear Friend, Forgive my indignation if this message comes to you as a surprise and if it might offend you without your prior consent and writing through this channel. I am BENSON EKO CHIEF AUDITOR MINISTRIE OF FINANCE ECONOMICS COTONUO-BENIN REPUBLIC.I got your information when I was searching for a reliable,honest and trustworthy person to entrust this business with.I was simply inspired and motivated to pick your contact from the many names and lists in the website. I wish to transfer the sum of $14,300,000.00USD (Fourteen Million Three Hundred Thousand United States Dollars only.into your personal or company`s bank account. This fund was a residue of the over invoiced Industrial Contract bills awarded by MINISTRIE OF FINANCE ECONOMICS COTONUO-BENIN REPUBLIC to some foreign firms. This DEAL was deliberately hatched out and carefully protected with all the attendant lope holes sealed off.As the chief auditor,I have the cooperation and mandate of the Financial Director and the Secretary. It was my consensus to seek the assistance of a willing foreigner to provide us with the facilities to transfer this money out of West Africa.This is borne out of our beleive in the non-stable and sporous political nature of this sub-region. The original contractors have been duely paid by the Banque Centrale Des Etats De L`Afrique De L`Ouest (Central Bank of the West African States)This balance is suspended in the escrowaccounts awaiting claims by any foreign company of our choice.I intend to pay out this fund now as the organisation is winding up its activities. Based on the laws and ethics of employment,we as civil servants working under this organisation, are not allowed to operate a foreign account.This is the more reason why we needed your assistance to provide an account that can sustain this fund for safe keeping and our future investment with your comprehensive advise,assistance and partnership in your country. I have however agreed,as the account owner in this deal to allow you 40% of the entire sum as compensation,why 55% will be held on trust for me while 5% will be used to defray any incidental charges and cost if any. Upon the receipt of your information, the certificate of job completion of one of the contracts will be issued in your for the transfering of the fund to your nominated account withoutdelay. As with the case of all organised (sensitive)and conspired DEALS,we solicit for your unreserved confidentiality and utmost secret in this business. We hope to retire peacefully and lead a honourable business life afterwards.There are no risks involved. REPLY ASAP. With regards. MR BENSON EKO

Dear Sir/Madam, How are you doing. I came across your email address and your brief profile through an email listing affiliated with the US Chamber of Commerce. I would be very interested in offering you a part-time paying job in which you could earn alot. My names are Thomas Daniel Owen Jr. and I am 52 years of age. I just resigned my job as a research scientist for ARINI(Agricultural Research Institute of Northern Ireland) and I now work as a freelance consultant for the instistute which gives me very much time to do my own work which is basically being a freelance researcher who could be employed by research institutes to do research projects anywhere in the world. Presently, I have just been granted a funding to head a research project in the tropical regions of West Africa/Asia regarding rare and vulnerable plant species and this would be commencing very soon. This research program will be funded and sponsored by some of my American counterparts and Associates. But the only set back is that the American counterparts want to make payments for the research in form of US money orders/ cashier's cheque only and its a known fact that money in such forms cannot be cashed outside the US. Getting an accountant in the states or opening an account would have been my best choice but I have a deadline to meet and taking any of those choices would cost me time and a whole lot of other requirements which I am not ready to deal with. This is where I need to employ your assistance and service. WHAT I NEED YOU FOR? At this point, I will be glad if you could work with me as my representative in the US. You will be working as my payment assistant incharge of collecting and processing the payments from my Associates. Since they will be making the payment in Money orders/ Cashier checks made payable only in the US, you will be collecting this payments and cashing them on my behalf. On agreement to been my representative in the US, you will receive a commission of 10% of whatever amount of payment you receive from my associates. JOB DESCRIPTION? 1. Recieve payments (in form of money orders/checks) from my associates via mail(UPS/FEDEX/DHL). 2. Cash the Payments at your Bank. 3. Deduct 10% which will be your commission/percentage on Payment processed. 4. You are to remit the balance via Money Gram or Western Union Money Transfer according to my instruction. HOW MUCH WILL YOU EARN? 10% from each transaction! For instance: On receiving 6000 USD via cheques or money orders on my behalf. You will cash the payment and keep 10% to yourself before remitting the balance! At the beginning your commission will equal 10%, though later it will increase up to 12%! For the research, I am expecting about the sum of $105,000 in total from the clients(though the money will be sent in installmentally due to the progress of my research). You could make over $10,500 for the little time we will be working together. ADVANTAGES? You dont have to go out of your present daily activity inorder to engage in this Job(i.e. you can do this Work easily without leaving or affecting your present Job).You will work as an independent contractor right from your home /office. Your job is absolutely legal. You do not need any capital to start(non of your personal funds is needed). REQUIREMENTS? 18 years or older. Legally capable. Responsible, Reliable and Trustworthy. Ready to work 3-4 hours per week. Able to check and respond to emails often. Easy telephone access. IS THIS LEGAL? Yes it is.As a matter of fact,my lawyer checked all legal provisions to know if there is any dosmestic or international law against businesses or deals in this manner.And he said its allowed by all LAWS.So know that doing this work is safe and legitimate. I hope all is well understood. I would be glad if you accept my proposal and I intend to commence as soon as you are ready. Please, to facilitate the conclusion of this transaction if accepted, do send promptly by email the following details below, to indicate your interest. NAME: ADDRESS: PHONE NUMBER: AGE: SEX: I hope to hear back from you. ALL REPLIES TO BE SENT TO : owentholu03@yahoo.com.hk Dr. Thoams D. Owen Jr. Agricultural Research Institute of Northern Ireland Hillsborough, Ireland BT26 6DR.

CENTRAL BANK OF NIGERIA TINUBU SQUARE,VICTORIA ISLAND,LAGOS. FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF NIGERIA From the Desk Of: Prof Charles Soludo Executive Governor (CBN) IMMEDIATE PAYMENT REF: CBN/IRD/CBX/021/06 THIS IS AN OFFICIAL NOTIFICATION OF FUNDS DEPOSITED IN YOUR NAME AND IT IS NOT A SALES SOLICITATION. I am professor Charles.c. Soludo governor, central bank of Nigeria ( CBN ). The mentioned bank is known for the safekeeping of special and valuable packages and baggage in trust for reputable clients that are honest and trustworthy. We work in collaboration with top firms and Governments of various countries as we have earned a name as a service whose hallmarks in reliability and confidentiality are revered. International missions and Embassies of the world have used our services to satisfaction. A benefactor whose identity can not be disclosed because of the Non Circumvention and Non Disclosure Agreement that was signed with the said benefactor when the funds were being deposited in the Central Bank of Nigeria, made you the beneficiary of a package containing some amount of money and stated clearly that you should only be contacted when the time signed for it to be in our care elapses and the time has already elapsed that is why you are being contacted. The Non Circumvention and Non Disclosure Agreement signed with the benefactor mandates us to fully divulge and disclose the benefactor's identity 18 months after you, the beneficiary has received the funds. The funds totals $5.000,000 (Five Million Dollars) i shall reconfirm to you are fully free of any liens, or encumbrances and are clean, clear and non- criminal origin and are available in the form of CASH. You are hereby advised to reconfirm your Full Contact Information for verification with information contained in our computer database as well as other relevant information in the format stated below so that the funds would be arranged by the deplomats who will be moving the funds from the Central Bank of Nigeria to be brought to you. I would also inform you clearly here that you must procure an affidavit of claim of ownership before the comensment of the diplomat bringing the funds to you, this you will be informed as soon as your information is received. The Diplomats shall accompany you to your bank (if you want them to) to deposit the funds in your name and submit all documentations of proof of the origin of the funds in other to exonerate you from any form of investigations or interrogation and to authenticate the fact that the funds are clean and has no links whatsoever with either drugs or terrorism. The Requested Information is to ensure that no mistake or error is made and it should be forwarded in the manner stated below: Your Full Name: ______________________________ Your Complete Address (Physical Address with Zip Code not P.O.BOX) : ______________________________ Name of City of Residence:_______________________________ Country:____________________________________ Direct Telephone Number: ____________________________________ Mobile Number:____________________________________ Fax Number:___________________________________ Finally your age and sex very impotant too please note this. The Contact Numbers are very necessary because the number would be called before the funds would be handed over to the Deplomats so as to ensure that the package is handed over to the right person.So, it is mandatory you send your Direct Telephone Number preferably your Mobile or Cell Phone Number. Complete the above and send back to me through my E-mail address below as soon as possible. Congratulations in advance. YOURS SINCERELY, PROFESSOR CHARLES C. SOLUDO, GOVERNOR, CENTRAL BANK OF NIGERIA (CBN). PRIVATE E-MAIL: prof_charles.soludocbn@gawab.com ****PRIVATE & CONFIDENTIAL***** This e-mail and any attached files are confidential and may be legally privileged. If you are not the addressee, any disclosure, reproduction, copying,distribution, or other dissemination or use of this communication is strictly prohibited. ---------------------------------------------------------------- Reserve your free e-mail@egypt.com, http://www.egypt.com Spam free & Virus clean web based mail service Report abuse to abuse@egypt.com

Goodday, You may be surprised to receive this letter from me since you dont know me personally, I am DR RANI ALI JUMA, the first son of DR. OMAR ALI JUMA, and he was the VICE PRESIDENT of the REPUBLIC OF TANZANIA. Before he died, my father died at the age of 63 in the year 2001 after addressing fellow TANZANIANS during the visit of PRESIDENT JOSEPH KABILA of DEMOCRATIC REPUBLIC OF CONGO and YUERI MUSEVENI of UGANDA. I got your contact through the Ghana information Exchange (G.I.E) in my search for a reliable and reputable person to handle a very confidential transaction which involves the transfer of fund to a foreign account and I decided to write you. My late father was among the ruling party (CCM) which the opposition party was dominated by his Muslim brothers led by PROF. IBRAHIM LIPUMBA. Before his death he had taken to Europe to deposit the sum of US$40 million (FORTY MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS) with a security and finance company as if he foresaw the looming danger coming. The money was deposited in two sealed boxes as valuables goods to avoid much demurrage from the security company. I most say that the death of my father has warned me and my whole family not to go back to politics. For the fact that PRESIDENT BENJAMIN MKAPA, never showed any concern since the death of my father and after I discovered that my life was no longer safe I decided to leave to Ghana ,West Africa where I am residing now with my own family. Meanwhile here in Ghana West Africa I dont think of going back and for this I and my family have decided to transfer my fathers money into a foreign account in a Islamic counrty. As the eldest son of my father, I am saddled with the responsibility of seeking a genuine foreign account where this money could be transferred without the knowledge of my government who have tactically frozen our family wealth as I may not trust the system of African government. Furthermore, the new Ghana government does not allow such investment hence I am seeking for asylum. As a business person whom I must entrust my future and that of my family into his hands I must let you know that this transaction is 100% RISK FREE and the nature of your business does not necessarily matter. Therefore, if you accept to assist me and my family, we are willing to offer you 20% of the total sum for your assistance, 75% for me and my family, while 5% will be mapped out for any expenses that may be incurred in the process of this transaction. We wish to invest our money on commercial property based on your advice and I will also wish to receive your genuine assurance that you would not sit on this money when it is finally transferred into your personal or companys account. If this transaction is acceptable by you. you can contact me on my private email address:drranialijuma@katamail.com BEST REGARDS DR. RANI ALI JUMA.

Direct and private cell number +447040114795 Direct and private Telephone + 447040121012 Direct and private fax number +447005804255 Dear Friend, I am Mr. T. Smith, deputy senior regional manager at Lloyds TSB Commercial Finance in Yorkshire. I have urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. On June 6, 2000, Mr. Barry Kelly made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for forty-eight months, (being four years) valued at US$40,000,000.00, (forty Million, Dollars) in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his employers, that Mr. Barry Kelly died from tsunami on his holidays in Thailand 26 December 2004. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL and all attempts to trace his next of kin were fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Barry Kelly did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$40,000,000 has carefully been moved out of my bank to a security company for safekeeping. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to British Law, at the expiration of (three) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the British Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you to stand in as the owner of the money I deposited it in a security company in two trunk boxes though the security company does not know the contents of the boxes as I tagged them to be photographic materials for export. I am writing you because I as a public servant (Manager with the bank), I cannot operate a foreign account or have an account that is more than $1m. I want to present you as the owner of the boxes in the security company so you can be able to claim them with the help of my attorney. This is simple. I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents which will put you in place as the as the owner of the boxes. The money will be moved out for us to share in the ratio of 70% for me and 30% for you. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the Attorney and this will guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via my email address upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in (Buying of properties like houses, hotels and doing charity works etc) Please do send me your private/mobile telephone fax number so that we can have a smooth communication. Awaiting your urgent reply ONLY via my email ( ttss7520062006@mixmail.com ) Thanks and regards. TONY SMITH N.B Reply me only on this my alternative email ttss7520062006@mixmail.com

FROM:THE DESK OF ENG.CLICF WANTOM NIGERIA NATIONAL PETROLEUM CORPORATION (NNPC) LAGOS-NIGERIA . Email:clicfwanton@rixmail.se Dear Friend, It is with trust and confidence that I write to reveal this urgent business relationship to you. I was assigned by two of my colleagues to seek for a foreign partner who will assist us in providing a convenient account in a designated bank overseas for the transfer of US$32,000, 000.00 (Thirty Two Million United States Dollars Only) pending our arrival in your country for utilization and disbursement of the fund with the owner of the account where the fund would be transferred into. On the 23rd of January 1996, our corporation, the Nigeria National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC) awarded a contract of $120,000,000.00 ( One Hundred and Twenty Million United States Dollars) but I and my colleagues being members of the contract award committee inflated the contract sum to the tune of US$152,000, 000.00 with the intention of sharing the remaining balance of US$32,000,000.00 among ourselves. The contract has been successfully executed and the actual contractors have been paid their US$120,000,000.00 ( One Hundred and Twenty Million United States Dollars) in full. But what we want to transfer out of the country in our favour for disbursement is US$32M. balance My colleagues and I have agreed that if you / your company can act as the beneficiary of this fund , we will transfer the funds to your account and you will retain 30% of the total fund for assistance rendered, while we will retain 60% of the total fund and the balance of 10% of the fund will be set aside for the offsetting of all expenses that might be incurredby both parties during the fund transfer process. We request you cooperate with us and provide a convenient account number in a designated bank where this fund can be safely transferred to, we intend to come over to your country on the completion of the fund transfer to secure our own share of the funds. THE NATURE OF YOUR BUSINESS IS NOT PARTICULARLY RELEVANT FOR THE CCESS OF THIS TRANS ACTION. ALL WE REQUIRE IS YOUR WELLINGNESS TO CO-OPERATE AND ASSURANCE THAT OUR OWN SHARE WILL BE GIVEN TO US WHEN THIS MONEY IS TRANSFERRED INTO YOUR ACCOUNT.ALL NECESSARY PRECAUTIONS HAVE BEEN TAKEN TO TO ENSURE A NO RISK SITUATION ON THE SIDE OF BOTHPARTIES AND IT IS BELIEVED THAT THIS TRANSACTION WILL LAST 20 WORKING DAYS, BARRING ANY DELAYS. SINCE WE HAVE NO KNOWLEDGE OF BUSINESS, OUR PLAN IS TO INVEST THIS MONEY INTO REAL ESTATE, STOCK AND PERHAPS IMPORTATION OF GOODS FROM YOUR COUNTRY BASED ON YOUR ADVISE BECAUSE MANY OF OUR YEARS HAS BEEN SPENT AS CIVIL SERVANT,AND WE MAY LIKELY RESIGN FROM GOVERMENT SERVICE TO PRIVATE BUSINESS AFTER THIS MONEY IS TRANFERED INTO YOUR ACCOUNT. Please note that we have been careful and have worked out all the modalities for a smooth transfer of the fund to your designated Bank Account before contacting you. We would therefore not want you to expose this proposal to anybody for the purpose of SECURITY and its CONFIDENTIALITY. We alsobelieve you would not sit on our money when it is transferred eventually into your account as you get your 30% share. Please, be rest assured that this transaction is 100% risk free. REPLY TO MY PRIVATE EMAIL ADDRESS : clicfwanton@rixmail.se Yours faithfully, ENGR. CLICF WANTOM clicfwanton@rixmail.se

FROM THE DESK OF DR.JASIR KELZI, AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING MANAGER, BANK OF AFRICA (B.O.A) OUAGADOUGOU-BURKINA FASO. BANK WEBSITE:www.bkofafrica.net PRIVATE TELEPHONE:00226-70-357-881 I am the manager of auditing and accounting department of BANK OF AFRICA (B.O.A) here in Ouagadougou, Burkina Faso. In my department we discovered an abandoned sum of US$20.5m dollars (Twenty Million Five Hundred Thousand US dollars) in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customer (MR. ANDREAS SCHRANNER from Munich, Germany) who died along with his entire family in Jully 2000 in a plane crash.For more informations about the crash you can visit this site: http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479.stm Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we can not release it unless some body applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidlings and laws but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I now decided to make this business proposal to you,so that the money can be release to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody will come for it and we don't want this money to go into the bank treasury as unclaimed dormant fund. The banking law and guidline here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed after six years, the money will be transfered into the bank treasury as unclaimed dormant fund. The request of foreigner as next of kin in this business is occassioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a Burkinabe like me can not stand as next of kin to a foreigner. I agreed that 30% of this money will be for you as a respect to the provision of a foriegn account ,10% will be set aside for expenses incurred during the business and 60% would be for me.Thereafter, I will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentage indicated Therefore, to enable the immediate transfer of this fund to you arranged,you must apply first to the bank as relation or next of kin to the deceased customer with a text of application that i will send to you,but before i send to you the text of application form,I will like you to send me the following informations. 1. NAME IN FULL:................................ 2. ADDRESS:....................................... 3. NATIONALITY:................................... 4. AGE:............................................. 5. Sex.............................................. 6. OCCUPATION:...................................... 7. MARITAL STATUS:.................................. 8. PRIAVTE PHONE NO............................................ 9. PRIVATE FAX NO:............................................. so i will like you to send to me those informations for easy and effective communication,also location where the money will be remitted. Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or email the text of the application form. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch-free and that you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made for the transfer. You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this letter,if only you are intrested and ready to help. Trusting to hear from you immediately. Yours Faithfully, DR.JASIR KELZI MANAGER AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING DEPARTMENT BANK OF AFRICA _________________________________________________________________ Don't just search. Find. Check out the new MSN Search! http://search.msn.com/

Dear Sir/Madam, I am Mr MAXWELL TAMBO, Bank Manager of a Reputable bank in Johannesburg, Gauteng Province, and Republic of South Africa. I have an urgent and very confidential business proposition for you.On feb 27, 2001, a British Oil Consultant/contractor with the South African Mining Corporation, (Name deliberately with held) made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$50,000,000.00 (Ffity Million Dollars) in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the South African Mining Corporation, that the depositor died from an automobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless.I therefore made further investigation and discovered that the depositor did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents,US$50,00,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Laws of Republic of South Africa,at the expiration of 5(five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the South African Government if nobody applies to claim the fund.Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as THE NEXT OF KIN to the depositor so that the fruits of this old man's labour will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the attorney will prepare the Necessary documents and affidavits that will put you in place as the next of kin.We shall employ the services of an attorney for drafting and notarisation of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favour for the transfer. A bank account in any part of the world that you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin.The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 60%for me and 35% for you and 5% for any expenses that we are going to incue.There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via the private email address.Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please send me your full name,address, confidential telephone and fax numbers for easy communication.Also,Please observe utmost confidentiality, and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Thanks and Regards. Mr.Maxwell Tambo Reply me via my alternative email address: maxwelltambo2006@myway.com

Dear Sir, I am Mrs Aminat Mohamed from Liberia, presently staying in Germany. I am married to Mr. Hassan Mohamed who worked with Liberian embassy in Lome-Togo for Ten years before he died in the year 2002.We were married for eleven years without a child. He died after a brief illness that lasted for only four days.Before his death we were both born again Moslim. Since his death I decided not to remarry or get a child outside my matrimonial home which the Quran is against. When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of $6.8Million (Six Million Eight hundred thousand U.S. Dollars) with one security company in Europe. Presently, this money is still with the Security Company. Recently, my Doctor told me that I would not last for the next Eight months due to cancer problem. The one that disturbs me most is my stroke sickness. Having known my condition I decided to keep this fund in Europe. I want an organization or an individual that will use this fund for orphanages, idows,propagating the word of Allah and to endeavor that the house of Allah is maintained. The Holy Quran made us to understand that Blessed is the hand that giveth. I took this decision because I don't have any child that will inherit this money and my husband relatives are not Moslim and I don't want my husbands efforts to be used by unbelievers. I don't want a situation where this money will be used in an ungodly way. This is why I am taking this decision. I am not afraid of death hence I know where I am going. I know that I am going to be in the bosom of the Almighty Allah .I don't need any telephone Communication in this regard because of my health hence the presence of my husband's relatives around me always. I don't want them to know about this development. With Allah all things are possible. As soon as I receive your reply I shall inform the security company in Europe that you are the beneficiary of the said consignment you will need to go and claim this fund in Europe. I will also issue you an authority letter that will prove you the present beneficiary of this fund. I want you and the organization to always pray for me because the lord is my shepherd. My happiness is that I lived a life of a worthy Moslim. Whoever that wants to serve the Allah must serve him in spirit and truth. Please always be prayerful all through your life. Any delay in your reply will give me room in sourcing another person for this same purpose. Please assure me that you will act accordingly as I stated herein. Hoping to receive your reply and Remain blessed in the Allah.. Yours in Allah , Mrs Aminat Mohamed

Dr.Eric Morgan                                                         Branch Supervisor, Banque International De L’Afrique De L’Ouest (BIAO-CI), Abidjan,Cote D’Ivoire, EMAIL:eric.morgan001@yahoo.co.uk

Dearest Beloved,

This mail may be a surprise because you did not give me the permission to do reach you and neither do you know me in person. Before introducing myself, I want you to please forgive me for sending this mail without your Consent .

Dearest beloved I came to know you through my search for a reliable, transparent and trustworthy person or partner to assist me execute a vital private and confidential business transaction as stated b elow, therefore I am very glad Ih ave found a personlike you.

I am Dr.Eric Morgan an account officer with Banque Internationale de L' afrique De L' Ouest Cote D' Ivoire. I am writing following an opportunity in my department here in the bank that will be of immense benefit both of us.

In my department we discovered an abandoned sum of $10 million Ten million united states dollars) in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customer the Late Mr Smith B.Andrea an American oil engineer with Petro Technical Services Sarl who unfortunately lost his life in the plane crash of Alaska Airlines Flight 261 which crashed on January 31 2000, including his wife.

You read more on the crash on visiting this Site.http://www.cnn.com/2000/US/02/01/alaska. airlines.list/smith.html.

Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin or relatives to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relatio n to the deceased as indicated in our bankingguidelines.

Unfortunately I learnt that his supposed next of kin being his wife [Patty Andrea] died along with him in the plane crash leaving nobody with the knowledge of this fund behind for the claim.

It is therefore upon this discovery that I now decided to make business with you and release the money to you as the next of kin or beneficiary of the funds for safety keeping and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we don't want this money to go back into Government treasury as unclaimed bill.

The banking law and guidelines here stipulates that if such money remained after six and half years, the money will then be transferred into Government treasury as unclaimed funds.

I agree that 30% of this money will be for you as the foreign partner, while the balance will be for me. I will visit your country for the disbursement according to the percentages indicated above once this money gets into your account.

Please be honest to me and trust is our watchword in this trans action. Note this transaction is confidential and risk free.

As soon as you receive this mail you should contact me by return mail.Please note that all necessary arrangement for the smooth release of these funds to your yet to be provided account has been finalised.

We will discuss much in details when I do receive your response. Please in your response include your telephone number for easy communication between us.

Best Regards, Dr. Eric Morgan.

PLEASE NOTE: The material being sent to you contains PRIVILEGED AND CONFIDENTIAL information only for the use of the addressee(s) named above.

If the reader of this message is not the intended recipient, please note that any dissemination, distribution, or copying of this communication is prohibited.

It is requested that anyone who receives this communication in error notify the sender immediately by e-mail reply and destroy all copies of the tran smission received.

Thanks ! FROM Dr.ERIC MORGAN

Assalamualaikum My name is Amina Hannah Hatleberg from America. I am the surviving Daughter of Dr. and Mrs Hatleberg who died as a result of plane crash of Alaska Airlines Flight 261 which crashed on January 31 2000. My family converted to Islam in 1998. When my late Parent were alive, my father deposited the sum of$8.5 Million (eight million five hundred thousand U.S. Dollars) with International Diplomatic service firm in south east Asia with purpose to invest the fund in Islamic foundation in Asia before death took him, The fund is still under safe keeping with the International Diplomatic firm in south east Asia, hence am contacting you to help me to achieve this project in your country. Two years ago I fell sick and my doctor told me I had cancer, I had tried all my best to treat myself with every medical expert but there is no improvement, Currently my Doctor told me that I would not last for the next six months due to my cancer problems. Having known my condition, I decided to donate this fund to mosque, Islamic school authority or better Muslim individual that will utilize this money the way I instruct. I want this fund to be disburse to, orphanages, widows promoting the work of Almighty Allah, needies and to promote work of almighty Allah in your country. The Koran made us to understand that blessed is the hand that giveth. I took this decision because I don't have anybody left except Almighty Allah and my Father relatives are Christians and unbelievers. I don't want my Father hard earned money to be misused by unbelievers because I know he will be rejoicing in the bosom of Allah if this fund is spent to promote the work of almighty Allah. I don't want a situation where this money will be used in an ungodly manner. That's the reason for taking this bold decision. I am not afraid of death since I know where I am going. I know that I am going to be in the heaven. I don't need any telephone communication in this regard because my health. With Allah all things are possible. As soon as I receive your reply I will instruct the DIPLOMATIC operation manager and my Father lawyer in London to furnish you with more details on how to receive this fund. I will also instruct him to issue you a letter of authority that will empower you as the original-beneficiary of this fund. I want you and the Moslem to always pray for me because in almighty Allah I put my hope. My happiness is that I lived a life of a worthy Moslem. Whosever that wants to serve Allah must serve him in spirit and truth. Please always be prayerful all through your life. And reply me through my e- mail address as delay in your reply will give me room in sourcing for another faith member for this same purpose. Please assure me that you will act accordingly as I stated here. As I am disabled and can not be able to move around and do much due to am presently very ill, I will really appreciate your urgent respond through my Email address as the internet is my only mean of communicating. Or through the help of a nurse here who is so kind to assist me in the hospital and taking care of me You can read more about this crash by visiting this website, <http://www.cnn.com/2000/US/02/01/alaska.airlines.list/> and <http://www.nativefederation.org/history/people/mThompson.html> Remain blessed in the name of the Allah. Hannah Hatleberg.

MR BABU MARRINS The Account / Audit Manager, African Development Bank (ADB). Ouagadougou Burkina Faso. PRIVATE PHONE N0: +226 76 49 81 68 Dear Beloved, I presumed that all is well with you and your family. Please let this do not be a surprise proposal to you because i got your contact information from the international directory in few weeks ago before i decided to contact you on this magintude and lucrative transaction for our future survival in life. Moreover, i have laid all the solemn trust in you beforei decided to disclose this successful & confidential transaction to you. IM MR BABU MARRINS The Account / Audit Manager of our bank and i have had the intent to contact you over this financial transaction worth the sum of THIRTY THREE MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS($33,000,000.00 ) for our success.This is an abandoned sum that belongs to one of our bank foreign customers who died along with his entire family through plane crash disaster since few years ago. Meanwhile i was very fortune to came across the deceased file when i was arranging the old and abandoned customers files in other to sign and submit to the entire bank management for an official re-documentation and audit of the yearagainst 2007. Be informed clearly that it was stated in our banking rules and regulations which was signed lawfully that if such fund remains unclaimed till the period of 4 years started from the date when the beneficiary died, the money will be transferred into the treasury as an unclaimed fund. As a honour and advantage bestowed to our foreign customers base on the rules guideing our bank, it was stated obviously that if you are not a Burkina Faso citizen, you have the absolute authority to claim the fund despite your differences from the country of origin of the deceased. So the request of you as a foreigner is necessary to apply for the claim and transfer of the fund smoothly into your reliable bank account as the NEXT OF KIN to the deceased. PERCENTAGE RATIO: note that 35% being (US$11,55,000.00) will be your share in respect of your assistance and account provide for the tranfer, 55% (18,150,000.00) will be my share being the pioneer of the business while the rest 10% (US$3,000,000.00) will be used to install a joint company in your country which will bear our name in particular and whatever profit made out from this company will be used in helping the less privileges, mothrless babies home and charity organization in the world. If you are really sure of your trustworthy, accountability and confidentiality on his transaction, contact me and agree that you will not change your mind to cheat or disappoint me when the fund have getting into your account. Besides you should not entertain any fear because i am sure of the success as an insider in the bank ok. Please reply with the assurance, include your private telephone and fax numbers necessary for effective and easy communication in this transaction. As soon as you reply , call me through my private telephone number indicated above so that i will let you know the next step to follow in order to finalize this transaction immediately. I expect your urgent communication. Yours sincerely, MR BABU MARRINS _________________________________________________________________ Testez Windows Live Mail Beta ! http://www.ideas.live.com/

FROM:PAULSON BENSON TEL:+27-73-7830-560 JOHANNESBURG, SOUTH AFRICA ATTN: MANAGING DIRECTOR/CEO URGENT AND CONFIDENTIAL BUSINESS PROPOSAL I am Mr.PAULSON BENSON the elder son of late Mr.JAMES BENSON of Zimbabwe. I got your contact address from the South African Chambers of Commerce and Industry please don't worry. During the current crises against the farmers of Zimbabwe by the supporters of our President Robert Mugabe to claim all the white owned farms in my country, he ordered all the white farmers to surrender their farms to his party members and their followers. My father was one of the biggest farmers in the country and although a black indegene, he did not support the President?s political ideology.Therefore, the president?s supporters invaded my father?s farm burnt down everything, killed him and confiscated all his investments. After the death of my father, my mother and I together with my younger brother decided to move out of Zimbabwe for the safety of our lives. On our departure from Zimbabwe,we took along with us some money which my father kept in the safe in my mother?s custody which amounted to the sum of US$15,000,000.00 (FIFTEEN MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS) to the Republic of South Africa where we have deposited it as personal valuables in a private security company and sought for political asylum. My mother has suggested and I agree that we have to further move out of the African continent to overseas for actual safety and to do reliable business investments. Therefore we have decided that I should contact any reliable overseas person/firm/company who could assist us to transfer this money out of South Africa through a current investment account because as refugees we are not allowed to operate any account exceeding US$2,000(Two Thousand US Dollars). So we need your help to come down to South Africa to open a bank account through which we can transfer this money to your country.If my proposal is considered, for assisting us to Transfer this money to your country, we unanimously agree to offer you 20% of the total fund,5% will be for any expenses that may be incuured during the transaction ,75% will be for me and my family to invest in your country under your assistance. For detailed information, you can contact me on my direct line or my private e-mail: TEL : +27-73-783-0560 FAX:+27-11-507-6392 EMAIL=paulsonbenson6@yahoo.com.hk NOTE: PLEASE,FOR REASON OF OUR ASYLUM STATUS DO MAINTAIN ABSOLUTE CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECRECY WHILE WE ALSO PROMISE TO DO SAME. I ASSURE YOU THAT THIS TRANSACTION IS 100%RISKFREE. TIME IS OF ESSENCE.YOUR URGENT RESPONSE WILL BE HIGHLY APPRECIATED. BEST REGARDS PAULSON BENSON

FROM THE DESK OF: MRS AJAHA AHMED AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK (ADB) BILL AND EXCHANGE DEPARTMENT, OFFSHORE OFFICE,OUAGADOUGOU, BURKINA-FASO. Dear Friend, I am the Bill and Exchange(assistant) Manager of the Africa development Bank, In my department I discovered an abandoned sum of USD$11.300.000 (ELEVEN MILLION THREE HUNDERS U.S.A DOLLARS). In an account that belongs to one of our foreign customer who died along with his wife and two children in July 2000 in a plane crash. Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased, as indicated in our banking guidelines but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him in the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. You can also confirm this in the website as follow: http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479.stm It is therefore upon this discovery that I in my department now decided to make this business proposals to you and release the money to you as next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we don't want this money to go into the bank treasury as unclaimed fund. The banking law and guidelines here stipulates that if such money remains unclaimed after five years, the money will be transferred into the bank treasury as unclaimed fund. The request of foreigner in this transaction is necessary because our late customer was a foreigner and a Burkinabe cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. We agree that 27% of this money will be for you as foreigner partner, in respect to the provision of a foreign account,3% will be set aside for expenses incurred during the business and 70% would be for me and my colleague, after which we shall visit your country for disbursement according to the percentages indicated. Therefore to enable the immediate transfer of this fund to you as arranged, you must apply first to the bank, and send your account number, your private telephone and fax number for easy and effective communication and location where the money will be remitted. Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or e-mail the text of the application which you shall retype and fax to our foreign remittance maneger,for easy execution of the transaction. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is 100% hitch-free on both side. As all required arrangement have been made for the transfer. You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this letter. Trusting to receive your urgent reply through my alternative Email :mrs_ajaha66@yahoo.fr Best regards. MRS AJAHA AHMED BILL AND EXCHANGE (ASSIST.)MANAGER, AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK ANNEXE, OUAGADOUGOU BURKINA-FASO. _________________________________________________________________ Testez Windows Live Mail Beta ! http://www.ideas.live.com/

FROM: MICHEAL BALOY TEL:2776 44 10054. EMAIL:michaelbaloy@yahoo.com Dear Sir & Madam I know you will be surprise to receive this letter. I am MR.MICHEAL BALOY the only son of the General EDWARD BALOY who was killed during a bloody shoot out claimed the lives of 24 Cols and Generals including the life of the late SAVIMBI of republic of ANGOLA. I got your contact through the South African information of Exchange (S.A.I.E) regarding your trust worthy, as such; I decided to ask for your assistance to transfer some money Out of South Africa into your personal or company account. Be fore my father's death, he was the General in charge of Arms and Ammunition purchase for the Republic of Angola Arms Forces. And in his will he specifically drew my at! tention to the sum of US$35.7 MIL! LION United State Dollars) which deposited in a private Security and finance company in South Africa. IN FACT MY FATHER SAID IN HIS "WILL"AND I QUOTE. MY BELOVED SON, I WISH TO DRAW YOUR ATTENTION TO THE SUM OF US$35.7 MILION, WHICH I DEPOSITED IN PRIVATE SECURITY AND FINANCE COMPANY IN SOUTH AFRICA (JOHANNESBURG) LIFE BEING UNPREDICTABLE ESPECIALLY IN THE MILLITARY. INCASE OF ANYTHING TOMMORROW DO TAKE CARE OF YOUR MOTHER AND MAKE SURE SHE DO NOT LACK ANYTHING. >From the above, you will understand that the lives and our future depend on this money, as such we will be very grateful if you can assist us. We are now leaving in South Africa as political asylum Seekers and financial law of republic of South Africa do not allow Asylum seekers certain financial right to such huge amount of money. In view of this, I cannot invest this money in South Africa, hence my ! asking you to assist me to trans! fer this money out of South Africa to your own personal or Company account overseas for investment purposes. For your effort my family is willing to offer you 30% of the total Money, while 5% will be put aside for local and international expenses Incurred during the transaction and the balance I intend to invest in a Profitable venture in your country or else where you may advice. Please Note that this transaction is 100% risk free, the major thing I require from you is absolute ASSURANCE that the money will be safe when transferred to your account Finally, modalities on how to transfer this money will be discussed Once a genuine interest from you is shown.you can call me on my number +2776 44 10054.reply back with my allternative email address: michaelbaloy@aim.com Thanks and God Bles! s You, Best Regards. MR. MICHEAL BALOY(FOR THE FAMILY)

Mr.Abgottspon Ewald Banque Jacob Safra(Schweiz)AG Bleicherweg 1 / Paradeplatz 8022 ZURICH Switzerland. Email:aewald2000@msn.com Dear Sir, I got your contact on my private search for a reliable and trusted person to handle a transaction of this nature. I know that the contents of this mail might sound so strange, but I want to assure you that every word of it is true.I am Mr.Abgottspon Ewald, a credit officer with Banque Jacob Safra(Schweiz)AG.I have a concealed business suggestion for you.Before the plane crash of Mrs.Dimka Ilkova Boskovic on February 26, 2004 ,Dimka Ilkova Boskovic from the Ministry of Foreign Affairs,macedonia and also a business woman made a fixed deposit for 12 calendar months, with a value of Nine Million,eight Hundred Thousand United State Dollars only in my branch.You can visit this website: http://www.rferl.org/featuresarticle/2004/02/8c37dc80-40e3-4333-8d04-dad352108cb5.html The board of directors of my bank adopted a resolution and as the accounting officer to Mrs.Dimka Ilkova Boskovic I was mandated to provide her next of kin for the payment of this money within 14 working days or forfeit the money to the bank as an abandoned property. Further investigations revealed that Dimka Ilkova Boskovic did not declare any next of kin in her official papers including the paper work of his bank deposit. And she also confided in me the last time she was at my office that no one except me knew of her deposit in my bank. So Nine Million,eight Hundred Thousand United State Dollars is still lying in my bank and no one will ever come forward to claim it. What bothers me most is that the directors of my bank had planned to invoke the abandoned property decree of 1991 to confiscate the funds after the expiration of the period given to me, despairing at the point of exhaustiveness but fortunately, I came across your name. My suggestion to you is that I will like you to stand as the next of kin to Dimka Ilkova Boskovic so that you will be able to receive this funds. However, I seek your consent to present you as the Next of Kin to the deceased. I have contacted an attorney that will prepare the necessary document that will back you up as the next of kin to Dimka Ilkova Boskovic. All I require is your honest cooperation to enable us see this deal through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of law. Be Inform also that we shall share the funds in the ratio 70% for me and 25% for you, while 5% should be for Expenses or Tax as your Government may require. Please endeavor to observe utmost discretion in all matters concerning this issue. I will bring you into a more detailed picture of this transaction when I hear from you. Your earliest response to this letter will be appreciated via my private email address(aewald2000@msn.com). Kind Regards, Mr.Abgottspon Ewald.

FROM THE DESK OF MR.Atik BASSIM BILL AND EXCHANGE FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPT. BANK  OF  AFRICA  ( BOA) OUAGADOUGOU, BURKINA FASO ,                       Dear Friend,   Compliments,   I am the manager of bill and exchange at the foreign remittance department of BANK OF AFRICA. I am writting to seek your coperation over this business deal. In my department,  I discovered an abandoned sum of$15million USD(Fifteen million US dollars)only , in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customers who died along with his entire family in a plane crash that took place in Kenya,East Africa,the Late DR. GEORGE BRUMLEY,a citizen of Atlanta,United States of America but naturalised in Burkinafaso,WestAfrica and  contractor with ECOWAS,(ECONOMIC COMMUNITY OF WEST AFRICAN STATES) .   Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because it cannot be released  unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines but unfortunately , all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I now decided to makethis businness proposal to you and release the money to  you via your foreign bank account as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and this money Could  go into the Bank treasury as unclaimed Bill.   The Banking law and guideline here stipulates that if such money remainedunclamed after four years, the money will betransfered into the Bank treasury as unclaimed fund.The request for your assistance and maximum co-operation as a  foreign citizen  to stand as the next of kin in this business is occasioned by the fact that the deceased customer was a foreigner and a Burkinabe cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. 30 % of this money will be for you as my foreign partner, inrespect to the provision of a foreign account. 10 %will be set aside for expences incured during the business and 60 % would be for me.There after I will come over to your country for disbursement accoding to the percentages indicated.   Therefore to enable the immediate trnansfer of this fund to you as arranged,you must apply first to the bank as the relation or next of kin to the deceased,indicating your claims and wherein the money will be remitted . Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or email the text of application which you will fill and submit to the office of the foreign remittance director of the bank of africa. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is stricly confidential and i will use my position in this Bank to effect a hitch free transfer of the fund. You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this letter. Trusting to hear from you immediately. Please , visit the website below for more informations about the Plane Crash and the tragic death of the deceased and his entire family, Late DR.GEORGE BRUMLEY.   http://www.wral.com/news/2345844/detail.html   Your’s faithfully, MR.Atik BASSIM. Marre des virus ? utilisez Windows Live One Care, c'est gratuit !

ATTENTION: BENEFICIARY This is to officially inform you that we have verified your contract /inheritance file and discovered reasons why you are yet to receive your payment. It is because of irregularities and complications discovered on your payment file by our technical experts in respect to your contract / inheritance payment requirements which have just been duly rectified. Meanwhile, we have been informed that you are still dealing with impostors and non recommended officials in the bank. Such acts must stop for security reasons if you wish to receive your payment. Since we have decided to bring a solution to your problem, right now we have arranged your payment through our atm swift card payment this is the latest instruction by our president Chief, Olusegun Obasonjo (GCFR)federal republic of Nigeria. Below is the arrangement... The swift card center will send you an ATM CARD which you will use to withdrew your money from any atm machine in any part of the world, but the maximum is one thousand dollars per day, so if you would like to receive your fund through this way do let us know by contacting the card payment center Dr Hassan Ali on E-mail (paymastergeneral66@myway.com) and Prof.Charles c. Soludo, Governor Central Bank of Nigeria on email for more information:(profsoludocbn60@yahoo.com).Tel;234-8055158993. And also send the following information to swift card center: 1 phone and fax number, 2 address where you want them to send the card through DHL courier service (p.o box not accepted) 3 your full name and total amount you are expecting. Instead of losing your fund.Please indicate to the card center the total sum you are expecting and for your information you have to stop any further communication with any institution or office until you receive the ATM CARD. Call CBN Governor as soon as you receive this important message on his direct number:234-8055158993 for more direction on this regards and also update him for further instruction and directives.Note:because of impostors,we hereby issue you our code of conduct tag number which is (105)so you must have to indicate this code when contacting the card payment center. We await your urgent response. THANKS, DR.USMAN ABUBAKAR DIRECTOR OF FOREIGN REMITTANCE CENTRAL BANK OF NIGERIA.

NOTIFICATION OF BEQUEST ATTN. On behalf of my church member, late Chief Sir Daniel Duru of the Blessed Memory, I write to notify you that my late member Chief Sir Daniel Duru made you one of beneficiary to the bequest sum of Ten Million six Hundred Thousand US Dollars ($10,600,000,00) in the Codicil to his will and last Testament. Late Chief Sir Daniel Duru Died after a brief illness on may 1st 2004. Until his death, Late Chief Sir Daniel Duru was a Renowned Philanthropist; A Businessman of an international repute and an industrialist, infact he was blessed by God. Chief Sir Daniel did not play with the life and progress of the people who were opportuned to meet him on the way and among all he had a very big regard for his God the things of God and works of God. Late Chief Sir Daniel Duru used his resources to serve humanity and thus touched the lives of many through charity. According to him, he said, He is giving back to God just a Little from what God had given to him?. as a result of that he is giving you this because of your involvement in Christian activities, helping the less privileged and in making better the world situation. As Trustees and Executes of this will, I wish to inform you that the will was read at the Owerri High Court Probate Division (Registry) August 7th, 2004, as the law provides and is in execution. You are hereby required to by this notification to confirm your ownership to this Legacy by forwarding proofs of identity. Also send a personal telephone and fax numbers for easy communication. Most importantly, if there is any disparity on the name and address or if your name, address and any other useful information does not tally with the information we have, it then means that you are not the rightful or bonafide beneficiary of this particular request as it contained in paragraph four (4) of the codicil to the last Testament of the Benefactor (Chief Sir Daniel Duru. As we Cannot afford to give or pay to a wrong Person or Body. on that note please do not inconvenience your very self by replying. But, if the information (your name and address)is compatible with the information we have, you are hereby advice to confirm this notification immediately, for you are the rightful one (person or body). We would detail you on the procedure and involvement in benefiting this will on receipt of your reply letter or e-mail. God bless you. Best regards. REV. MIKE EZEKIEL (GENERAL OVERSEER, HEALING FIELDS MINISTRY.) NO 23 ADEOLA ODEKUN VICTORIA ISLAND LAGOS NIGERIA

FROM: MR ALIU SALAMI. AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK (ANNEX) BILL AND EXCHANGE DEPARTMENT, OFFSHORE OFFICE,OUAGADOUGOU,BURKINA-FASO. Dear, I know that this letter may come to you as a surprise, I got your contact address from the computerized search when I was searching for a business partner. My name is Mr Aliu Salami, I am the Bill and Exchange (assistant) Manager of African Development Bank Ouagadouguo, Burkina Faso. In my department I discovered an abandoned sum of eighteen million three hundred thousand United State of American dollars ($18.3MILLION U.S.A DOLLARS) in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customer Mr Hazim Ibrahim from Alexandra Eygpt who died along with his family in Siber airline that crashed into sea at Isreal on 4th October 2001. Since I got information about his death I have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless somebody applies for it as the next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines, but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him in the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I decided to make this business proposal to you and release the money to you as next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it because I don't want the money to go into the bank treasury as unclaimed Bill. The banking laws and guidelines here stipulates that if such money remains unclaimed after five years the money will be transfered into the bank treasury as unclaimed fund. The request of foreigner in this transaction is necessary because our late customer was a foreigner and a Burkinabe cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. I have agreed that 33% of this money will be for you as foreigner partner in respect to the provision of a foreign account, 2% will be set aside for expenses that might occurred during the business and 65% would be for me, after which I shall visit your country for disbursement according to the percentages indicated. Therefore to enable the immediate transfer of this fund to you as we arranged you will furnished me with a good receiving account details where the money will be transfered, your private telephone and fax number for easy communication. Upon receipt of your reply I will send to you by fax or e-mail a text of the application which you shall retype and fax to our foreign remittance manager for easy execution of the transaction. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is 100% hitch-free on both side as all required arrangement has been made for the transfer. Please I would like you to keep this transaction confidential and as a top secret as you may wish to know that I am a Bank official. Trusting to hear from you immediately. Yours Sincerely, Mr Aliu Salami. _________________________________________________________________ Découvrez Windows Live Messenger : le futur de MSN Messenger ! www.windowslivemessenger.fr

FROM THE DESK OF MRS. ALIMA AHMED THE BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING UNIT. FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPT. BANK OF AFRICA (BOA)ANNEX OUAGA-BURKINA FASO. I am Alima Ahmed, the manager in charge of auditing and accounting unit foreign remittance department of bank of africa (BOA)ouaga-burkina faso in west Africa. With due respect and regards I have decided to contact you on a business transaction that will be very beneficial to both of us at the end of the transaction ,During our investigation and auditing in the bank, in my department I came across a very huge sum of money belonging to a deceased person, a foriegner who died in a plane crash and the fund has been dormant in his account with the bank without any claim of the fund in our custody either from his family or relation before my discovery to this development,Although personally, I kept this information secrete within myself and to enable the whole plans and idea be profitable and uccessful during the time of execution. The amount involved is (us$7,500.000) (Seven Million Five Hundred Thousand United State Dollars ). Meanwhile, all the whole arrangement and directives needed to put claim over this fund as the next of kin to the deceased, Upon your acceptance all the information will be forward to you as soon as you indicate your interest and willingness to assist me and also benefit your self to this great business opportunity,In fact, I could have done this deal alone but because of my position in this country as a civil servant,we are not allowed to operate a foriegn account and would eventually raise an eye brow on my side during the time of transfer because I work in this bank, this is the actual reason why it will require a second party or fellow who will forward claims as the next of kin with affidavit of trust of Oath to the bank and also present a foriegn account where you will need the said fund to be transferred into, after due verification and clarification to designated bank account,I will not fail to inform you that this transaction is 100% risk free, On smooth conclusion of this transaction, you will be entitled to 40% of the total sum as ratification, while 10% will be set aside to take care of expenses that may arise during the time of transfer such as telephone bills etc,While 50% will be for me. Please you have been adviced to keep top secret as I am still in service and intend to retire from service after I conclude this deal with you, I will be monitoring the whole situation here in the bank until you confirm the money in your account and ask me to come down there for subsequent shearing of the fund according to percentages previously indicated and further investment,either in your country or any other country you may advice me to invest in. All other necessary information will be sent to you when I hear from you, I suggest you get back to me as soon as possible, stating your wish in this deal. Trusting to receive your urgent reply through my alternative Email :mrs_alima_ahmed20@yahoo.fr Your's Sincerely alima Ahmed _________________________________________________________________ Express yourself instantly with MSN Messenger! Download today it's FREE! http://messenger.msn.click-url.com/go/onm00200471ave/direct/01/

Greetings I am Barr Charles Brown, a Canadian attorney based in Manchester, United Kingdom and the personal attorney to Late Mr. Mark Michelle, a French National. Late Mr. Mark Michelle until his untimely death was a private oil consultant/contractor with the British Petroleum Company, herein after shall be referred to as my client. On 23rd December 2003, my client and his wife with their three children were involved in a ghastly auto crash; all occupants of the vehicle unfortunately lost their lives. Since then, I have made several enquiries with his countrys' embassies to locate any of my clients extended relatives. After several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to personally contact you with this business partnership proposal. The deceased had a deposit valued presently at Eighteen Million United states dollars and the company has issued me a notice to provide his next of kin or beneficiary. Having been unsuccessful in locating any of my late client relatives for over two (2) years now. I am now seeking your consent to present you as the next of kin/beneficiary to the deceased so that the proceeds of this account can be paid to you. I have worked out modalities for achieving my aim of appointing a next of kin as well as transferring the money abroad for us to share in the ratio of 50% for me and 35% for you, and we shall collectively donate 10% to the charity homes course while 5% will be set aside for any incurable expenses both local and international. The money transfer paperwork itself will include a certificate of origin so that the receiving bank does not ask questions. Also the paperwork will include proper certificate that the fund being transferred is from non-criminal sources. In short this will be a proper and legal money transfer with no risk involved. The transaction is guaranteed to succeed without any problem. All I need is your trust and confidence. As soon as I hear from you, I shall provide you with further clarification that you may need to know. Best wishes, Mr. Charles Brown.

FROM: CAPT. JOE ALEX. TELE 00226 78 02 21 52 CENTRAL VILLE OUAGADOUGOU, BURKINA-FAS0 DEAR SIR / MADAM STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL I AM SURE, THIS LETTER WILL BE A SURPRISE TO YOU, I AM CAPT. JOE ALEX. OF THE REPUBLIC OF LIBERIAN (WEST AFRICA) AND THE FORMER AIDE DE CAMP OF THE EX- PRESIDENT, CHARLES TAYLOR, OF THE REPUBLIC OF LIBERIA. I GOT YOUR ADDRESS THROUGH INTERNET SEARCH HERE IN OUAGADOUGOU, BURKINA FASO ALTHOUGH I DID NOT KNOW YOU BEFORE BUT GOD HAS DIRECTED ME TO CONTACT YOU THAT YOU WILL BE CAPABLE OF HANDLING THIS TRANSACTION SUCCESFULLY WITHOUT HITCH. THE THE EX- PRESIDENT, CHARLES TAYLOR, SUCCESSFULLY TOPPLED THE FORMER PRESIDENT OF MY COUNTRY, THE LATE SAMUEL DOE AND RULED PEACEFULLY FOR FEW YEARS. HOW EVER, FOUR (4) YEARS AGO, THE REBELS FROM THE NORTHERN PART OF MY COUNTRY REBELLED AGAINST THE GOVERNMENT. EVER SINCE THEN, MY COUNTRY HAS BEEN AT WAR. DUE TO THIS WAR, PUBLIC FUNDS AND PROPERTIES HAVE BEEN CONSTANTLY LOOTED AND STOLEN BY THE REBEL SOLDIERS AND GOVERNMENT FUNCTIONARIES. HOWEVER, WHEN THE REBEL ATTACK BECAME SO SERIOUS, L WAS ASSIGNED BY THE PRESIDENT ON BEHALF OF HIS CABINET THREE YEARS AGO TO PURCHASE AMMUNITION WORTH OF U.S. $ 11 MILLION (ELEVEN MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS) FROM BURKINA FASO, WHILE WE WERE STILL NEGOTIATING FOR THE ARMS DEAL IN BURKINA FASO , WE HEARD OVER THE NEWS THAT THE REBELS HAS INVADED THE CAPITAL CITY, MONROVIA AND THE PRESIDENT CHARLES TAYLOR, HAS BEEN GIVEN AUTOMATON TO RELINQUISH POWER, WHICH TOOK PLACE ON THE 11TH DAY OF AUGUST 2003, SO WE SAW THIS AS A GOLDEN OPPORTUNITY TO DIVERT THE FUND FOR OUR OWN INTEREST , COUPLED WITH THE NEWS WE HEARD ABOUT AMERICAN AND ECOWAS TROOPS SENT TO MONROVIA FOR PEACE KEEPING. FURTHERMORE, WE DEPOSITED THE FUND WITH THE SECURITY AND FINANCE HOUSE, HERE IN OUAGADOUG, BURKINA FASO. I AM PRESENTLY LIVING IN BURKINA FASO ON ASYLUM. THE FINANCIAL LAW OF BURKINA FASO DOES NOT ALLOW ASYLUM ANY FINANCIAL RIGHTS. IN VIEW OF THIS, COUPLED WITH THE WAY IN WHICH THE MONEY WAS ACQUIRED, I DECIDED NOT TO INVEST THIS MONEY ANYWHERE IN BURKINA FASO OR THE WESTERN AFRICAN CONTINENT AS A WHOLE. FOR YOUR EFFORTS, I AM PREPARED TO OFFER YOU 30% OF THE TOTAL SUM IF YOU WILL ASSIST ME TO TRANSFER THIS MONEY INTO YOUR ACCOUNT OVERSEAS, 5% HAVE ALSO BEEN MAPPED OUT FOR EXPENSES THAT MIGHT BE INCURRED IN THE PROCESS OF THIS TRANSACTION, AND REMAINING 65% WILL BE FOR I AND MY FAMILY WHICH WE INTEND INVESTING IN YOUR COUNTRY OR ANY WHERE YOU MAY DEEM FIT. FROM THE ABOVE, YOU WILL UNDERSTAND THAT MY ENTIRE LIFE AND OUR FUTURE AND THAT OF OUR FAMILIES DEPENDS ON THIS MONEY, AS SUCH I WILL VERY MUCH APPRECIATE IF YOU CAN ASSIST US. PLEASE NOTE THAT THIS TRANSACTION IS RISK FREE. THE MAJOR THING I REQUEST FROM YOU IS ABSOLUTE ASSURANCE THAT THIS MONEY WILL BE SAFE WHEN TRANSFERRED TO YOUR ACCOUNT. IF YOU CAN BE OF ASSISTANCE, KINDLY CONTACT ME ON THE ABOVE TELEPHONE NUMBER. EVEN IF YOU HAVE DECIDED OTHERWISE, I WILL BE MOST GRATEFUL IF YOU MAINTAIN THE CONFIDENTIALITY OF THIS MATTER. I AM LOOKING FORWARD TO YOUR URGENT REPLY. YOURS SINCERELY, CAPT. JOE ALEX (FOR THE FAMILY) PLEASE REPLY ME THROUGH THIS MAIL BOX (J_ALEX1BF@LATINMAIL.COM) ¡Miles de amigos con tus mismas aficiones! http://www.latinchat.com

Hello, I have got your contact in the cause of my serious search for a reliable foreign partner through a profile in which convinced me of your honesty. However, I am Justice Sonko my father was a businessman and also one the leaders of Liberians United for Reconciliation and Democracy movement that fought against the Government in Liberia West African. I confide in you hoping you will never betray me at last, My most required concern is for you to recognised me as your best friend while esterblisbing a long lasting relationship for our future. Presently,I am in Dakar-senegal with the sum of Eight Million Two Hundred Thousand United States Dollars (US$8.2m) .These money was realise by my father before his death thruogh Diamond sales when Revolutional Movement (L.U.R.D )conquered one of the Diamond region , by then my father was the Chief in my region and the Director Of Kono Gold and Diamond Corp. The money was kept under my father care for the purchase of arms, it was a sitution of war so my father died I consider it my chance and then move immediately to Dakar-Senegal where my late father Deposited this fund with a holding company for save keeping since then i have being looking for a nice business to invest this fund into. My aim of contacting you is to assist me in two ways (1)to help and transfer the money to your country (2)and to help me get a profitable business for investment any where in oversea all is base on your professional advise and acceptance to assist me. Note that a substantial portion of these money would be compensated to you for all your assistance. Please, do not hesitate to reply immediately in other to know the next thing to do on how to move this money to your country through proper arrangement. Finally, keep this with your utmost secrecy and confidentality as you can understand my condition in Dakar-Senegal because i am into hiding as so many people knows me. Thanks for your co-operation. Best Regards. Justice Sonko, +2214542103

>From The Desck Of Mr Liow Hanoi Selangor Malaysia Email:liow_hanoi46@gawab.com Attention: Sir/ Madam. Firstly, I must solicit your confidence in this transaction,this is by virtue of its nature as being utterly confidential and top secret.Before I introduce myself, I wish to inform you that this letter is not an hoax mail and I urge you to treat it with seriousness. We want to transfer the sum of Nine Million Seven Hundred Thousand United States Dollars ($9,700.000.00) to an oversea account from one of the banks located in Malaysia. I want to ask you, If you are not capable to quietly look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable and fit to provide either an existing bank account or to set up a new Bank a/c immediately to receive this money, even an empty A/C can serve to receive this money, as long as you will remain honest to me till the end of this important business ,I am trusting in you and believing in God that you will never let me down either now or in future. I am Mr.Liow Hanoi a personal account officer to late Mr Morris Anthony an INDUSTRALIST. During the course of auditing,it was discovered that since the death of this INDUSTRALIST no one has come forward to lay claim to this funds. So the bank issued me a memo to provide his next of kin or forfeith the funds. This account was opened with the bank in 1998 and since 2002 nobody has operated on this account again, after going through some old files in my records,I discovered that my late client died without a [Heir/WILL] hence the money is floating and if I do not remit this money out urgently it will be forfeited for nothing.The owner of this account is an American and great industrialist who lost his life along with his family members leaving nobody as next of kin. No other person knows about this account or any thing concerning it,the account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to me as well that the account is a secret account. The total amount involved is Nine Million Seven Hundred Thousand United States Dollars only [$9,700.000.00] and we wish to transfer this money into a safe foreigners account abroad,but I don't know any foreigner, I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be approved to a local person here,rather it will only be approved to a foreigner who has information about the account,which I shall give to you upon your positive response. I am revealing this to you with believe in God that you will never let me down in this business, you are the first and the only person that I am contacting for this business, so please reply urgently so that I will inform you the next step to take urgently.I need your strong assurance that you will never let us down, me and the key bank officials who are deeply involved with me in this business. I guarantee that this transaction will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. The bank official will destroy all documents of transaction immediately we receive this money,leaving no trace to any place. I will use my position and influence to obtain all legal approvals for onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance from the relevant ministries and foreign exchange departments. At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 25% of the total amount,70% will be for us, while 5% will be for expenses both parties might have incurred during the process of transferring. I look forward to your earliest reply. PLEASE, TREAT THIS PROPOSAL AS TOP SECRET. Please email me at: liow_hanoi46@gawab.com Best Regards, Mr Liow Hanoi

FROM: MISS STELLA MAKASIN ABIDJAN, COTE D'IVOIRE. HELLO, l AM MISS. STELLA MAKASIN in, THE DAUGHTER OF LATE MICHAEL MAKASIN KIJANI FROM REPUBLIC OF SIERRA LEONE, MY FATHER IS A LIMITED COCOA AND GOLD BUSINESSES IN SIERRA LEONE. AFTER MY FATHER'S TRIP TO ABIDJAN COTE D'IVIORE TO NEGOTIATE FOR A COCOA AND GOLD BUSINESS WHICH HE INTENDED TO ESTABLISH IN ABIDJAN ; IT CAME TO PASS THAT BARELY A WEEK HE CAME BACK FROM HIS TRIP TO ABIDJAN HE WAS INVOLVED IN A FATAL CAR ACCIDENT IN COMPANY WITH MY MOTHER AND A BROTHER WHICH LEFT MY MOTHER INSTANTLY DEAD BUT MY FATHER SURVIVED FOR 5-DAYS AND LATER DIED ALSO IN THE HOSPITAL. MY BROTHER WAS THE ONLY SURVIVOR IN THE ACCIDENT. BEFORE THE ACCIDENT, HE MY FATHER DISCLOSED TO ME THAT HE DEPOSITED THE SUM OF ($12,000,000.00) TWELVE MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS IN A BANK IN ABIDJAN IVORY COAST. THE MONEY WAS MEANT FOR COCOA AND GOLD BUSINESS HE WENTED TO ESTABLISH IN ABIDJAN.HE ALSO, EXPLAINED TO ME THAT HE USED MY NAME AS HIS NEXT OF KIN TO DEPOSIT . MY FATHER INFORMED ME WHERE I WILL GET THE LODGEMENT RECEIPT IN OUR HOUSE WHICH COVERS THE DEPOSIT OF THE FUND, AND INSTRUCTED ME TO SEEK FOR A RELIABLE AND TRUSTWORTHY FOREIGN BUSINESS PARTNER FOR A LIFE TIME INVESTMENT OF THE MONEY. HE MADE THE DEPOSIT ON THE PRETEXT THAT THE MONEY WILL BE TRANSFERED LATER TO AN UN-NAMED BANK ACCOUNT WHERE THE MONEY WOULD BE INVESTED INTO BUSINESS; THIS IS TO DEFUSE ANY GOVERNMENT HAND IN THE MONEY IN HIS ABSENCE SUCH AS DEATH - BECAUSE THE GOVERNMENT OF COTE D'IVORE AND THE BANK ON AWARE OF OUR FATHER's DEATH WOULD HAVE A SHARE OF THE MONEY WHICH WE MAY BE EXPECTED TO RECEIVE BACKONLY A TOKEN OF ABOUT 1/3. THIS IS WHY I AM SEEKING YOUR ASSISTANCE TO PROVIDE A NEW OR OLD TRUSTWORTHY BANK ACCOUNT WHERE THE FUND WILL BE TRANSFERRED INTO. AND TO MAKE ARRANGEMENT FOR ME AND MY BROTHER TO COME OVER TO YOUR COUNTRY AFTER THE SUCESSFUL TRANSFER OF THE FUND THERE ; ALSO FOR ME AND MY BROTHER TO FURTHER OUR EDUCATION ABROAD. SO THAT WE CAN INVEST THE MONEY IN ANY LUCRATIVE BUSINESS IN YOUR COUNTRY BECAUSE THIS IS OUR ONLY HOPE IN LIFE , WE ARE READY TO COMPENSATE YOU WITH 20% OF THE MONEY ON YOUR ASSISTANCE TO HELP US TRANSFER THIS MONEY TO YOUR ACCOUNT IN YOUR COUNTRY AND TO HELP US INVEST IT IN YOUR COUNTRY. PLEASE IF YOU HAVE ACCEPTED TO HELP US IN THIS TRANSACTION I WANT YOU TO GET BACK TO ME THROUGH THIS EMAIL ADDRESS (stellamakasin25@yahoo.com) OR CALL ME AT 0022506021695 I AM WAITING ANXIOUSLY TO HEAR FROM YOU, THANKS AND GOD BLESS YOU. YOURS TRULY, MISS STELLA MAKASIN AND BROTHER

BARRISTER RICHARD WILSON. RICHARD WILSON & ASSOCIATES DAKAR-SENEGAL TEL: + 221 4183317 Email: barrwilson@katamail.com Dear Friend, I am Barrister Richard Wilson, I am the personal attorney to Mr. Patrick a National of your country who works with a petroleum Company in Europe and he is known and referred to as my Client, he died along with his entire family of a wife and two children in a car accident. Since we heard of his death, I have made several enquires to his embassy to locate any of my clients extended relatives but all my efforts proved unsuccessful and to no avail. After these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to track his last name over the Internet, to locate any member of his family hence I contacted you. Now my contacts to you is to assist me in repatriating his money which is been lodged in a security/Finance company in a trunk box in Europe, before the money will be confiscated or declared unserviceable by the security/Finance company where he deposit this money valued about $20,500,000 (Twenty Million Five Hundred thousand United States Dollars) More importantly, the security/finance company where the deceased client deposited this huge sum of money has served me a write of notice to provide the NEXT OF KIN of my client or the (money) will be confiscated and send to the government treasury as unclaimed funds. Since I have tried and failed on several occasions in locating his relatives I am now seeking for your consent to present you as the next of kin to the deceased so that the money will be paid to you while I will come over to your country for the sharing. I will take 45% while you will take 45% and 5% will be for any expenses incurred during the transaction and the remaining 5% will go to any charity organization. All I require is your honest cooperation to enable us see this deal through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you and I from any breach of the law. Finally, if this business interest you, please get in touch with me immediately via my private email address or telephone for security reasons, I will welcome messages that come only from my private email address and telephone. Also indicate to me your contact phone and fax numbers to enable me call you immediately for more information. PLEASE, I RESPECT CONFIDENTIALITY AND I WOULD LIKE YOU TO RESPECT THE CONFIDENTIALITY OF THIS TRANSACTION. I await your urgent response to this message. Yours sincerely, Barrister Richard Wilson (ESQ) TEL: + 221 4183317 Email: barristerwilson@terramail.com.sv

From: Mrs. Ngoni Elita Tawanda. Dear friend, WIDOW IN NEED. Please don't be surprised to receive this letter from me since we do not know each other before . I am MRS.Elita Ngoni Tawanda,the wife of late Ndinonzi Kajengo Tawanda, a farmer in ZIMBABWE who was recently murdered in the land dispute in my country. I got your contact through network online hence decided to write you. Before the death of my husband, he made a deposit with a security company somewhere which I will tell you after I have received your positive response, The consignment was declared to contain GEM STONES shipped on diplomatic cover to avoid customs detecting the actual contents. The actual content is the sum of US12.5 million (twelve million, Five Hundred thousand United States dollars only). This was done when he noticed the looming danger in Zimbabwe on land policies. The security company does not know the actual contents of the boxes consignment as it was not disclosed to them for security reasons. This amount was meant for the purchase of new Agricultural machineries and chemicals for our Farms and establishment of new farms in Swaziland. This land problem came when Zimbabwean President Mr.Robert Mugabe introduced a new Land Act Reform that wholly affected the rich white farmers and some few rich black farmers alike. This resulted to the killing and mob action by Zimbabwean war veterans and some lunatics in the society. In fact a lot of people were killed because of this Land reform Act for which my husband was one of the victims. It is against this background that, all my family members fled Zimbabwe for fear of our lives. We are currently taking refuge in the Malawi where we sort political asylum. At this point, I have now decided to transfer my late husband’s money to a safe custody. All I want is to introduce you to the security company as the next of kin to my late husband, I am saddled with the responsibility of seeking a genuine partner that could assist me without the knowledge of my government who are bent on taking everything we have gotten. To the best of my knowledge, the Zimbabwean government had written their counter-part in Malawi to extradite me and my children to face the laws of the land. To the glory of God, the Malawian government has not yielded to this request because International Bodies are watching. We have been under close watch by the authority and the asylum we signed do not permit us to live country hence we cannot travel to take delivery. I am seeking for a partner who I have to entrust my future and that of my family in his or her hands. I must let you know that this transaction is free from risk. If you accept to assist us, do please contact me urgently to finalize all the arrangement with the security company for the delivery of the consignment to you. I would have done the collection and invested these funds myself. But presently now that we are under political asylum in Malawi and as an asylum seeker; I am not permitted by law to engage in any gainful economic activity as I do not have legal status. This is my reason for contacting you. Should this endeavor be of interest to you, please respond in the affirmative via my email address so that we can discuss and agree upon a remuneration that will be most suitable to you for the role you are to play in this endeavor? Investment to be made in your country with our share with your advice.Contact me through this email box: elitatawanda1962@yahoo.co.uk </ym/Compose?To=elitatawanda1962@yahoo.co.uk> Awaiting your positive response. Regards, Thanks, GOD BLESS YOU Yours Faithfully, Mrs. Elita Tawanda. For: (the family

>From Sammar Abubakar, Dakar Senegal ,West Africa. Attn : Based on the information I gathered about you from a very reliable source, I am happy to send this message to you. I hope you will consider and give it urgent and favourable reply. My name is Sammar abubakar,23 years,a citizen of Sierra - Leone.The Son of late Bala abubakar, who before his death was the person managing the Sierra - Leone goldand diamond corporation( SGDC ) . I hope you are aware of the war which has ravaged my country for the past years now . It was in one of this attacks by the rebels that led to the death of my Father and Two of my Sister, now I am left with only my Yonger Sister Nene. I was terrified of the situation and because of this I escaped with my yonger sister Nene from Sierra - Leone to Senegal into a refugee camp. Senegal Was Where My Late Father have deposited US$ 10,.000.000.00 (Ten Million United States Dollars ). To be honest with you, this is the only legacy left for me by my Late Father which Iam with the certificate of deposit and other necessary documents regarding this deposit. My aim of contacting you is to seek for your able assistance as a front in transferring this fund abroad into an account , then as a business developer , you can help us to invest wisely in areas you deem lucrative and finally obtain a residential permit for us to stay comfortable in your country of abode . Presently we cannot go back to Sierra- Leone because of the situation there and you know that Senegal. where we are now is politically unstable; we therefore wish you could help us get out of here before it become worse. We are prepared to offer you 20% of the total funds for your able assistance and support and would send you proofs of the funds as soon as we favourably hear from you. Finally I implore you to treat this transaction with secrecy and confidentiality for security reasons. Note that this transaction is 100% Risk free and absolutely confidential. You can reply US through Our private e-mail sammar_sisternene@yahoo.co.uk . Also I Will like you to send US your Full Information . 1) TELEPHONE NUMBER 2) YOUR FAS NUMBER 3) YOUR PASPORT 4) HOUSE ADDRESS Thanking you in anticipation and God bless. Sincerely Yours Sammar And Sister .

Call me + 225 07 500630 Contacts email me ( rita_02555abed@yahoo.com GREETINGS, Based on the information and recommendation I got about quick growth of business, investment and commerce in your country, I deemed it necessary to write and inform you about my interest to invest in any viable venture in joint partnership with you. I am Mrs Rita Abed the first wife of king George Abed K.S.M the king of mende tribe in Sierra-Leone. On the 19th May, 2004 my husband was murdered by some rebel group on the accusation that he is a great sponsor and in support to restore the democratically elected President of Alhadji Tejan Kabba. Almost half of the palace was burnt.Fortunately I was not in the place when they raided the palace my husband married 4 wives with 16 children two of the wives, with my 3 children where murdered in cold blood while my second son escape the incident with bullet wounds on his right leg at the moment where the remaining families are I don?t know their way about whether they are alive or not. Right now I am left alone with only one son since the sudden assassination of my husband the family has been displaced and totally disorganized left with noting. Early that year befor my husband was Late husband was murdered he came back from travel and gave me some document to keep for him as usual he told me that he deposited 18.5 million USD in a trunk box with private security company in Abidjan Côte d?Ivoire as a family treasure. So I decided to go and search for the documents where I use to keep them I discovered the documents covering the deposit he made with the company and some other documents like his will and other documents for his business. As my town has been a serious war zone, I made arrangement with two peace keeping force to help me and my son move out of the country, however we moved out of Sierra-Leone successfully, to Abidjan Côte d?Ivoire where we are now. I have gone and conform the deposit with the company with all the documents all the documents are with me here. Now I wish to transfer these funds abroad and enter into a business venture as the country (Côte d?Ivoire) is no longer in peace since they conducted their Presidential election on the 22nd October 2004 the country has witness all sort of political unrest ranging from ethnic clash which resulted to killing of innocent citizens and strangers people are living in fears as the country is no longer that peaceful nation as it was before due to this reason that I have decided to contact you, to assist me to lift this my consignment out of this country. Please I need your assistance. Waiting for your urgent reply.Thanks and God bless. Best regards.(rita_02555abed@yahoo.com) Mrs Rita Abed.+22507500630 _________________________________________________________________ MSN Messenger: appels gratuits de PC à PC ! http://www.msn.fr/msger/default.asp

Miss Aranima Enfandy. UNHCR Refugee Camp, Danane, Cote d'Ivoire.   Dearest One,   A PLEA FOR ASSISTANCE.   It's my pleasure to contact you for an investment assistance which I intend to establish with you in your country.   Though we have not met with you before but I believe, one has to risk confiding in someone to succeed sometimes in life. However is not mandatory nor will in any manner compel you to honour against your will.    I am the only daughter to the Late Markeni Enfandy, from the Nshili District of Gikomgoro Province in the Republic of Rwanda. My Father before his death was a successful Gold and Cocoa Merchant in Johannesburg, South Africa and Ghana. Barely a week my father returned from his usual European business trips, on Wednesday 14th June 2004, he was attacked and killed by some unknown assassins together with my dearest Mum.   The Police could not trace the killers till today, and because I do not know those behind my parents brutal killing and their reasons, I felt out of fear that my safety is not guaranteed, that is the reason why I decided to relocate with the help of the International Care to Abidjan in Cote D' Ivoire (formerly Ivory Coast) to save my life.   They loved me so much, and I was like their confidants to them before their untimely death, as such my Dad gave me information痴 where he kept the documents on the very huge amount .(USD$10.500,000.00)   Which he kept for the family. Presently the money is in a Courier's Company Bonded Warehouse called the (IVSF) (full information痴 to be disclosed later to you on confirmation of your acceptance to assist me.   I have decided to invest this money in your country or anywhere safe enough outside Africa for security and political reasons and because of the problems in where I am now (Abidjan).    I want you to stand as my appointed beneficiary whom will receive the consignment on my behalf since it was deposited for shipment which stands the best way to retrieve the deposit.   Note: The Courier's Company does not know the exact content of the box, as the content was declared to be classified documents and valuables.   The shipment was done with Diplomatic Immunity [not to be inspected by any authority].   If you can be of assistance to me I will be pleased to offer to you 10% of the total fund for your assistance and your advice for the investments.   I hope to hear from you soonest for us to proceed.   Thank you and God bless you Yours Sincerely, Miss Aranima Enfandy

Protect Your PC Now ! -- 0 Yen Security Campaign

Waleed Abdalla Ibrahim Mohamed Birmingham, United Kingdom. Email: darfurefugee@yahoo.fr Dear Sir, Kindly Pardon me if this my letter would be an embarrassment to you for I am Waleed Abdalla Ibrahim Mohamed, a Sudanese from the town of Kass in Southern Darfur writing you from Birmingham, (United Kingdom), I am presently a Political Refugee in United Kingdom away from my native Country (Sudan), where there is a raging and devastating Civil war going on between the Southern Sudan Rebel Forces (Sudan People's Liberation Army) and Arab militias (Janjaweed) supported by the Government Forces loyal of President Umar Hassan al-Bashir. Bashir and his party have controlled the government since he led the military coup on 30 June 1989. The Darfur conflict erupted in early 2003. Fighting among various factions has killed hundreds of thousands of people and displaced more than 2 million, most escaping to larger towns where they stay in camps for "internally displaced people," and some crossing the border into Chad, where they live in refugee camps, straining local resources. Attacks on civilians during the conflict have been brutal and include burning homes, killing and rape. There has been signed a Darfur Peace Agreement between some of the parties in Darfur. This agreement is supervised by African Union Mission in Sudan (AMIS), though the war is still going on. Before the escalation of the war I was a VOLUNTIER SOCIAL WORKER and during my duties one of the local army Commander who was wounded in battle and dying from the wound handed over to me documents showing the sum of Twelve Million United States Dollars (US$12 Million) sent overseas mainly for purchasing foods, pharmaceutical drugs, Clothings etc for millions of Southern Sudanese refugees who have been impoverished, battered and displaced by years of Civil war in our lands. I am therefore using this medium to solicit for your assistance. Your contacts were obtained by me during my search on the Internet for a reliable person that would assist us in claiming this money from the Secret Vault of a Financial Institution where it was deposited in a friendly Country through the help of a sympathetic Senior Nurse attached to the Red Cross International Society some time ago, though the Nurse is late now as she died of Typhoid fever shortly after but there is a particular Financial Agent who would assist you in claiming the money and using part of it to buy foods, pharmaceutical drugs, Clothing etc for millions of Southern Sudanese refugees. I would send copy of a POWER OF ATTORNEY given to me by the Late Commander which I would send alongside copies of my INTERNATIONAL PASSPORT and a second Power of Attorney to you that would enable you claim the funds from the Financial Institution upon your agreement and readiness to assist us. I wish to repeat here and also wish to remind you of the TOP SECRECY this transaction requires, as I expect your positive response through this above Email address as my movement is presently restricted by law covering Political Refugees, though I might give you a telephone number later where you can talk with me. On receiving your positive response we hope to finish this transaction within one week as a lot of our people are dying from sicknesses, diseases and hunger. Expecting your URGENT Positive response and thanks in advance. Yours Sincerely, Waleed Abdalla Ibrahim Mohamed P/S. If you are not interested in assisting us, we beg you to destroy this letter so that it does not fall into wrong hands.

>From Mr. Thompson J. Alber Dear Friend, I sincerely hope that after you read this mail you will respond to my call, let me start by introducing myself my name is Thompson J. Alber. I am 70 years old, a British living in West Africa. I am a businessman and own two companies here in Ouagadougou, married with two children. My wife and two children died in a car accident six years ago but before this happened my business and concern for making money was all I lived for I never really cared about other values in life but since the loss of my family, I have found a new desire to assist helpless families. I have been helping orphans in motherless homes, I have donated some money to orphans in Sudan, America and some Asian countries. Before I became ill, I kept some money, Ten million,three hundred thousand dollars (US$10.3million) to be precise in a long term deposit account in a Bank. Presently, I'm in a hospital my doctor told me I have prostate cancer that I have a few months to live. It is my last wish to see this money distributed to charity organizations. Because so much of my wealth has been plundered by relatives and friends since my illness, hence I cannot live with the agony of entrusting this huge responsibility to any of them since the money in the Bank is the last fund that I have left. Right now I am partially stranded in the hospital due to the nature of my sickness so I am appealing to you to help me collect the deposit from the Bank and distribute it amongst charity organizations. I would want you to use your discretion to distribute the money and keep 20% of it for yourself. Feel free to reimburse yourself when you have the money for any cost you might have incurred during the process of collecting and distributing the money to charity organizations. May the good Lord bless you and your family. if you are interested to proceed with this project go ahead and forward the below information so that I will instruct you on how to proceed: Your Full Names: Your Direct Telephone Number: Your Fax: Your Occupation: Your Nationality: Your Age: Please reply to this mail as I can only communicate through my laptop which is by my bed, as soon as I get the above listed information, I shall then give you the necessary information you need to collect this money. God bless you. Mr. Thompson J. Alber.

Mr.Paul Clarke Senior Audit Officer HSBC Bank Group UK. Dear Friend, I am Mr.Paul Clarke Senior Audit Officer of HSBC Bank Group UK. HSBC Bank London. I am writing following an opportunity in my office that will be of immense benefit to both of us. In my department we discovered an abandoned sum of£30.5million British Pounds Sterling (Thirty million five hundred thousand British Pounds) in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customers Late Mr. Morris Thompson an American who unfortunately lost his life in the plane crash of Alaska Airlines Flight 261 which crashed on January 31 2000, including his wife and only daughter. You shall read more about the crash on visiting this site. http://www.cnn.com/2000/US/02/01/alaska.airlines.list/ Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin or relatves to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines. Unfortunately I learnt that his supposed next of kin being his only daughter died along with him in the plane crash leaving nobody with the knowledge of this fund behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I and two other officials in this department now decided to make business with you and release the money to you as the next of kin or beneficiary of the funds for safety keeping and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we don't want this money to go back into Government treasury as unclaimed bill. The banking law and guidelines here stipulates that such money remained after six years the money will be transferred into banking treasury as unclaimed funds. We agreed that 35% of this money will be for you as foreign partner, while the balance will be for me and my colleagues. I will visit your country for the disbursement according to the percentages indicated above once this money gets into your account.Please be honest to me and trust is our watchword in this transaction. Note this transaction is confidential and risk free.As soon as you receive this mail you should contact me by return mail.Please note that all necessary arrangement for the smooth release of these funds to you has been finalised. We will discuss much in details when I do receive your response. Please if you are interested in this project contact me for further directives on paul_clark01@yahoo.co.uk or paul_clarke02@yahoo.co.uk Best regards Mr Paul Clarke

>From Mrs.Vikki Meade. 120,Paul Kruger Street, Boksburg South, Johannesburg Province. Republic of South Africa Hello, RE: TRANSFER OF $ 29,000.000.00 USD (TWENTY NINE MILLION UNITED STATE DOLLAR) ========================================= I am Mrs.Vikki Meade, the Auditor General of prime banks here South Africa, during the course of our auditing, I discovered a floating fund in an account opened in the bank in 1990 and since 1993 nobody has operated on this account again. After going through some old files in the records I discovered that the owner of the account died without a [heir] hence the money is floating and if I do not remit this money out urgently it will beforfeited for nothing. The owner of this account is Mr. Howard Sweeney, a foreigner, a miner and an industrialist.He made millions of dollars before he died misteriously .Since 1993 no other person knows about this account or any thing concerning it. My investigation proved to me that the account has no other beneficiary and that Mr.Howard Sweeney until his death was the manager Sweeney Coy.(pty). SA. We will start the first transfer with six million dollars [$6,000,000.00] upon successful transaction without any disappoint from your side, we shall re-apply for the payment of the remaining amount to your account. The amount involved is (USD 29M) Twenty Nine million United States Dollars only. I want to first transfer$6,000.000 [Six million United States Dollar] from this money into a safe foreigners account abroad before the rest, but I don't know any foreigner. I am revealing this to you with believein God that you will never let me down in this business. Also send your private telephone number and fax number including the full details of the account to be used for the deposit. I need your strong assurance that you will never let me down in this business proposition. With my influence and the position of a bank official whom is working in our favour we can transfer this money to any foreigner's reliable account which you can provide with assurance that this money will be intact pending our physical arrival in your country for sharing. The bank official will destroy all documents of transaction immediately we receive this money leaving no trace to any place and to build confidence you can come immediately to discuss with me face to face after which I will make this remittance in your presence and three of us will fly to your country at least two days ahead of the money going into the account. At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 35% of the total amount, 60% will be for me, while 5% will be for expenses both parties might have incurred during the process of transferring. I look forward to your earliest response. Best Regards, Mrs.Vikki Meade. _________________________________________________________________ See their smiles, hear their laughter with Windows Live Messenger! http://messenger.live.com

From: Maria Rose Muduo Av.12 RD 16,Apt.39B, Triechville Abidjan, Cote D'Ivoire. Email:missmariarose_m@yahoo.com Dear Friend, (PROJECT/2005/PWM/M.MUDUO-INVESTMENT) Permit me to inform you of my desire of going into business relationship with you .I am Maria Rose Muduo. The daugther of late Chief and Mrs. Alaine Muduo JP. My father was a very wealthy gold merchant who based in Abidjan the economic capital of Cote D'Ivoire His business associate on one of their business outings poisoned him to death. When my mother died on the 21ST October 1994, my father took my brother and me so special because we were motherless. Before the death of my father on the 29th November 2000 in a private hospital here in Abidjan, He sincerely called me on his bedside and told me that he had a sum of US$10,500,000 (TEN MILLION FIVE HOUNDRED THOUSAND U.S DOLLARS) kept in a security company here. He also said that the security company does not know the content of the Trunk Boxes. He also put my name in Depositing the 1 boxes as the beneficiary and next of kin. He also explained to me that it was because of this wealth that he was poisoned by his business associates, That I should seek for a foreign partner in a country of my choice where I will transfer this money and use it for investment purposes and further my education, I want you to assist me in clearing this fund into your account overseas as a beneficiary of the fund, and also use it for an investment purpose, such as real estate management. My interested areas of investment are; REAL ESTATE, HOTELS, PETROLUM INDUSTRY & MINING, TRANSPORT or in any good investment you may advise me on. I am honorably seeking for your assistance To serve as the guardian of this fund since I am a student with no business experience. Moreover, I am willing to offer you 20% of the total sum as compensation for your effort /input after the successful transfer of this fund to your nominated account. Furthermore, you can indicate your option towards assisting me, as I believe that this transaction would be concluded within 14 days, from the day you signify interest to assist me. Waiting to hear from you soonest. Have a nice day and remain blessed. Yours Truly, Maria Rose Muduo

Dear Friend, My Name is John Amane Clarke, managing director of Diamond Security & Storage Company here in Accra- Ghana. In my department, I discovered an abandoned consignment worth over sum of US$12Million dollars (Twelve Million US dollars) in file that belongs to our foreign customer, LATE MR. ANDREAS SCHRANNER from Munich, Germany who died along with his entire family in July 2000 in a plane crash. Below is a website which I will appreciate you going through to read the information. http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479.stm Since then, I have made several enquiries to locate any of his extended relatives but all effort has proved abortive. The reason why I am contacting you is based on trust to enable me present you as the next-of-kin to him so this consignment will be released to you for safety and subsequent disbursement. Nobody has come to our company for claiming of the consignment. It will be easy to convince the company since I am in possession of the necessary legalised documents that backs-up the consignment and which will present you as the rightful next-of-kin to the deceased customer. I don't want this consignment to go into company,s treasury as unclaimed bill. The company laws and guidelines stipulates that if such consignment remains unclaimed after seven years, the company will confiscate it. The request for a foreigner as next-of-kin in this transaction is occasioned by the fact that late ANDREAS was a foreigner and any indigene cannot stand as next-of-kin to a foreigner. All I require is your honest co-operation to enable us see this transaction through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. I agree that 25% of this money will be for you as a respect to the provision of your assistance , 5% will be set aside for expenses incurred during the transaction, another 5% to help the less privilege and to assist the charity organisations here in Africa and abroad while the rest 65% will be for me. Thereafter, I will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentage indicated. Therefore, to enable the immediate release of this consignment, you must apply to the company as the relation or next of kin of the deceased indicating your complete information, complete name, postal address, occupation, your private telephone and fax number for easy and effective communication and location where the consignment will be release to. Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or email the text of the Application you will send to the company to seek the release of the consignment to you. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch-free and that you should not entertain any fear as all required Arrangements have been made. You should contact me as soon as you receive this mail. My email address i: johnamaneclarke1@aim.com Or you can send your number for me to call you. Trusting to hear from you immediately for more detailed discussion. Regards, John Amane Clarke. Managing Director, Diamond Security & Storage Company Accra, Ghana.

FROM: Dr.Abdul Latif Chairman Contract Review Panel, Abidjan, Cote D'Ivoire. West Africa. DEAR FRIEND. First, I must solicit your strictest confidence in this transaction. This by virtue of its nature as being utterly confidential and TOP SECRET. I got your contact in our search for a foreign partner who has the Ability and reliability to prosecute a transaction of great magnitude Involving a pending business transaction requiring maximum confidence. We are top officials of the Federal Government contract review panel who are interested in investment in your country with funds which are presently trapped here in Cote D Ivoire.In other to commence this Business, we solicit your assistance to enable us transfer into your Account the said trapped funds. The source of this fund is as follows: During the last regime here of General Robert Guei in Cote D Ivoire some government official's set up companies and awarded themselves contracts which were grossly over Invoiced in various ministries. The government set up a contract review panel and we have Identified a lot of inflated contracts funds which are presently Deposited in a BANK here in Abidjan,Cote D Ivoire . However, by virtue of our position as civil servants and members of the panel ,we cannot acquire this money in our name. we have therefore ,been delegated as a matter of trust by my colleagues to look for an overseas partner into whose account we would transfer the total sum of USD$15,500,000.00 (FIFTEEN MILLION,FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS) Hence we are writing you this letter. We agreed to share the money thus: (1) 20% FOR THE ACCOUNT OWNER (YOU) (2) 10% FOR MICSELLENIOUS EXPENSES (3)70% FOR US (THE OFFICALS) It is from the 70% that we wish to commence investments in your country as you will also stand as our foreign agent over there. Please note that this transaction is 100% safe and we hope to commence the transaction latest seven (7) days from the date of the receipt of the following information bellow. (A) COMPANYS NAME BENEFICIARY OF ACCOUNT. (B)YOUR PERSONAL TELEPHONE NUMBER AND FAX NUMBERS. (C) BANK ACCOUNT/SORT/ABA/ROUTING NUMBERS WHICH THE FUND WILL BE TRANSFERED TO. (D) YOUR BANK ADDRESS, TELEPHONE NUMBERS/FAX NUMBERS. The above information will enable us commence the transfer of this funds into your account in your country without delay We are looking forward to doing this business with you and solicit your confidentiality in this transaction. Please acknowledge the receipt of this letter using the above email address; I will bring you into the complete picture of this pending project when I hear from you. With Kind regards, Dr.Abdul Latif _________________________________________________________________ Express yourself instantly with MSN Messenger! Download today it's FREE! http://messenger.msn.click-url.com/go/onm00200471ave/direct/01/

From: Mr. Dezaryi #67 Cresent Close, Lynnwood Road Hatfield Pretoria Gauteng, South Africa. {INTERNATIONAL HERITAGE TRANSACTION} {One Hundred & Seventy Two Million Six Hundred And Fifty Four Thousand United State Dollars} {(RE: TRANSFER OF ($172,654,000.00 USD} {BUSINESS OPPORTUNITY/YOUR ASSISTANCE IS NEEDED} Dear Sir/Madam!! I sincerely ask for forgiveness for I know this may seem like a complete intrusion to your privacy but right about now this is my option of communication. This mail might come to you as a surprise and the temptation to ignore it as unserious could come into your mind; but please consider it a divine wish and accept it with a deep sense of humility. I am aware that this is certainly an unconventional approach to starting a relationship. I am Mr. Dezaryi, the personal account officer to the great late diseased who has an account in one of the top banks here in South Africa. The account was opened in 2001 and he died in 2004 without a written or oral WILL and since 2004 nobody has operated on this account again hence the money is floating and if I do not remit this money out urgently it will be forfeited for nothing and Govt. of South Africa will confiscate the funds for their personal use which I personally don't want such incident to happen being that this is a great opportunity for me. My contact is for you to please assist me to transfer the fund ($172,654,000.00 USD) One Hundred & Seventy Two Million Six Hundred And Fifty Four Thousand United State Dollars from a Cooperate Bank here in South Africa to an oversea account. First, I must solicit your strictest confidence in this transaction. This is by virtue of its nature as being utterly confidential. I am sure and have confidence of your ability and reliability to prosecute a transaction of this great magnitude. I solicit your assistance to enable us transfer the said amount into your safe account for onward investment. You can either provide us with an existing account or to set up a new Bank account immediately to receive this money, even an empty a/c can serve to receive this money, as long as you will remain honest to me till the end of this important business trusting in you and believing that you will never let me down either now or in future because this business is my life. The owner of this account is a foreigner and no other person knows about this account or anything concerning it, the account has no other beneficiary and until his death he was the manager of the company. My investigation through the National immigration department & Ministries here proved to me as well that he was single as at the time of his entry into the Republic of South Africa. The amount in this account is USD ($172,654,000.00 USD) Two Hundred & Twenty fifty million United States Dollars} only. As a matter of fact, I have decided to transfer this fund abroad for investment. Your assistance as a foreigner is necessary because the management of the bank will welcome any foreigner who has correct information to this account which I will give to you immediately, if you are interested to do this business with me. There is no risk in this business. With my position and my personal contact with the manager of the bank, the money can be transferred to any account you can provide with assurance that this money will be intact pending our physical arrival in your country for sharing. We will start the first transfer with Fifty million [$50,000.000]. Upon successful transfer without any disappointment from your side, we shall re-apply for the payment of the remaining balance of $122,654,000.00 Million to your account. I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money cannot be approved to a local person here, but can only be approved to any foreigner who has the correct information of the account, which I will provide for you. So you should provide me with your correct account details where you will like the fund to be transferred to, or you can set up a new account for the transfer even an empty account is ok. At the conclusion of the transfer you will take 45%, 6% will be for any expenses both parties incurred in the process of this business and the remaining 49% will be for me. As soon as I hear from you and upon your strong assurance that you will not let me down once the fund goes into your account I will then start the processing of the transfer of the fund to your account without further delay. If you are interested, please forward the following information as below: {1} Your Name/company's name and full address, {2} Bank Name:............ {3} Bank Address... {4} Account No:......... {5} Swift Code...{if any} {6} Account Holder's Name: .......... {7} Your telephone Nos.both Home, Office & Cell/Mobile and fax Numbers... {8} Your Occupation {9} Your Valid ID Upon the receipt of the above details, payment will be activated by the feeding of your data into payment system, followed by a signal that will be sent to the paying bank to remit funds into your nominated bank account within 5 official working days of receipt of the above information. Contact me urgently via email privately for further details:[dezaryi@yahoo.com] Thanks. Best Regards, Mr. Dezaryi,

SUPPLY FROM MR KONAN ALAIN Abidjan.Cote d'Ivoire. Attn:The President Dear Sir, I write to solicite your assistance and support to enable me execute a very lucrative and high profiting business transaction.I am very sure that with trust and understanding,we will be able to execute this busines to our mutual benefit and believe that you will not let down the trust I am willing to repose in you. I work for an Ivorien based import and export firm ("a-MIC"), I work product sourcing manager. Between the 17th -19th of may, 2002 a business seminar was held in BOUAKE Cote Divoire of which I attended.While in the Seminar, I was opportuned to meet ALHAJI NURUDEEN ALI MAHMOUD ,the President of ALI-MAHMOUD DAIRY & CATTLE FARMS ETS. ALHAJI NURUDEEN ALI MAHMOUD isan accomplished and widely known and recognised millionaire farmer in this part of the region. He has cattle farms in different countries. Above all, he is one of the greatest supplier of cattle,beef and other diary products in this part of the coast.On getting to know my proffesion, ALHAJI NURUDEEN ALI MAHMOUD took me into confidence by informing me about the purchase of a particular but very important medicine for his cattle. He informed me that he buys this product at $5,000.00 USD per carton, and that he mostly buys to the excess of 450 cartons. He informed me that he would like me to find out if my organisation could source for him a cheaper supplier considering the recent trend of falls in the general price of beef in the world market which is affecting his business. Back in my office, I discussed this proposal with my boss and he decided to handle the supply by himself.We carried out a market research and discovered that we could purchase this medicine somewhere cheaper in EUROPE for $2,000.00 USD per carton . We moved a proposal to ALI-MAHMOUD DAIRY & CATTLE FARMS ETS. to make the supply to them at $4,800.00 USD per carton of which he accepted. Owing to my role in the transaction, I had an agreement with my director to be receiving 15% of whatever gain is made on each supply of which he agreed. But on the completion of the suply and the receipt of the payment, my boss renegated on our agreement and refused to give me my share of the profit. Since then our relationship has been at its lowest ebb. I have since accepted it as one of life experiences. However, as God would have it, recently, I ran into ALHAJI NURUDEEN ALI MAHMOUD and he informed me that he would want us to urgently supply him with 1250 cartons of the same product before the end of Dec 2006.I used the oppurtunity to inform Alhaji that I can introduce him to the main producer of this vaccine who can supply him the product at $4,400.00 USD if he will pay in advance as he usually does. He was very pleased and has assured me that he is not going to contact my boss again for this vaccine. He is now waiting for me to link him to the producer of the vaccine. We will buy the medicine at $2,000.00 USD from EUROPE and sell at $4,400.00 USD TO ALHAJI NURUDEEN ALI MAHMOUD,with him making a down payment of 50% of our quoted price first. If you are interested and capable of handling this supplies on my behalf,kindly get back to me urgently through my e-mail,so that we can agree on the terms and profit sharing,after which I can then furnish you with the contacts of both our source in EUROPE and that of ALHAJI NURUDEEN ALI MAHMOUD . Kindly be notified that at no point in time should you let ALHAJI NURUDEEN ALI MAHMOUD know that you are not the producer of the medicine and we should never allow him to know the contact of our real source in EUROPE so that he would'nt bypass us to deal directly with them. Thanks for your cooperation. Yours sincerely, MR KONAN ALAIN _________________________________________________________________ Express yourself instantly with MSN Messenger! Download today it's FREE! http://messenger.msn.click-url.com/go/onm00200471ave/direct/01/

From: Dr .A. Smith NatWest Bank PLC., 24 Frith Street, London W1D5LG, INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER. LEICESTER CURRENCY CHEQUE/DRAFT DEPARTMENT Telegram: FBNFOREX, Reply to :allensmith_112@yahoo.ca Dear:Sir, I am Hon. Dr.A Smith Director allocation department from the (NatWest Bank PLC,)London Branch.my office monitors and controls the affairs of all banks and financial institutions in London concerned with foreign claim payments. I am the final signatory to any transfer or remittance of huge funds moving within banks both on the local and international levels in line with foreign claim settlement. I have before me list of funds, which could not be transferred to some nominated accounts as these accounts have been identified either as, unclaimed deposits and over-invoiced sum etc. Your Name was among the people expecting the funds to be transferred into their account, on this note; I wish to have a deal with you as regards to your unpaid funds.I have your file before me and hope your data's are correct and un-tampered unless you reconfirm it not correct. As it is my duty to recommend the transfer of these surplus funds to the Federal Government Treasury and Reserve Accounts as unclaimed deposits, I have the opportunity to write you based on the instructions I received two days ago from the Foreign Debts reconciliation dept to submit the List of payment reports/ expenditures and audited reports of revenues. Among several others, I have decided to remit your claim sum following my idea that we can have a deal/agreement and I am going to do this legally.My conditions: 1. The sum of USD$16.7M only will be transfer into your account after the proccessing of all relevant legal documents with your name as the bonfide beneficary,the transfer will be made by Draft or telegraphic Transfer (T/T), confirmable in 21 working days. 2. This deal must be kept secret forever, and all correspondence will be strictly by email / telephone, for security purposes. 3. There should be no third parties as most problem associated with your fund release are caused by your agents or representative. If you AGREE with my conditions, l advise you on what to do immediately and the transfer will commence without delay as I will proceed to fix your name on the Payment schedule instantly to meet the days mandate. I hope you don't reject this offer and have your funds transferred. Waiting for your reply soon. Yours Faithfully Dr.A. Smith.

Attention: President/Director, I am the chairman of the contract award committee of the Gold and Natural resources ministry here in Dakar Senegal, for security reasons, I may not wish to disclose the most important thing for now until I hear from you. After due deliberation with my partner, I decided to forward to you this business proposal, we want you to assist us receive the sum of Twenty eight million, six hundred thousand united state bills ($28.6M) into your account. This fund resulted from an over-invoiced contract awarded by us under the budget allocation to my ministry and the bill was approved for payment by the concerned ministries. The contract was executed, commissioned and the contractor was paid his actual cost of the contract. Now, we are left with the balance of $28.6M as the over invoiced amount, which we have deliberately over estimated for our own use. Please note that the law forbids civil servants to operate or own foreign accounts hence this contact, we have agreed to share the money in the following percentages: 30 for you, 60 for us 10 for tax as may be required by your government, because we don?t need anything will delay this money when it arrive in your bank account. Note that this transaction is very much free from all sorts of risk hence the business was carefully planned before it was successfully executed and we the officials involved in the deal have put many years in service to our ministry. We have been exercising patience for this privilege for so long not until the presidential announcement last week, that all foreign contractors owed be paid forthwith, this will enable the presidency reconcile our debt ratio with the outside world and to most of us, this is a lifetime blessing we cannot afford to miss. Upon indication of your interest to fully co-operate with us, a payment application/information form will be sent to you via email for completion. Note that the following information: your private phone number and email address willenable us seek/secure approval of the fund from the concerned government quarters/ministries within 3-4 banking days. As soon as we confirm receipt of this money in your nominated bank account, my partner and I will come over to your country to arrange for our own share and possibly invest part of this money in your country. Let honesty and trust be our watchword throughout this transaction. I shall furnish you with some details about myself. Your prompt reply will be highly appreciated. Best regards, Mr.Wilson Ogodi

dear friend, I am the manager of bill and exchange at the foriegn remittance department of AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK. I am writing, following the impressive information about you through one of my friends WORKS WITH THE BURKINA CHAMBERS firm. In my department we discovered an abandoned sum of $U.S15.5Million dollars (fifteen million five hundred thousand US dolloars) in an account that belongs to one of our foriegn customer who died along with his entire family in November 2004 in a plane crash. Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless some body applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidlines and laws but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I and other officials in my department now decided to make this business proposal to you and release the money to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we don't want this money to go into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. The banking law and guidling here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed after six years the money will be transfered into the bank treasury as unclaimed fund. The request of foreigner as next of kin in this business is occassioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a Burkinabe cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. We agree that 30% of this money will be for you as a foreign partner, in respect to the provision of a foriegn account, 10% will be set aside for expenses occured during the business and 60% would be for me and my colleagues. There after I and my colleagues will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentage indicated. Therefore, to enable the immediate transfer of this fund to you as arranged, you must apply first to the bank as relation or next of kin of the deceased indicating your bank name, your bank account number, your private telephone and fax number for easy and effective communication and location wherein the money will be remitted. Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or email the text of the application. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch -free and that you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made for the transfer. You should contact me immediately as soon as you recieve this letter. Yours faithful Bill & Exchange Manager. YOBO _________________________________________________________________ Les révélations de la starac 6 commentées par Jérémy! http://starac2006.spaces.live.com/

Dear Friend, My Compliment to you, I guess this letter may come to you as a surprise since I had no previous correspondence with you. I am sending you this mail on behalf of the tender board of the Niger Delta Development Commission (NDDC), which is in charge of managing and supervising the disbursement of oil sales revenues for the Nigerian government which covers payment to foreign and local contractors that have executed contracts for our country. The revenue under our control runs into several hundred of millions of dollars monthly. We came across your contact in our search for a reliable person to handle a very confidential transaction involving the transfer of Nine Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars (US$9.500m). This fund was accrued from various over invoicing of foreign contractors' payments made over the years. The contract has long been executed and payment of the actual contract amount has been paid to the foreign contractor. The balance of the actual contract is what my colleagues and I now interested in transferring out of Nigeria into a reliable foreign account for our personal use. As civil servants we are not allowed to run foreign accounts. Hence we have chosen you to front and support us as the beneficiary to be paid. If you are interested in this proposal, kindly get back to me by sending me your letter of acceptance along with your direct telephone and fax numbers. For your support and partnership, please reply me to negotiate your fees or the percentage you wish to be paid when the funds are transferred into your bank account. Further details about this transaction will be discussed in the subsequent correspondence. Note also that the particular nature of your business is irrelevant to this transaction and all local contacts and arrangements are in place for a smooth and successful conclusion of this transaction. We will appreciate that you treat this proposal with utmost attention, knowing fully well that you cannot and will not be compelled to assist us if you are not disposed to. I will be in UK on official assignment probably in a week’s time. I can be contacted via this email account drahmedsuleman@gmail.com I will appreciate that you forward to me your contact telephone and fax numbers on responding to this mail; I will endeavour to call you for detailed discussion on the proposal. Thank you as I await your response. Sincerely, Dr. Ahmed.

>From Mark Nguessane. Dear , I am Mark Nguessane from Seirra-Leone I am the son of Chief Nguessane Bakari who was the managing director and owner of NGEBAK Import/Export company,NGEBAK Logistics company and NGEBAK Glass company here in Abidjan Cote d'Ivoire West Africa. Dear I humbly wish to write you this letter in order that you will assist me and my only Sister Cecilia in this money transfer to your bank account in your country for investment in a profitable business. On the 11th october 2004 our late father attended the general meeting of all the import/export companies in the country and unfortunately he was poisoned by his business rivals and he later died in the hospital. But before his death,after staying in bed for three days in the hospital,he told me that he deposited the sum of US$12,000,000.(Twelve Million US dollars) in a bank here in abidjan on behalf of his foreign business partner in abroad and he advised me to look for a co-beneficiary from abroad to transfer these money to his account for investment in his country. Presently,the members of his extended family has claimed all his companies leaving nothing behind for us,his extended family members also sent us away from his house where we are living and they seized all our house hold properties. We are presently now staying in a hotel here in Abidjan Cote d'Ivoire because of our lives and the security of the valid documents which the bank gave to our late father on the day he made the deposit lest the members of our late fathers extended family will kill us and Claim these money in the bank. Based on our ignorance in the international business world of this sort,we hereby solicit for your urgent assistance as the co-beneficiary of these money, for the bank to transfer these money to your safe and secured bank account in your country. for further proceedings as we wait for your soonest response. Please,we don't want neither third party nor publicity of any kind in this business transaction as we have agreed to offer you 25% of the total sum and 75% will be for us respectively as you will also assist us to join you in your country as soon as this money is transfered to your account in your country for the investment. Thanks in advance as we wait for your soonest response, Yours Sincerely, Mark and Cecillia Nguessane. _________________________________________________________________ Don't just search. Find. Check out the new MSN Search! http://search.msn.click-url.com/go/onm00200636ave/direct/01/

Hello Dear. You will be surprised to read from me, but please consider this letter as a genuine request from a family in dire need of your humble assistance.I am Benson Dime. A Citizen of Zimbabwe,I am now seeking political assylum. I got your contact through the Information Exchange Online. I am the only Son of Sonya Michael, a wealthy black farmer and senior politician with the opposition political party in my country, Movement for Democratic Change (MDC). Our wicked President Robert Mugabe murdered my father, before I ran way from my country because I have become his next target to eliminate. My father was a fighter for Justice and a moving force in The MDC, a party wanting to end the several years of brutal Dictatorship government of President Robert Mugabe. You will read more stories about President Mugabe's brutal acts by visiting this web site:<http://www.rte.ie/news/2000/0418/zimbabwe.html> My father was accused of assisting the White farmers in fighting the government. Few weeks after his arrest, he was reported dead. The government claimed he died of heart attack and his body was never seen for proper autopsy, they buried him in the government cemetery. My father's associate Mr.Mc Graw Olds a White farmer from Britain assisted me in fighting my father's death through the Court and media. The Government saw us as a big threat to them and decided to eliminate us. Mr. Olds was attacked and murdered in his House, but fortunately, before they came looking for me, I received the news and I left the country through the border to save my life. Here is my reason for contacting you. Before the death of my father, he deposited (US$ 7,000,000.00) with a finance firm,The money was deposited as a gem/precious stone in a metal trunk box to avoid seizure and much demurrage from the security company organization. This money was earmarked for the purchase of new machinery and chemicals for the farms and the establishment of new farms in Lesotho and Swaziland. The government seized my father’s farms and bank account before his arrest and Murder. He told me everything concerning the funds while he was still in detention. This is why I need your assistance in securing the funds there in your Country, so that I can arrange on how to come over to your country for the investment of the fund, I am willing to offer you 25% of the total fund for your assistance.as you may know that the financial law and regulations of the government does not give we assylum seekers financial rights to such huge sum of money. In view of this, The monetary policy/law does not allow such investment by an asylum seeker or refugee. Please, let me know if you can assist me, so that I can give you more details on how we shall proceed. As I wait for your urgent Response, please treat this information as top secret.Pls u can also contact me through this alternative mail (mr_sajoy01@voila.fr) Yours truly, Mr.Ajoy Sonya.

Financial Adviser. 121 Old ojo road, Pmb 224 Ikoyi, Lagos-Nigeria. Dear friend, THIS IS THE TRUE STORY OF THIS MATTER Please my name is Jones Usman a financial adviser to David a national of your country.He was an oil merchant here in Nigeria. On the 21st 1997, my client, his wife and their three children were involved in a car accident along Ibadan Express road lagos. All occupants of the vehicle unfortunately lost their lives along with the driver. Since then I have made several enquiries in his Embassy to locate any of my client's extended relatives.After these several unsuccessful attempts,as a matter of fact,I decided to trace his relatives over the internet in order to locate any member of his family for a huge sum of fund deposited on his name in an offshore financial company overseas but that was to no avail, hence I decided within myself to contact you as his supposed relative since you are also a foreigner to avoid the offshore company from confiscating the deposit for theirs . Please, I want you to assist me in repatriating the money left behind by my client before they get confiscated or declared unserviceable by the UBN Finance company offshore payment centre where these huge deposits were lodged. He had an deposit valued at about US$12M(Twelve Million US Dollars)and now the finance company has issued me an urgent notice to provide the next-of-kin or have the account freezed within the next ten official working days. This was the last fund moved by my late claim to the offshore payment company of UBN for sefety by the oil merchant shortly before the autocrash that took his life and all in the car.This was as a result of the conflict emulated from the annulled june 12 presidential election by the military dictatorship Gen.Ibrahim Babangida which resulted to the death of many people in Nigeria even chief Moshood K.O Abiola that won the presidential race. GO THROUGH; topics.nytimes.com/top/reference/timestopics/people/a/moshood_k_o_abiola/index .html?s=oldest& - 42k ) Since, I have succeeded in locating you today as his relative,I hereby seek your consent to present you as well as use your name and particulars apply as the next of kin to the deceased,so that the proceeds of this account deposit valued at US$12M can be paid to you and then you and I can share the money at last or invest with it for a profitable venture in your country, 50% to me and 50% to you.To present you as the next of kin will pose no difficulty as there is no risk involved hence i am the one presenting you officially. I have all the necessary legal documents that can be used to back up our claim. 1. The Death Certificate 2. Letter of Administration 3. Sworn Affidavit All I require is your honest co-operation to enable us see this transaction through. I guarantee that this business proposal to you is 100% real and will be executed under a legitimate arrangement without any problem at all. Please get in touch with me via my secured and confidential email address while you forward to me the following informations immediately you receive this message so that I will give you further details if you are interested and ready to work with me . 1.. YOUR NAME AND ADDRESS TO MAKE THE CLAIM... 2...YOUR PHONE NUMBER FOR URGENT CONTACT BY ME.. 3...YOUR OCCUPATION AND YOUR AGE.. Remember to include your own private or mobile cell phone with which I can equally reach you. Anticipating your prompt response. Yours Sincerely, Financial Adviser.. Jones Usman.. (jones_usman1977@rixmail.se)

My Dear, When I picked up your contact, I have this interest in going through your profile though not enough in giving me your detailed information to access your capability of a cordial relationship. But after going through your profile with due deliberation, I deem it wise to contact you directly and seek your assistance in a business dealing that will be of mutual benefit to both of us. Though not minding the consequence but hoping that you would understand the complication on my side and the need for your kind assistance. Please excuse the manner of approach. But I think it is more convenient and discreet to contact you through this means. I am interested in a partnership investment programme with yourself/corporation. There is this huge amount of ($9,245,000.00) which my late father kept in a security/financial firm before he was assassinated by government mercenary on 22 February, 2002, during a political crisis in my country- Angola. This fund was stashed in a security vault in Senegal, out of foresight for a likely situation which I and my family found our selves then. My father - Late Mr. Karim Fab deposited it as a family treasure and that was before his death. Now I and sister have left Angola to Dakar in the Republic of Senegal, through the help of my late father's loyal friend. Meanwhile, we are staying here with refugee status, instead of going to exile and we have decided also to invest this money in your country or anywhere safe enough outside my country Angola and the whole of Africa for security and political reasons. We would want you to assist us to retrieve and transfer this fund to your country for safety and investment purposes. If you are willing to render this service to us, we shall adequately compensate you with 25% of the total figure. We will arrange all the necessary procedures in ensuring a smooth process for the transaction. We will also appreciate if you contact me once you receive this mail to enable megive you more details and modus operandi concerning the business. This matter requires your urgent attention, confidentiality and discretion no matter what your decision maybe. Thank you and God bless you. Yours Sincerely, Mr. Bill Karim & Sister . billkarm222@yahoo.fr

Dear friend, Let me apologize to you for using this medium to communicate to you about this project. I am a highly placed official of the Government of Nigeria and also a founding member of the PEOPLES DEMOCRATAIC PARTY (PDP),which is the ruling party in Power now, in this Country. My committee - The Niger Delta Development Commission(NDDC)-which is in charge of managing and supervising the development of the Oil rich states in this Country. We are given Monthly allocation that runs into several millions of DOLLARS/POUNDS from oil sales of this Country to cover payments of foreign and local contractors who has/is executing contracts for this oil region called the NIGER DELTA. My self and other colleagues in this commission, NDDC are currently in need of a foreign partner with whose bank account we shall transfer the sum of Forty Nine Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars($49.5m).This fund was accrued from various over invoicing of contracts awarded to foreign contractors over the existing years of this commission. However, by virtue of our position as civil servants and members of the NDDC, we cannot acquire this funds in our name. This is because as top civil servants, we are not allowed by law of the land to own or operate bank accounts outside our country for now therefore, I have been delegated as a matter of trust by my colleagues,to look for an oversea trusted partner in whose account we would transfer the fund Hence the reason for this mail. NOTE PLEASE: We shall be transferring the fund to your account with your company as the beneficiary and you are been paid for a contract,which you executed for our country through the NDDC. For your support and partnership,please reply me to negotiate your fees or the percentage you wish to be paid when the funds arrive your bank account. You must however note that this transaction, with regards to our disposition to continue with you, is subject to these terms below. FIRST, our conviction of your transparency. SECONDLY,that you treat this transaction with utmost secrecy and confidentiality. Finally and above all, that you will provide an account that you have absolute control. This transaction, although discrete, is legitimate and there is no risk or legal disadvantages either to ourselves or yourself now or in the future as we have put in place perfect machineries that will ensure a hitch free transfer of fund into your account upon acceptance. The transfer will be effected to your account within ten-fourteen (10-14) working days as soon as we reach an agreement and you furnish me with a suitable bank account,company name,address and with all your contact phone numbers including fax number. I am looking forward to doing business with you and do solicit your confidentiality in this transaction, Please mail your response to me through this email eric_stephenxxx@yahoo.com Yours faithfully, MR.ERIC STEPHEN

FROM: Mr George Adams Audit and Accounting Officer ECOBANK BENIN , Rue du Gouverneur Bayol, 01 BP 1280-Cotonou my Private email address is;godbless22@sify.com Calvary Greetings, I am Mr. George Adams Audit Manager ECOBANK of AFRICA BENIN . In the capital city of Cotonou Benin republic, and assistance, this is a very confidential proposition for you. On April 21st 1999, A Swedish Oil consultant/contractor with the Benenoise Solid Minerals Corporation, Mr.Soren Anderson made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$15,000,000.00 (fifteen Million Dollars only) in my branch. Upon maturity on November 20th 2003 as his Credit Officer, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally I discovered from his contract employers, the Benenoise Solid Minerals Corporation that Mr.Soren Anderson died on auto accident with his entire family. Further investigations and all attempts to trace his next of kin were fruitless. Again, I made further investigation and discovered that Mr.Soren Anderson did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$15,000,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to the International Banking ethics, codes and Laws, at the expiration of 7(Two) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Benin Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr.Soren. This is simple, I will like you to respond immediately with your full names and address so that we will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits that will put you in place as the next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 70% for me and some of my colleagues who are aware of this transaction and 25% for you and 5% for Expenses Incurred in the course of the transaction There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by my colleagues and with my position as the Foreign Remittance Director guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please send me your confidential telephone and fax numbers for easy communication. You should observe utmost confidentiality, and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Reply me in my Private email; Awaiting your urgent reply. Remain Bless. Mr.George Adams

Good day, I am contacting you because of a business concerning a huge sum of money which was deposited by a client in the Security and Finance company where I work here in Nigeria.Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make any one apprehensive and worried, but I am assuring you that all will be well at the end of the day. I actually decided to contact you due to the urgency of this transaction. PROPOSITION; I discovered an abandoned deposit in my company owned by one of our foreign customers who died along with his entire family as a result of an automobile crash. He actually deposited this funds amounting to US$40,000,000.00 (fourty million united states dollars), for safe keeping in my company here in Nigeria. Company file records shows that the funds was actually for a project. Our late costurmer wanted to start a multi million Dollar steel plant in Florida, USA in the near futur,before his sudden and untimely death. As such since his death none ofhis relations or next-of-kin has come forward to lay claims for this property as the heir, this basically the reason why I have contacted you. My company cannot release the property unless someone applies for claim as the next-of-kin to the deceased as indicated in our operating guidelines. Upon this discovery, I now seek your permission to have you stand as a next of kin to the deceased as all documentations will be carefully worked out by me for the funds to be released in your favour as the beneficiary's next of kin. It may interest you to know that I have secured from the probate an order to locate any of deceased beneficiaries. Please acknowledge receipt of this message in acceptance of our mutual business endeavour by furnishing me with the following; 1. Beneficiary full name and address 2. Direct Telephone and fax numbers 3. Occupation and position 4. Nationality and Date of birth 5. Marital status 6. Gender/sex These requirements will enable me file letter of claim to the appropriate departments for necessary approvals in your favour before you can personally appear for the claim. I shall be compensating you with 30% of the total money while 10% will be for any expenses incurred and the rest will be mine on final conclusion of this project. Please note that your share stays while the rest shall be for me for investment purposes. If this proposal is acceptable by you, do not take undue advantage of the trust I have bestowed in you, I await your urgent reply through my private email;; U BELLO _________________________________________________________________ Express yourself instantly with MSN Messenger! Download today it's FREE! http://messenger.msn.click-url.com/go/onm00200471ave/direct/01/

Dear Sir/CEO, I am Mr.D S Ammer, the purchasing director African Millennium Villages Project. Our head office is situated in Lome, Federal Republic Togo. This agency has been existing since over 3 years. Our duty is to fight against rural poverty in Africa. This scheme has over US$500,000,000,00 involves targeted investment in health, education and farming to help lift African villages out of poverty. Presently we have currently covers around 107 villages in 13 countries, including, Ethiopia, Ghana, Mali, Rwanda, Uganda and Kenya. Under the scheme, villages are supplied with various materials, e.g. mosquito nets to prevent the spread of malaria, fertilizers, clothing of various kinds and treatment for people living with HIV/Aids. This scheme makes up part of the UN'S Millennium Development Goals, which are internationally agreed targets to cut poverty, hunger, disease and boots literacy by 2015 in Africa. I am contacting you for a business; I would like you to register with our agency as one of our foreign suppliers that supplys relief materials to our organization. I have about US$8MILLION to transfer into any secured bank account abroad. The money is an over-invoiced contract amount executed by a foreign supplier and commissioned with African Millennium Villages project (AMVP), and the original supplier has been paid since march last year remaining the over-invoiced amount of $8million. This was intentional and since then the US$8million has been in the suspense account of our organization awaiting for claim. Now i am ready to transfer the fund(US$8million) overseas for our personal business investment and that is where i need your assistance by providing me with a trusted bank account to remit the fund. Then both of us will share the fund. Now, how to start is just for me to pass through my attorney and register your name/company as a sub-contract with African Millennium Villages project, and the date of the registration will be back-dated to the date the contract was awarded to the original supplier. Then you will serve among the foreign suppliers that supplied relief material to our organization awaiting for payment. All arrangements have been put in place to ensure a successful project. Please if you are capable of working this project with me get back to me quickly via this email:deansammer033@yahoo.com. We will discuss on the sharing modality of the fund if i receive your positive response. I will send you more details on how we are going to proceed on the claim. Note this project is risk free and genue.With your corporation it will only take just few weeks to accomplish our project. Kind regards Mr.D S Ammer

Barr. ALEX GIVENS (Esq.) Hello, It is with a Heavy Heart that I am reaching you regarding the death of my late client. I am ALEX GIVENS, the legal adviser to late MR. MIKE & CAROL HALL, a Very Wealthy Couple that lived here in the United Kingdom, before their recent Death on the 26th of December during Tsunami disaster in the year (2004). Below is the webpage of the deceased. http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/england/bristol/4153821.stm This couple Deposited a sum of US$15,500,000.00 with the management of the HSBC BANK PLC here in london prior to their unfortunate and untimely death. As their known attorney, the management of the HSBC BANK PLC has written to my firm requesting me to present to them a relative of the deceased to enable them ( The Bank) release the funds of the late Mr. Mike Hall to whomever their relative will be in accordance to British and international law. Since I have been unsuccessful in locating the relatives,I wish to seek your consent to present you as the next of kin of the deceased before the bank. I will furnish you with the whole procedures to ensure that this is successfully concluded, for your assistance in this transaction, I have decided to give you Fourty percent (40%) of the total sum at the successful end of this transaction, that is when the funds have been successfully remitted into any of your given bank account. All I require is your honest co-operation to enable this deal go through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you and I from any breach of the law. I will also furnish you with certain priviledged information and details of the account my late client operated with the HSBC BANK PLc like the account number and the secret pin code for you to make verifications by yourself at the bank. I will also be on hand to furnish the bank with any legaldocument that may be needed to facilitate the swift release of the funds to you as the next of kin to my deceased clients. I will also need your most confidential telephone number and fax numbers, if you have a mobile phone,I believe it will help so that I can reach you anytime. You can write to my Email account:alex.given@yahoo.com however I will furnish you with my most confidential email address as we proceed in this transaction. I will also furnish you with a confidential telephone number to be used in reaching me as soon as I receive a positive response from you. Yours trully Barr. ALEX GIVENS (Esq.) alex.given@yahoo.com

Caspar J. Justin Solicitors 86 Market Place, Mansfield NG10 7HR,United Kingdom Tel: +44-701-114-9174 Fax: +44-871-264-3736 Email: caspar_j_justin@LawDr.net Dear, Re: Next of Kin I am Caspar J. Justin an Attorney at Law, a South African national practicing here in the UK. I am writing to notify you of the TESTAMENT of one or our Client who unfortunately lost his life in the Madrid bomb blast on March 11, 2004, killing over two hundred people including tourists in Spain. He was a prominent business leader who had been in Spain for vacation with his wife and their only daughter. The deceased who was residing in the United States of America before his death made a deposit of Fifteen Million Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars (US$15,500,000.00) in Amsterdam Netherlands, his effort to avoid the obligatory payment of income tax in the United States of America. However, I was mandated by our team of professionals to search for the relatives of the deceased regarding his deposit as the holding financial institution wants him to come forward for the endorsement of the reinvestments documents on interest accrued. Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his Next of Kin or relatives to come over to sign the reinvestment documents or claim his deposit because the financial institution cannot release these funds unless a formal application is made which is in line with the Royal Dutch law on inheritance claim. Regrettably, I learnt that his supposed Next of Kin, which could be his spouse or his only daughter died along with him in the ugly Madrid Bomb Blast leaving nobody with the knowledge of this huge deposit except me as the personal lawyer attached to monitor his deposit. It is in this regard that I and my colleagues decided to solicit your assistance by presenting you as the next of kin to the deceased. Although, we have agreed on the following sharing ratios: 25% for your assistance and 75% for me and my colleagues but it is still negotiable. NB: This transaction is very confidential and 100% risk free as I have a copy of his LAST WILL AND TESTAMENT which I can present your name as the TRUSTEE & EXECUTOR. This transaction shall be executed under legitimate and legal procedures that will protect you from any breach of the Law. Therefore, do not hesitate to revert back to me, either via fax or email, with the following details if my proposal interests you: A signed copy of this letter, your address and your telephone and fax numbers. Best regards, Caspar J. Justin Attorney At Law (Principal)

ATTN: Sir/Madam, INVITATION FOR PARTNERSHIP/INVESTMENT With due respect, trust and humility, I write to you this proposal, which I believe would be of great interest to you. I am looking for a reliable and capable foreign partner that will assist my family and I to transfer fund to his/her personal or private account oversea and for investment purpose's. Am Mr. AUTHOR GEZI the son of Late Dr.JOMO GEZI, who was the "Chairman" of the farmer's co-operation in Zimbabwe. My Father was among the few blacks that were murdered in cold blood by the President Robert Mugabe Administration during the land dispute that just happened in Zimbabwe. After the death of my Father, we decided to move out of ZIMBABWE because our lives were in danger because of the money that my father kept in his hidden safe in our house. The amount contained in the safe is US$15.5 Million Dollars (FIFTEEN MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS). This money was meant for the purchase of new machines and chemicals for the farms and establishment of new farms in Swazpartner pending when we see somebody that will assist us, for the safety of ours. iland. We moved to South Africa and deposited this money in a security company in a box as valuables belonging to our foreign We are presently in South Africa as Refugee (Asylum Seekers) and as such the law of South Africa does not permit us to operate or open any bank account here in South Africa or be involved in any financial transaction with the bank. That is why we contacted you to assist us in this transaction. We are ready to give you 30% of the total amount for the inconveniences this will cost you and for accepting to assist us. Indicating your interest as soon as possible, by sending you telephone and fax number for easier communication. On receiving of your acceptance, I shall be glad to give you more clarification on the modalities needed for smooth successful completion of this transaction. I anticipate your quick response. MR.AUTHOR GEZI Alternative email: gezis_family@hotmail.com (For and on Behalf of the Family)

FROM THE DESK OF IBRAHIM MUSSA, BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER, AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK(ADB) OUAGADOUGOU,BURKINA FASO.WEST AFRICA. With Due Respect I am the manager of bill and exchange at the foreign remittance department of african development bank (ADB). I crave your indulgence as i contact you in such a surprising manner. But I respectfully insist you read this letter carefully as I am optimistic it will open doors for unimaginable financial rewards for both of us. In my department we discovered an abandoned sum of Ten Million,Five Hundred Thousand US dollars (US$10.5m) only , in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customer who died along with his entire family in November 2001 in a plan crash. Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died along with him at the plan crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I now decided to make this business proposal to you so that the money could be released to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and i dont want this money to go into the bank treasury as unclaimed Bill. The Banking law and guideline here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed after five years, the money will be transferred into the Bank treasury as "unclaimed fund". The request for a foreigner as next of kin in this business is occasioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a Burkinabe cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. We agree that 30% of this money will be for you as a foreign partner, in respect to the provision of a foreign account , 10% will be set aside for expenses incurred during the business and 60% would be for me. There after I will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentages indicated. Therefore to enable the immediate transfer of this fund to you as arranged, you must apply first to the bank as relation or next of kin of the deceased indicating your bank name,your bank account number, your private telephone and fax number for easy and effective communication and location wherein the money will be remitted. Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or email the text of the application.I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch free and that you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made for the transfer. You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this letter. Trusting to hear from you immediately. Yours faithfully, ibrahim mussa, Bill and exchange manager, African Development bank ADB _________________________________________________________________ Découvrez Live.com : le nouveau moteur de recherche par Messenger! http://www.windowslive.fr/livecom/

X-Mailer: popper Season's Greetings! Forgive my indignation if this message comes to you as a surprise and may offend your personality for contacting you without your prior consent and writing through this channel.I got your contact from a professional database found in internet while searching for a reliable and honest person that will be an anointed steward in a vision very dear to me. I am Mrs. Alondra Jose-Carlos person from Puerto Rico undergoing medical treatment. I am married to Dr. Kevin Jose-Carlos who was a gun runner supplying arms and ammunition to warring factions in Africa before he died in the year 2002.We were married for eleven years without a child. He died after a brief illness that lasted for only four days. Since his after death, I decided not to re-marry or get a child outside my matrimonial home. When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of £ 11.8.Million (Eleven Million, Eight Hundred Thousand British Pounds Sterling) with a Fiduciary company. Presently ,this money is still with the Fiduciary Company. Recently, my doctor told me that I would not last for the next three months due to cancer problem. Though what disturbs me most is my partial paralysis. Having known my condition I decided to donate this fund to an organisation or individual that will utilize this money the way I am going to instruct here in. I want an organisation or individual that will use this to fund, women and youth groups, victims of war, environmental protection, charities, orphanages and widows . It is said that blessed is the hand that giveth. I took this decision because I don't have any child that will inherit this money and as a part of restitution for the atrocities of my husband which I tacitly supported. I don't want a situation where this money will be used in an ungodly manner , hence the reason for taking this bold decision. I am not afraid of death, hence I know where I am going .I know that I am going to be in the bosom. If you consider yourself adequately equipped morally and spiritually for this mission, please ,respond by letting me know your decision to alondracarlos@sify.com Yours sincerely, Mrs. Alondra Jose-Carlos

Dear friend, I am a staff of Private Banking Services at the Bank of China (BOC). I am contacting you concerning our customer and, an investment placed under our banks management 3 years ago. I would respectfully request that you keep the contents of this mail confidential and respect the integrity of the information you come by as a result of this mail. I contacted you independently of our investigation and no one is informed of this communication. I would like to intimate you with certain facts that I believe would be of interest to you. In 2002, the subject matter; ref: bb/boc/bank/0012 came to our bank to engage in business discussions with our Private Banking Services Department. He informed us that he had a financial portfolio of 8.35 million United States Dollars, which he wished to have us turn over (invest) on his behalf. I was the officer assigned to his case; I made numerous suggestions in line with my duties as the de-facto chief operations officer of the Private Banking Services Department, especially given the volume of funds he wished to put into our bank. We met on numerous occasions prior to any investments being placed. I encouraged him to consider various growth funds with prime ratings. The favored route in my advice to customers is to start by assessing data on 6000 traditional stocks and bond managers and 2000 managers of alternative investments. Based on my advice, we spun the money around various opportunities and made attractive margins for our first months of operation, the accrued profit and interest stood at this point at over 10 million United States Dollars, this margin was not the full potential of the fund but he desired low risk guaranteed returns on investments. In mid 2004, he asked that the money be liquidated because he needed to make an urgent investment requiring cash payments in Europe. He directed that I liquidate the funds and had it deposited with a firm. I informed him that the bank would have to make special arrangements to have this done and in order not to circumvent due process, the bank would have to make a 9.5 % deduction from the funds to cater for banking and statutory charges. He complained about the charges but later came around when I explained to him the complexities of the task he was asking of us. Cash movement across borders has become especially strict since the incident of 9/11. I contacted my affiliate in and had the funds available. I undertook all the processes and made sure I followed his precise instructions to the letter and had the funds deposited in a security consultancy firm, the firm is a specialist private firm that accepts deposits from high net worth individuals and blue chip corporations that handle valuable products or undertake transactions that need immediate access to cash. This small and highly private organization is familiar especially to the highly placed and well-connected organizations. In line with instructions, the money was deposited. He told me he wanted the money there in anticipation of his arrival from Norway later that week. This was the last communication we had, this transpired around 9th October 2004. In January this year, we got a call from the security firm informing us that the inactivity of that particular portfolio. This was an astounding position as far as I was concerned, given the fact that I managed the private banking sector I was the only one who knew about the deposit , and I could not understand why he had not come forward to claim his deposit. I made futile efforts to locate him I immediately passed the task of locating him to the internal investigations department of the bank of china. Four days later, information started to trickle in, apparently he was dead. A person who suited his description was declared dead of a heart attack in Canne, South of France. We were soon enough able to identify the body and cause of death was confirmed. The bank immediately launched an investigation into possible surviving next of kin to alert about the situation and also to come forward to claim his estate. If you are familiar with private banking affairs, those who patronize our services usually prefer anonymity, but also some levels of detachment from conventional processes. In his bio-data form, he listed no next of kin. In the field of private banking, opening an account with us means no one will know of its existence, accounts are rarely held under a name; depositors use numbers and codes to make the accounts anonymous. This bank also gives the choice to depositors of having their mail sent to them or held at the bank itself, ensuring that there are no traces of the account and as I said, rarely do they nominate next of kin. Private banking clients apart from not nominating next of kin also usually in most cases leave wills in our care, in this case; he died intestate. In line with our internal processes for account holders who have passed away, we instituted our own investigations in good faith to determine who should have right to claim the estate. This investigation has for the past months been unfruitful. We have scanned every continent and used our private investigation affiliate companies to get to the root of the problem. The investigation did not ever yield any result My official capacity dictates that I am the only party to supervise the investigation and the only party to receive the results of the investigation. This leaves me as the only person with the full picture of what the prevailing situation is in relation to the deposit and the late beneficiary of the deposit. According to practice, the firm will by the end of this financial year broadcast a request for statements of claim to BOC, failing to receive viable claims they will most probably revert the deposit back to BOC. This will result in the money entering the BOC accounting system and the portfolio will be out of my hands and out of the Private Banking Services Department. This will not happen if I have my way. What I wish to relate to you will smack of unethical practice but I want you to understand something. It is only an outsider to the banking world who finds the internal politics of the banking world aberrational. The world of private banking especially is fraught with huge rewards for those who occupy certain offices and oversee certain portfolios. You should have begun by now to put together the general direction of what I propose. There is US$ 8,370,000.00 deposited, I alone have the deposit details and they will release the deposit to no one unless I instruct them to do so. I alone know of the existence of this deposit for as far as BOC is concerned, the transaction with our deceased customer concluded when I sent the funds to the firm, all outstanding interactions in relation to the file are just customer services and due process. They are simply awaiting instructions to release the deposit to any party that comes forward. This is the situation. This bank has spent great amounts of money trying to track this man's family; they have investigated for months and have found no family. The investigation has come to an end. My proposal; I am prepared to place you in a position to give instruction for the release of the deposit to you as the closest surviving relation. Upon receipt of the deposit, I am prepared to share the money with you in half. That is: I will simply nominate you as the next of kin and have them release the deposit to you. We share the proceeds 50/50. I would have gone ahead to ask the funds be released to me, but that would have drawn a straight line to me and my involvement in claiming the deposit. I assure you that I could have the deposit released to you within a few days. I will simply inform the bank of the final closing of the file relating to the customer I will then officially communicate with the firm and instruct them to release the deposit to you. With these two things: all is done. The alternative would be for us to have the firm direct the funds to another bank with you as account holder. This way there will be no need for you to think of receiving the money from the firm. We can fine-tune this based on our interactions. I am aware of the consequences of this proposal. I ask that if you find no interest in this project that you should discard this mail. I ask that you do not be vindictive and destructive. If my offer is of no appeal to you, delete this message and forget I ever contacted you. Do not destroy my career because you do not approve of my proposal. You may not know this but people like myself who have made tidy sums out of comparable situations run the whole private banking sector. I am not a criminal and what I do, I do not find against good conscience, this may be hard for you to understand, but the dynamics of my industry dictates that I make this move. Such opportunities only come ones' way once in a lifetime. I cannot let this chance pass me by, for once I find myself in total control of my destiny. These chances won't pass me by. I ask that you do not destroy my chance, if you will not work with me let me know and let me move on with my life but do not destroy me. I am a family man and this is an opportunity to provide them with new opportunities. There is a reward for this project and it is a task well worth undertaking. I have evaluated the risks and the only risk I have here is from you refusing to work with me and alerting my bank. I am the only one who knows of this situation, good fortune has blessed you with a name that has planted you into the center of relevance in my life. Let's share the blessing. If you find yourself able to work with me, contact me through this same email account. If you give me positive signals, I will initiate this process towards a conclusion. I wish to inform you that should you contact me via official channels; I will deny knowing you and about this project. I repeat, I do not want you contacting me through my official phone lines nor do I want you contacting me through my official email account. Contact me only through this email address. I do not want any direct link between you and me. My official lines are not secure lines as they are periodically monitored to assess our level of customer care in line with our Total Quality Management Policy. Please observe this instruction religiously. Please, again, note I am a family man; I have a wife and children. I send you this mail not without a measure of fear as to what the consequences, but I know within me that nothing ventured is nothing gained and that success and riches never come easy or on a platter of gold. This is the one truth I have learned from my private banking clients. Do not betray my confidence. If we can be of one accord, send me your response on this email fsh1953@yahoo.com.cn to enable us commences this line of discussion. Best regards, Shang Fulin

Dear Friend, Kindly accept my apology for sending my mail to you. I want you to trust me and help me out in this my condition. I believe you are a highly respected personality, considering the fact that I sourced your profile from a human resource profile database on your country in the Internet. Though, I do not know to what extent you are familiar with events and fragile political situation in Liberia but it has formed consistent headlines in the CNN, BBCnews bulletins. My Name is Miss Peace Mathew 24 years old and my mother is rebecca tomson from Liberia, a Country in West Africa, now seeking for refugee in Dakar-Senegal under the(UNHCR). The only surviving daughter and my mother a widow who is presently in Hospital in Dakar-Senegal. My late Father is Mathew dennis tomson, Deputy Minister of Public Works in Liberia. My Father was falsely accused of plotting to remove the then PRESIDENT OF LIBERIA CHARLES TAYLOR) from office. Without trial, Charles Taylor killed him. I am looking looking for someone who can take me as child I promise to be obedient to you and I will bring happiness to your life. I got your contact from the Internet Search. I want you to assist me in this transaction. The deposit documents indicate me as the next of kin. Presently, I am saddled with the problem of securing a trust worthy foriegn personality to help me. You can verify this from some of the international newspapers posted in the web sites below: (I) <<http://www.usatoday.com/news/world/2003-07-15-liberia_x.htm>> (ii) < color.http://www.unwire.org/UNWire/20030716/449_66> 21.asp Before my Father was killed, he moved out the sum of $5.2 million and deposited it with a Finance Company. All that is needed is for me to instruct the Finance company to transfer the fund to your account, We will renumerate you with 20% at the end, but most of all is that I solicit your trust in this transaction. Kindly include your Full Name, Private Telephone and Fax Numbers where you can always be reached, your Residential or Company Address to enable him send detail information/documents that will enable you receive the fund without any problem either now or in future as all modalities as been perfected. As soon as I get your full acceptance I will forward you the contact informations of the Finance company. My email address is peace_mathew10.com I will send my picture when I hear from you. Please your urgent response is needed. Best Regards. MISS.Peace

Hello This letter may come to you as a surprise due to the fact that we have not yet met. I have to say that I have no intentions of causing you any pains so i decided to contact you through this medium. As you read this, I don't want you to feel sorry for me, because, I believe everyone will die someday. My name is Razaq Samiu, a merchant in Dubai, in the U.A.E. I have been diagnosed with prostate and esophageal Cancer that was discovered very late due to my laxity in caring for my health. It has defiled all form of medicine and right now, I have only about a few months to live according to medical experts. I have not particularly lived my life so well, as I never really cared for anyone not even myself but my business. Though I am very rich, I was never generous, I was always hostile to people and only focus on my business as that was the only thing I cared for. But now I regret all this as I now know that there is more to life than just wanting to have or make all the money in the world. I believe when God gives me a second chance to come to this world I would live my life a different way from how I have lived it. Now that I know my time is near, I have willed and given most of my properties and assets to my immediate and extended family members and as well as a few close friends and Schools in the UAE. I have decided to give alms to charity organizations, as I want this to be one of the last good deeds I do on earth. So far, I have distributed money to some charity organizations in the U.A.E, England and Ireland. Now that my health has deteriorated so badly, I cannot do this my self any more. I once asked members of my family to close one of my accounts and donate the money, which I have there to charity organization in Bulgaria, they refused and kept the money to themselves. Hence, I do not trust them anymore, as they seem not to be contended with what I have left for them. The last of my money which is the huge cash that I deposit in a bank in England Uk. I want you to help me collect this deposit and dispatched it to charity organizations and let them know that it is I Razaq Samiu that is making this generous donation. I am writing this from my laptop computer in my hospital bed in England where I wait for my time to come. If you are interested to help me i will give you more information about this like the amount that i deposited in the bank and Contact of the bank so you can contcat them. I will also send you a picture of my self when i am on my laptop in the hospital. Note that you will take 20% out of the funds and give 80% to the charity organizations. I pray that God uses you to support and assist me with good heart God be with you. If you can help respond back to me on my private email: razaqin01@yahoo.es Razaq Samiu

My dear. greetings from miss Fatoumata Saleeby. I am writting this letter with due respect and heartful of tears since we have not known or met ourselves previously, I am asking for whom to love and love me as well after I have gone through your profile and i just pick interest on you. I am fair in complexion, I am about 5fit 7in tall, I love sport events, going outdoors activities, watching of moving, shopping, walking etc.In a nutshell, My name is Miss Fatoumata Saleeby 22 years old from the republic of Liberia in west Africa, now seeking for refugee in Dakar-Senegal under the (UNHCR). I therefore write to inform you that I am the only surviving child and daughter of the deceased Dr. ELIE E. SALEEBY the former MINISTER OF FINANCE / EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR CENTRAL BANK OF LIBERIA in the year July 1997-Feb. 2003. The reason for this correspondence is to formally request for mutual assistance on business relationship with you in order to benefit from your wealth of experience in business. The secret fact therefore, is that my father kept the sum of US$4,700, 000.00 (Four million seven hundred thousand US Dollars) CASH. The money was deposited at Bank here in Dakar Senegal. The money is the share of proceeds from a deal executed with my father's colleagues in the hierarchy of membership of the LIBERIAN JOINT PUBLIC TENDER BOARD during a contract award to an Ukrainian - RUSSIA Diamond Extracting Company when my father was a chairman. Due to the civil war caused by rebel leader Charles Taylor who has just been toppled by another rebel group and my father's status as a civil-servant by law in my country and the sensitivity of my father's position that attracts public attention, he cannot operate a Domiciliary account in order to keep this large sum of money in a bank in my country. My father retired and died lately before he could withdraw this money here in and transfer it out of Africa. I anticipate to conclude arrangement to start this venture with you as quick as possible. Due to my youthful age and also refugee here in senegal, decide to claim the money now with a foreign partner. Upon your indicated interest, we will arrange for a meeting in the country of your choice when the money is moved from the Bank to your account and discuss in details the terms of agreement. I want to invest in any company that you suggest under your professional guidance. Please include your private mobile telephone number in your reply for easy communication. I earnestly await your urgent response as I expect you to treat this matter with required maturity, attention and committment. with best regards Fatoumata Saleeby. v

FROM:BARR.ROTIMI BELLO (ESQ)NO.5 MILVERTON STREET, VICTORIA-ISLAND LAGOS. EMAIL:barrister_rotimibello_chamber@yahoo.co.uk Dear Sir/Madam, I am Barrister Rotimi Bello, a solicitor at law. I am the personal attorney to Mr. Douglas Raju, a national of your country, who used to work with shell development company in Nigeria and as well a one time secret agent in transferring of money overseas for the Late head of state of Nigeria {Late Gen.SANI ABACHA}.Before his death On the 21st of April 2002 [my client,his wife and their only daugther were involved in a car accident along sagamu express way in which all occupants of the motor died}. My client {RAJU}deposited the sum of $15.5m in a commercial bank(CENTRAL BANK OF NIGERIA) here in Nigeria for himself, with the hope of transferring it to his country as soon as he is on leave. Since his death I have made several enquiries to your embassy to locate any of my clients extended relatives this has also proved unsuccessful. After these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to trace his last name over the Internet, to locate any member of his family hence I contacted you. I have contacted you to assist in repatriating the money and property left behind by my client before they get confiscated or declared unserviceable by the bank where these Money were Deposited. Particularly, the (CENTRAL BANK OF NIGERIA) where the deceased Deposited (US$15,500,000)fiftheen million five hundred thounsand dollars has issued me a notice to provide the next of kin with in the next ten official working days. Since I have been unsuccessful in locating the relatives for over 3years now I seek your consent to present you as the next of kin of the deceased since you have the same last name so that the proceeds of this deposit (Money) valued at (US$15,500,000)fiftheen million five hundred thounsand dollars can be claim by you and then you and me can share the money. 40% to me and 60% to you I have all necessary legal documents that can be used to back up any claim we may make. All I require is your honest cooperation to enable us see this deal through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you and me from any breach of the law. Please get in touch with me by my private email address:(barrister_rotimibello_chamber@yahoo.co.uk) for more information to enable us discuss further or you can call my private line;# 234 8033791090 Best regards, Barrister Rotimi bello (Esq) EMAIL:barrister_rotimibello_chamber@yahoo.co.uk

DEAR SIR, With due respect and humility I send you this mail. Please I am indeed sorry bothering you. Permit me a brief intoduction . I believe that on the basis of such introduction you would understand the purpose of this mail. I am a professional financial advisor on offshore and real estate investment, portfolio management with a private finance and security company in Thailand. My company work for expatriate community here in Bangkok, Thailand. One of my client , Mr. Lee Kok Wai, a Singaporean business man deposited the sum of Sixteen Million, Eight Hundred thousand United States Dollars (US$16.8M) with our company . It was deposited as family treasures. But sadly and unfortunately, Mr. Lee Kok Wai lost his life in the deadly Tsunami of December 26th 2004. Ever since no close relative or next of kin has come forward to claim the money deposited with us. Therefore, My colleague and I, who are the direct fund managers have decided to move/transfer this fund into a nominated foreing account, for future investment. To this regards, I seek your assistance and co-operation . 1. I will arrange for the deposit certificate to be changed to your name, 2.I will issue to you a Transfer Authorisation of the Consignment, 3. Afterwhich, you will transfer the money to your private accounts. 4. You will later on assist us in investing the money in a lucrative business. You should be rest assured that no one will question it because all financial deposit Cerificates and transfe r authorisation pass my desk for final approval To facilitate a smooth deal, we have agree on the followng :1. 30% of the money for you as reward , 2. 5% For expenses on hotel , flight tickets and any other, 3. While, 65% shall be for us {My colleage and Me}. For further details , send to me : 1. Your mobile phone number, 2. Your direct fax number , this will enable me fax to you the documents concerning the consignment. This is a sensitive and private business, The knowledge of which should be restricted , therfore do not dicsuss it with a third party . Do not fear, it is not terrorist or drug money. I thank you in advance for reasoning with me. I look forward to your favorable reply. Yours sincerely, JAMES SILAS .

RE: COLLECTION OF FUND (US$25,000,000.00) UNDER SPECIAL ARRANGEMENT. Pardon me if I have offended you by contacting you for such a big transaction through an ordinary letter which makes it suspicious considering the type of fraud proposals moving around the world today. However, I was advised to explain this transaction to you on a face to face meeting. I could not do this because of the situation in the world today not being sure of your reaction. I am Jones Martin, a Consultant and Broker from Kingston Jamaica. I was hired by a Japanese Businessman to broker an investment deal between him and an oil company in Venezuela. This deal was executed in January, 2003 and matured for termination in January 2005. On maturity, the Japanese Businessman and the oil firm decided to terminate the investment in cash to avoid payment of investment tax which amounted to several tens of millions of US Dollars to the American Internal Revenue Service (IRS). A special arrangement was made between a top Japanese banker working with Japanese bank in New York, the Oil Company and the businessman to terminate the investment in cash payment under a fictitious name, with an arrangement to change it later with a power of attorney which they prepared and handed over to The banker. I was directly involved, well paid and mandated to organized and carry out the deal. All the cash was withdrawn in June 2005 and transported to EUROPE by direct bank vault delivery to a finance company for safekeeping pending the collection. The real content of the boxes was not declared to the storage as it was delivered as personal family treasure worth US$25M.The certificates for the storage, secret codes for the opening of the boxes and its keys were all handed over to me. Mr. Takashi the Florida businessman was planning to go to Europe by August 2005 with me for the collection when the unexpected happened in Hurricane Katrina Mishap, a natural disaster which claimed his life and that of the top banker. This left me devastated and confused as I have not yet handed over the deposit details to the owner and the power of attorney prepared for the change which was signed was still with the banker in his office which was lost. Since last December the diplomatic storage manager has been calling me to bring or tell the owner to come over for collection. Since then, I have been finding any reliable person to collect these consignments under special and well negotiated arrangement until I came across your details. Be rest assured that this transaction has been well organized, 100% safe, legal, and should be kept very confidential. Signify your interest by getting back to me via my email as soon as possible. Regard, Jones Martin

Content-Type: text/plain Message-Id: <20070105032923.C072410015C5@reliquia.netfor.com.br> Date: Fri, 5 Jan 2007 01:29:23 -0200 (BRST) Content-Transfer-Encoding: quoted-printable =0D FROM VICTORIA BOLANO.=0D INTERNATIONAL PROMOTIONS/PRIZE AWARD DEPARTMENT=0D RESULTS FOR CATEGORY "A" DRAWS.=0D =0D Congratulations to you as we bring to your notice, the results of the Fir= st Category draws of THE HOLLAND CASINO LOTTO PROMO INT. We are happy to = inform you that you have emerged a winner under the First Category, which= is part of our promotional draws. The draws were being officially announ= ced this morning the 4th of January, 2007.Participants were selected thro= ugh a computer ballot system drawn from 2,500,000 email addresses of indi= viduals and companies from Africa, America, Asia, Australia,Europe, Middl= e East and Oceania as part of our International Promotions Program.=0D =0D Your e- mail address, attached to Coupon numbers 4770001 consequently won= in the First Category. You have therefore been awarded a lump sum pay ou= t of 500,00000eur (Five hundred thousand euros), which is the winning pay= out for Category A winners. This is from a total cash prize of 5,000,000.= 00 Million Euros shared amongst the first Ten (10) lucky winners in this = category. =0D =0D CONGRATULATIONS!=0D =0D Your fund is now deposited with the paying Bank.In your best interest to = avoid mix up of numbers and names of any kind, we request that you keep t= he entire details of your award strictly from public notice until the pro= cess of transferring your claims has been completed, and your funds remit= ted to your account.This is part of our security protocol to avoid double= claiming or unscrupulous acts by participants/nonparticipants of this pr= ogram. =0D =0D Please contact your claims agent immediately for due processing and remit= tance of your prize money to a designated bank account of your choice. Yo= u are advised to contact the agents by email,phone or fax. Failure to do = so may warrant disqualification.NOTE: For easy reference and identificati= on, remember to quote your Coupon numbers in your correspondence with you= r claims agent.=0D =0D To file for your claim,please contact the fiduciary agent with your Coupo= n numbers,tel/fax numbers and full names.=0D ***********************************************=0D MR. KARL WINSLOW.=0D AMSTERDAM,THE NETHERLANDS.=0D TEL: +31-626-403-565=0D FAX:+31-847-355-196.=0D EMAIL:k_winslow@myway.com or karlwinslow@sify.com=0D ***********************************************=0D All winnings must be notarized to complete the claim process; winners wil= l be referred to a Foreign Transfer Manager,to have their winnings notari= zed. =0D Congratulations once again from all our staff.=0D =0D Sincerely Yours,=0D =0D MRS. VICTORIA BOLANO.=0D THE PROMOTION COORDINATOR=0D =0D =0D

FROM:MR.MUSTAFA ALI AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING UNIT. INTERNATIONAL BANK OF AFRICA (IBA), BURKINA FASO. DIRECT TEL:00226 70 37 73 20. DEAR FRIEND I AM MR. MUSTAFA ALI THE DIRECTOR IN CHARGE OF AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING SECTION OF INTERNATIONAL BANK OF AFRICA(IBA)BURKINA FASO IN WEST AFRICA WITH DUE RESPECT AND REGARDS. I HAVE DECIDED TO CONTACT YOU ON A BUSINESS TRANSACTION THAT WILL BE VERY BENEFICIAL TO BOTH OF US AT THE END OF THE TRANSACTION. DURING OUR INVESTIGATION AND AUDITING IN THIS BANK, MY DEPARTMENT CAME ACROSS A VERY HUGE SUM OF MONEY BELONGING TO A DECEASED PERSON WHO DIED ON 31ST OCTOBER 1999 IN A PLANE CRASH AND THE FUND HAS BEEN ORMANT IN HIS ACCOUNT WITH THIS BANK WITHOUT ANY CLAIM OF THE FUND IN URCUSTODY EITHER FROM HIS MILY OR RELATION BEFORE OUR DISCOVERY TO THIS DEVELOPMENT. ALTHOUGH PERSONALLY, I KEEP THIS INFORMATION SECRET WITHIN MYSELF AND PARTNERS TO ENABLE THE WHOLE PLANS AND IDEA BE PROFITABLE AND SUCCESSFUL DURING THE TIME OF EXECUTION. THE SAID AMOUNT WAS U.S $21.7M (TWENTY ONE MILLION SEVEN HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS). AS IT MAY INTEREST YOU TO KNOW, I GOT YOUR IMPRESSIVE INFORMATION THROUGH THE BURKINA FASO CHAMBER OF COMMERCE ON FOREIGN BUSINESS RELATIONS HERE IN BURKINA FASO. MEANWHILE ALL THE WHOLE ARRANGEMENT TO PUT CLAIM OVER THIS FUND AS THE BONAFIDE NEXT OF KIN TO THE DECEASED, GET THE REQUIRED APPROVAL AND TRANSFER THIS MONEY TO A FOREIGN ACCOUNT HAS BEEN PUT IN PLACE AND DIRECTIVES AND NEEDED INFORMATION WILL BE RELAYED TO YOU AS SOON AS YOU INDICATE YOUR INTEREST AND WILLINGNESS TO ASSIST US AND ALSO BENEFIT YOUR SELF TO THIS GREAT BUSINESS OPPORTUNITY. IN FACT I COULD HAVE DONE THIS DEAL ALONE BUT BECAUSE OF MY POSITION IN THIS COUNTRY AS A CIVIL SERVANT(A BANKER),WE ARE NOT ALLOWED TO OPERATE A FOREIGN ACCOUNT AND WOULD EVENTUALLY RAISE AN EYE BROW ON MY SIDE DURING THE TIME OF TRANSFER BECAUSE I WORK IN THIS BANK. THIS IS THE ACTUAL REASON WHY IT WILL REQUIRE A SECOND PARTY OR FELLOW WHO WILL FORWARD CLAIMS AS THE NEXT OF KIN WITH AFFIDAVIT OF TRUST OF OATH TO THE BANK AND ALSO PRESENT A FOREIGN ACCOUNT WHERE HE WILL NEED THE MONEY TO BE RE-TRANSFERRED INTO ON HIS REQUEST AS IT MAY BE AFTER DUE VERIFICATION AND CLARIFICATION BY THE CORRESPONDENT BRANCH OF THE BANK WHERE THE WHOLE MONEY WILL BE REMITTED FROM TO YOUR OWN DESIGNATED BANK ACCOUNT. I WILL NOT FAIL TO INFORM YOU THAT THIS TRANSACTION IS 100% RISK FREE. ON SMOOTH CONCLUSION OF THIS TRANSACTION, YOU WILL BE ENTITLED TO 30% OF THE TOTAL SUM AS GRATIFICATION, WHILE 5% WILL BE SET ASIDE TO TAKE CARE OF EXPENSES THAT MAY ARISE DURING THE TIME OF TRANSFER AND ALSO TELEPHONE BILLS, WHILE 65% WILL BE FOR ME. PLEASE, YOU HAVE BEEN ADVICED TO KEEP "TOP SECRET" AS I AM STILL IN SERVICE AND INTEND TO RETIRE FROM SERVICE AFTER WE CONCLUDE THIS DEAL WITH YOU. I WILL BE MONITORING THE WHOLE SITUATION HERE IN THIS BANK UNTIL YOU CONFIRM THE MONEY IN YOUR ACCOUNT AND ASK ME TO COME DOWN TO YOUR COUNTRY FOR SUBSEQUENT SHARING OF THE FUND ACCORDING TO PERCENTAGES PREVIOUSLY INDICATED AND FURTHER INVESTMENT, EITHER IN YOUR COUNTRY OR ANY COUNTRY YOU ADVICE US TO INVEST IN. ALL OTHER NECESSARY VITAL INFORMATION WILL BE SENT TO YOU WHEN I HEAR FROM YOU. PLEASE INDICATE YOUR DIRECT TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBER WHEN REPLYINGTHIS BUSINESS PROPOSALOR CALL ME ON MY ABOVE DIRECT TELEPHONE NUMBER 00226703773320. IF YOU ARE NOT INTERESTED, PLEASE ALSO INDICATE SO THAT IT WILL ENABLE ME TO CONTACT ANOTHER FOREIGN PARTNER WITH RECOMMENDATIONS TO CARRY OUT THIS DEAL.A SWIFT ACKNOWLEDGMENT OF YOUR RECEIPT OF THIS MAIL WILL BE APPRECIATED.THANK YOU AND GOD BLESS YOU.I LOOK FORWARD TO RECEIVE YOUR EMAIL. BEST REGARDS, MR.MUSTAFA ALI _________________________________________________________________ MSN Messenger : appels gratuits de PC à PC ! http://www.msn.fr/newhotmail/Default.asp?Ath=f

Attn: Sir/ Madam, I am the personal account officer to the great late INDUSTRIALIST who had an account in one of the top banks here in South Africa. Forgive my contact because this letter comes to you as a surprise, as you don't know of it's coming before. My contact is for you to please assist to transfer US$125,000.000.00 ( One hundred & twenty- five million United States dollars only) in tranches from a Prime Bank here in South Africa to any oversea's account(s). The account was opened in 1998 and he died in 2003 without a written or oral WILL and since 2003 nobody had operated the account. The account is dormant and the funds floating. If I do not remit this money out urgently it will be forfeited to the bank. Firstly, I must solicit your strictest confidence in this transaction because of my official position and nature of the deal. The business can be concluded in 10 (ten) banking days .I am sure and have confidence of your ability and reliability to prosecute a transaction of this great magnitude. The account holder was a foreigner and no other person knows about this account or anything concerning it, the account has no other beneficiary and until his death he was the accountant of the company. My investigation through the National immigration department proved to me as well that he was single as at the time of his entry into the Republic of South Africa. The credit balance in this account is USD$125 Million ( One Hundred & Twenty five Million United States Dollars only). Your assistance as a foreigner is necessary because the management of the bank will welcome any foreigner who has correct information on this account which I will disclose to you if you are interested to do this business with me.There is no risk in this business if you follow my instructions. Given my position and my personal rapport with the manager of the bank, the funds can be transferred to any account(s) you nominate .I need an assurance from you that this money will be intact pending my arrival to your bank for disbursements. State the A/C Details. A/c No:............ Bank Name:........ A/c Holder:........ Beneficiary Name:... We will start with the first swift wire-transfer of US$25 million( Twenty -five million United States only) Upon successful transfer of the first tranch without any disappointment from your side, you shall apply for the outstanding sum of US $100 Million to the same or other account(s). Armed with correct information as a foreigner and appropriate documentations as we shall arrange I will use my position to secure a prompt conclusion to the transaction. Your duty is to send me the banking coordinates for the transfer while maintaining the required confidentiality . At the conclusion of the transfer you will receive 35%, 5% will be for any expenses both parties incurred in the process of this business and 60% of the funds will be for me. Upon your strong assurance of your full cooperations and receipt of your account details then I will start the process of the funds transfer to your account without further delay. Contact Me immediately for futher details. Thanks for your anticipated cooperations. Yours Faithfully, Mr.Stephen Ajken _________________________________________________________________ See their smiles, hear their laughter with Windows Live Messenger! http://messenger.live.com

Dr. Peter Gungula Auditing and Accounting Unit Foreign Operations Department Union Togolaise De Banque, Lome-Togo Branch Republic of Togo. Phone;+228 983 34 66 Email; pgungula@yahoo.co.uk I am Dr. Peter Gungula the Director in charge of Auditing and Accounting section Union Togolaise De Banque lome-togo and also Chairman of Investigating and Auditing Department of this Bank. With due respect and regard, I have decided to contact you on a Business Transaction that will be very beneficial to both of us and our families at the end of this transaction. During our Investigation and Auditing in this Bank, my department came across a very huge sum of money belonging to one Deceased who died on October 24, 2004 Martinsville plane crash Aircraft type Beechcraft King Air 200. As the fund has been dormant in his account with this Bank without any claim of the fund in our custody either from his family or relation because he did not indicate any next of kin to this account. The amount in the dormant account is Fourteen Million United States Dollars (US$14 000,000.00) . As it may interest you to know, I got your contact from the Chamber of Commerce on foreign business relations here in Lome -togo though I did not disclose why i needed a foreign contact and only told the director on seat it was for retirement and investment purposes. Meanwhile as a Senior Staff in this bank, and the Director of Auditing and Accounting, I have in my possession all the necessary documents to perfect this deal by making you the bonafide next of kin/Partner whom this money will be transferred into your account. I need your assistance and co-operation to get this deal done. Because as a foreigner, you stand a better position to be presented through documentation as the next of kin/Partner since the deceased is also a foreigner, this is the reason why I could not do this deal alone as a staff of the bank as well. I will not fail to inform you that this transaction is 100% risk free. On smooth Conclusion of this transaction, you will be entitled to 30% of the total sum as gratification, while 10% will be set aside to take care of expenses that may arise during the time of transfer and also telephone bills, while 60% will be for me and my partner. Please, you have been advised to keep this "Top Secret" as we are still in service and intend to retire from service after we conclude this deal with you. I will be monitoring the whole situation here in this bank until you confirm the money in your bank account. And ask me to come down to your country for subsequent sharing of the fund according to percentages previously indicated and further investment,either in your country or any country you advice us to invest in. All other necessary vital information will be sent to you when I hear from you. I suggest you get back to me as soon as possible stating your wish in this deal. I am expecting your urgent reply as soon as you receive this message. God bless you And your family. Dr. Peter Gungula Tell:+ 228 983 34 66 N/B:Please,for security reason,you should write me further with this e-mail account; pgungula@yahoo.co.uk _________________________________________________________________ Express yourself instantly with MSN Messenger! Download today it's FREE! http://messenger.msn.click-url.com/go/onm00200471ave/direct/01/

From: Mr.Al-Zarqawi Yusuf Dear Friend, Your first reaction to this mail will be total rejection, scare and maybe disbelief, owning largely to the atrocities people commit these days.But this mail comes from a devastated, sorrowful and emotional laden soul that needs compassion from a kind and good spirited person to wipe away my tears and appropriate my dream and humanitarian gesture. As you read this, I don't want you to feel sorry for me, because, I believe everyone dies someday.,I am Al-Zarqawi Yusuf, A Oil merchant in Dubai, United Arab Emirate ( UAE). I have been diagnosed with Cancer, which was discovered very late, due to my laxity in caring for my health. It has defiled all forms of medicine; Right now I have only about a limited to live, according to my Medical Doctor. I have not particularly lived my life so well, as I never really cared for myself but the Oil business.Though I am very rich, I was never generous, I only focused on my business as that was the only thing I cared for. But now I regret all this as I now know that there is more to life than just wanting to have or make all the money in the world. I believe when Allah gives me a second chance and heal me I would live my life a different way from how I have lived it.I have sowed a seed for my healing I have willed and given most of my properties and assets to my immediate and extended family members and as well as a few close friends. i want Allah to be merciful to me and accept my soul and so, I have decided to give arms to charity organizations and give succor and comfort to the less privileged of the Tsunami and Hurricane Katrina Victims, as I want this to be one of the last good deeds I do on earth so far, by distributed some of this money to some charity organizations in India,Hurricane Katrina victims in USA and other part of the world. Now that my health has deteriorated so badly, I cannot do this my self anymore.I once asked members of my family to close one of my accounts in Saudi Bank and distribute the money which I have there to charity organization and to the less privileged in Bulgaria and Sudan. They cashed the money but kept it only to themselves. Hence I do not trust them anymore,as they seem not to be contended with what I have left for them already.The last of my money, which no one knows of, is the huge cash deposit of Thirty Five Million United States Dollars ( US$35Million) that I have in the Vault of The Security Company as family valuable since the year 2003 for safekeeping.I want you to collect this deposit on my behalf and disburse it to the Tsunami Earthquake victims in Asia for the less privileged. Please send me a mail to indicate your wiliness to assist in this disbursement. I will set aside 10% for you for your time and efforts by notifying the security company as soon as i hear from you.I need your urgent reply with your full name and address, your Phone and Fax numbers and your Occupation so that I will not have to go on sourcing for a credible person to handle this project for himself and the rest of the less privileged.I will also plead to you to always pray for me because only Allah heals. Wasaalam Regards, Al-Zarqawi Yusuf.

DR.MIKE CHIBUZOR Executive Investigation Chairman,On Contracts Payment Review panal Committee. Falomo Office Complex, Ikoyi-Lagos. E-mail:dr_mikechibuzor02@yahoo.com.hk[ PLEASE REPLY ME WITH THIS E-MAIL ADDRESS] Attention:ceo First, I must solicit your strictest confidence in this transaction; this is virtue of its nature as being utterly confidential and top secret. I am the Executive Investigation Chairman Committee on Review of Contracts Payments instituted by H.E. President Olusegun Obasanjo to probe/review all contracts executed and payments made during the regime of late General Sani Abacha. I have been mandated by my colleagues on the Committee to seek your assistance in the transfer of the sum of US$31.5Million. As you may know, the late General Abacha and members of his government embezzled billion of dollars through spurious contracts and payments to foreigners between 1993-1998, and this is now the subject of probe by my Committee. In the course of our review, we have discovered the sum of US$31.5Million,which the former dictator could not transfer from the dedicated account of the Central Bank of Nigeria before his sudden death on June 8, 1998. It is this amount that my colleagues and I have decided to acquire for ourselves through your assistance. This assistance becomes crucial because we cannot acquire the fund in our names. We have thus developed a, fool proof, legal and totally risk free arrangement through which the fund can be transferred within a very short time, if you follow strictly our instructions. The plan is to use our position and influence on the Committee to present you as a foreign contractor beneficiary of the fund. We shall arrange all documentation to support this claim and get Approval for the transfer of the funds for your benefit on our behalf. The arrangement is perfected to be 100% risk free and we are sure the transaction can be concluded within 7-10 working days from when you agree to assist us. You should acknowledge the receipt of my mail through the above Telephone and Fax numbers Or E-Mail address so we can further discuss the modalities of your cooperation and negotiate the charge for your kindly assistance. You were highly recommended and You definitely have a lot to benefit from this transaction as we are prepared to give you 30% of the total funds as soon as you secure it in your Account. Please, endeavour to give me your telephone/fax number(s)including a bank details for the transfer of the above fund,through which we can communicate with you in confidence (in your response) as the need for strict confidentiality is of essence to this transaction. Please i want your reply from this email:<dr_mikechibuzor02@yahoo.com.hk> We await your urgent response. Yours Faithfully, DR.MIKE CHIBUZOR. CHIARMAN CONTRACT REVEIW.

From: Mrs. Patricia Jonas Savimbi Email: petersavimbi7@webmail.co.za +27-724340319 KEEP CONFIDENTIAL PLEASE. Attn: Sir/Madam. This letter may come to you as a surprise but I really prayed to God to help me choose somebody that will be my true partner, a person who has a fear of God that cannot betray my remaining family and me as I don't even know whom to trust so I allowed the spirit of God to lead me. I am Mrs. Patricia Jonas Savimbi, wife to the late leader of the National Union of the Total Liberation of Angola (UNITA) After surviving more than a dozen assassination attempts, my husband, Savimbi was killed four years later, in February 2002, in a battle with Angolan government troops. Two weeks before he died, he called me and reveals the existence of US$16,400.000.00 (SIXTEEN Million, FOUR HUNDRED THOUSAND United States Dollars) which he deposited as valuable items with a Finance and Security Company in South Africa. This money was income my late husband accumulate from the sale of Gold & Diamond with top member's of the National Union of the Total Liberation of Angola. When I heard the bad news of my husband's death, his trusted aid moved me and members of our family out on hiding, but unfornately my elder son and myself were caught and place under house arrest. Luckily to us, my second son has escaped to South Africa through the border where he reside as a political refugee. So my reason of contacting you is because of the problem which my son is facing in trying to transfer the money, the labour law of South Africa does not permit an asylum seeker (Refugee) the right to financial transaction. This was the basic reason why I decide to contact you, so that you will stand as the beneficiary of the fund. If we agree on this, then the ownership of the consignment/funds and every documents will automatically be changed to your name. We are offering you 30% of the total money, as a commission for your services, while 70% goes to my family, which we intend to invest immediately we are being released from house arrest. I am assuring you that this transaction is risk free, all we need from you is your co-operation and sincerity of purpose. You will be contacting my son Peter Savimbi on Email: petersavimbi7@webmail.co.za for more details on how to conclude this transaction. I will wait for your response through my son, thank you and God bless. In your email to my son Peter, kindly forward to him the following as it will be used during the process of change of ownership: 1 You're Full Name 2.You're Contact (Home) Address 3.Your Telephone Moble/Home,and Fax number 4.You can also call my son on his phone number in South Africa +27 724340319. Thanks and may the almighty father guide us through. Thank you. Mrs. Patricia Jonas Savimbi For: Savimbi Family. ALTERNATIVE EMAIL: petersavimbi5@webmail.co.za

Dear Friend, My name is Dr Willison Van, am the branch and computer management department here confidential business proposition for you. On october 6, 2002, an American Geologist/Contractor with the Economic Community Of West African States (ECOWAS), Dr. George W.Brumley From Atlanta,U.S.A Deposited the sum of US$15,500,000.00 ( Fiften million Five hundred thousand Dollars only) in my bank. Upon maturity,I sent aroutine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month,we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers,the Economic Community Of West Africa States (ECOWAS) that Dr George W.Brumley died in a plane crash with his intire family in Kenya,East Africa in the year 2003. I want you to visit the website below for more information about the PlaneCrash: <http://www.wral.com/news/2345844/detail.html> <http://www.cnn.com/2003/WORLD/africa/07/20/kenya.crash/index.html> I therefore made further investigation and discovered that In the bank form for next of kin, George W.Brumley Before his death filled his wife JEAN BRUMLEY as his next of kin but unfortunately, the wife died with him along others and therefore, there is nobody left behind to claim the fund of Dr. George Brumley as his next of kin that was why I contacted you and proposed it as a deal between us. Meanwhile, Official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank as the next of kin was in the name of his wife. Based on that, No one will ever come forward to claim itI will like to seek foryour permission as a foreigner to stand as the next of kin to Dr.George W.Brumley so that the fruits of this old man's labor will not be use for financing weapons which will further enhance the courses of war in the world in general. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 55% for me and 40% for you and 5% for Expenses Incurred in the course of the transaction.There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done accordingly and with my position as the bill the exchange guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. if you are interested, please reply immediately address: by indicating your address, Account number, phone and fax number for easy communication. Upon your response, I shall then provideyou with more details and that will help you understand the transaction Finally, You should observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Anxiously Awaiting for your urgent response. Thanks and best regards to your family. FROM Dr Willison Van

Dear Friend, With great pleasure I Mr. Donald Ofu Obidima, Credit control Manager of a Bank (name upheld)is writing you in respect of a foreign customer an Oil consultant/contractor with the Nigerian National Petroleum corporation,Engr.Lee Seunghyo made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months valued at US$25,000,000.00 (Twenty-five Million Dollars) in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation that Engr.Lee Seunghyo died in Korean Air Flight 801, which crashed in Guam on August 1997 with other passengers onboard. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Engr. Lee Seunghyo died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless.Also, he did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents,including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank.This sum of US$25,000,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. Since the demise of this our customer, I have personally watched the account with keen interest to see the next of kin but all has proved abortive as no one has come to claim his FIXED DEPOSIT fund of USD.$25million, [Twenty five million United States Dollars] which has been with my branch for a very long time. Since his death, none of his next-of-kin or relations has come forward to lay claims for this money asthe heir. A member of our government trade delegation to your country gave your impeccable profile to me. Hence I have decided to seek your co-operation in this business deal due to the sensitivity of this transaction. It may interest you to know that I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money cannot be approved to a local Bank account here, but can only be approved to a foreigner with an account since the money is in US Dollars. I have decided as a matter of urgency upon this discovery now seek your permission to have you stand as next of kin to the deceased Engr. Lee Seunghyo as No one has ever come forward to claim this fund. In accordance to Nigerian Law, fund deposited for a long period of time without claim will be reverted to the Nigerian Government treasury if nobody applies to claim this fund after a long period of time. I want you to co-operate with me so that the fruits of this man's labour will not get into the hands of some unsrupulous corrupt government officials if NOT CLAIMED now. I have secured from the probate an Order of Madamus to locate any of deceased beneficiaries. Hence I am contacting you with this proposal. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately the following below: 1.full names and address 2.Date of Birth 3.Tel & Fax Numbers So that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the next of kin. We shall employ the services of two Attorneys for drafting and notorization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favour for the transfer. The Bank cannot release the fund from his account unlesssomeone applies for claim as the next-of-kin to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines. I have almost resolved to finalize this transaction with some money to secure documents in your name as the bonafide beneficiary of this fund $25m which guarantees our safety and successful transfer. With the above suggestion, It is reliable,safe and quick for transfer process. At the successful conclusion of this business, your goodself shall be entitled to have 40% that is, USD$10m of the total money while I will have 55% that is USD$13.750m and 5% that is USD$1.250m for communications and other expenses. I am ready to invest a reasonable percentage of mine into any viable business you suggest as a joint partner. Your response is highly imperative as this is a TWO-man business deal transaction as I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. I need your assistance and co-operation to this reality as I have done my Home-work and fine tune the best way to create you as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the Attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction with you as the beneficiary to this fund. Your percentage will also be a source of upliftment.You have absolutely nothing to LOSE in assisting me instead, you have so much to GAIN. Be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us. I will appreciate your early reply for commencement of business.Contact me for acknowledgement by E-mail and whereby you are not interested, please indicate in your reply so that I can seek for the assistance of someone else. Thanks for your expected co-operation and treat ASAP as your utmost Trust,Honesty and Confidentiality will be highly appreciated in this business deal transaction. Thanks with great regards. Mr. Donald Ofu Obidima

Good day I know this mail might come to you as surprise but kindly allow me the opportunity of introducing myself. I am Ms. Aminata Bobi Kabila; daughter of the former head of state/president of Congo-Kinshasa (former Zaire), Mr. Laurent Desire Kabila. I got your particulars through the South African Chamber of Commerce; However, i am contacting you in order to ask for your assistance on this confidential business proposal with full financial benefit for both my family and you. Before i go into further details, please be informed that i am writing without any other perso(s) pre-knowledge of my contacting you on this transaction. Therefore i will appreciate same attitude to be maintained all through. I have the sum of USD8.5 Million from a secret sale of Diamond by my father before he was assassinated by one of his body guards (Rashid) on January 16th 2001. The essence of this mail is to ask you to stand as my foreign partner and receive the fund on my behalf as i can not do much on my own due to security reasons, my narration below will explain better. Before i continue, be well informed that your share in this transaction has been calculated at 30% of the total sum, 5% for expenses that may be incurred if any and the rest for my family and me. My father as an African traditionalist was a polygamist thereby having married so many wives, and my mother being the second wife of my father, my step-brother Joseph, who is the current president of my country, is the son of the first wife and he does not have any knowledge about this deal. Already president Joseph is using his power to colonise all the money and private property which our father left behind for the whole family. Now my mother, myself and my younger brother are left with nothing in the inheritance of my late father’s wealth. Our situation is seriously critical that we need your assistance to help us receive this fund for relocation overseas and for proper investment jointly between we and you. Let me quickly assure you the 100% safe proof of this transaction because the diamond sales are packaged from the onset in a pattern that shows no direct trace or linkage with us (Kabila family). At present the money is in cash and is secured in a security company as family treasures. I am waiting for your quick and favourable response, and in case you have any question(s), do not hesitate to contact me urgently. Thanks, Ms. Aminata B. Kabila.

FROM MY DESK,DR Gambo Abudul AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK (ADB). OUAGADOUGOU BURKINA FASO. WEST AFRICA. TRANSFER OF ($ 10,5) TEN. FIVE MILLION, DOLLARS. I AM DR GAmbo Abudul, THE AUDITOR GENERAL OF AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK OUAGADOUGOU BURKINA FASO. DURING THE COURSE OF OUR AUDITING, I DISCOVERED A FLOATING FUND IN AN ACCOUNT OPENED IN THE BANK BY MR EDWARD RIAD AND AFTER GOING THROUGH SOME OLD FILES IN THE RECORDS I DISCOVERED THAT THE OWNER OF THE ACCOUNT DIED IN THE (BEIRUT-BOUND CHARTER JET) PLANE CRASH ON THE 26TH DECEMBER 2003 IN COTONOU (REPUBLIC OF BENIN). HERE IS THE (http://www.cnn.com/2003/WORLD/africa/12/26/benin.crash ). AND NOBODY HAS OPERATED ON THIS ACCOUNT AGAIN,THE OWNER OF THIS ACCOUNT IS MR EDWARD RIAD A FOREIGNER FROM LEBANON, AND ALSO A TRADER WHOM TRADE ON GOLD AND MINING, HE DIED, SINCE 2003 AND NO OTHER PERSON KNOWS ABOUT THIS ACCOUNT OR ANYTHING CONCERNING IT, THE ACCOUNT HAS NO OTHER BENEFICIARY AND MY INVESTIGATION PROVED TO ME AS WELL THAT MR EDWARD RIAD DIED ALONG WITH HIS ENTIRE FAMILY. THE AMOUNT INVOLVED IS (USD 10.5 M) TEN.FIVE MILLION, UNITED STATES DOLLARS ONLY, I AM CONTACTING YOU AS A CONTERPART FOREIGNER NOT IN BURKINA FASO HERE,I BELIEVE YOU WILL ASSIT THIS TRANSACTION, BECAUSE THIS MONEY CAN NOT BE APPROVED TO A LOCAL PERSON HERE BURKINA FASO, BUT THE FUND CAN ONLY BE APPROVED TO ANY LEGITMATE FOREIGN NEXT OF KIN WITH VALID INTERNATIONAL PASSPORT OR DRIVERS LICENSE AND FOREIGN ACCOUNT, BECAUSE THE MONEY IS IN UNITED STATE DOLLARS AND THE FORMER OWNER OF THE ACCOUNT MR EDWARD RIAD IS A FOREIGNER FROM LEBANON TOO, AND THIS MONEY CAN ONLY BE APPROVED INTO A FOREIGN ACCOUNT, HAS THE BASIC STATUS OF THE DEPOSITED FUND. MY DEAR FRIEND, PLEASE I WILL NEED YOUR ASSISTANCE TO GET THIS MONEY OUT OF OUR BANK POSSESION BEFORE THE TIME IT REACHES DEMORRAGE AND IT GET CONFISTICATED BY OUR BANK . I NEED URGENT SUPPORT AND YOUR STRONG ASSURANCE THAT YOU WILL ASSIST AND NEVER,EVER CHEAT ME AS SOON AS THIS FUND REMMITS INTO YOUR ACCOUNT. WITH MY INFLUENCE AND MY POSITION IN THE BANK AS THE AUDITOR GENERAL, OF AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK OUAGADOUGOU,BURKINA FASO. WITHIN THE RULE OF THE BANKING FORMALITY, I ASSURE YOU THAT OUR A.D.B.BANK WILL TRANSFER THIS MONEY TO ANY FOREIGN OR ANY FOREIGNER'S RELIABLE ACCOUNT WHICH MUST BE PROVIDED AND PROVED. WHICH I WOULD LIKE YOU TO PROVIDE FOR THE FINAL REMMITTANCE FURNISHMENT OF THE MONEY TRANSFER OUT OF OUR BANK INTO YOUR NOMINATED ACCOUNT. AFTER THE COMPLEMENT VERIFICATION BY THE A.D.B.BANK OUAGADOUGOU BURKINA FASO, WHICH I MYSELF HAS BEEN GOING THROUGH EVER BEFORE I HAVE TO CONTACT YOU,HAS REACHED CONCLUSION, THE TRANSFER OF ($ 10,5) TEN. FIVE MILLION, DOLLARS WILL BE REMMITTED INTO YOUR NOMINATED ACCOUNT IN YOUR COUNTRY WHICH AFTER I WILL JOIN YOU IN YOUR COUNTRY. I WILL PROVIDE ALL DOCUMENTS OF THE BANK OFFICIAL(S) AND OF THE TRANSACTION IMMEDIATELY FOR YOU TO RECEIVE THIS FUND AND LEAVING NO TRACE TO ANYONE, PLACE OR WHATSOEVER AND FOR YOU TO BUILD A RELIABLE CONFIDENCE IN THIS TRANSACTION. I WANT YOU TO ASSURE ME, THAT THIS MONEY WILL BE INTACT, PENDING MY PHYSICAL ARRIVAL IN YOUR COUNTRY FOR THE FUND SHARING. ON THE CONCLUSION OF THIS TRANSACTION AS A PARTNER IN BUSINESS YOU WILL BE ENTITLED TO 40% OF THE TOTAL SUM AS GRATIFICATION, WHILE 10% WILL BE SET ASIDE TO TAKE CARE OF THE EXPENSES THAT WILL ARISE DURING THE TIME OF VERIFICATION AND TRANSFER AND ALSO TELEPHONE BILLS, WHILE 50% WILL BE FOR ME. THE MOST IMPORTANT INDICATION MY BELOVED FRIEND,I WOULD PLEAD THAT YOU MAKE THIS BUISNESS THE UPMOST SECRET,BECAUSE MY JOB IS AT STAKE IF I SHOULD BE DETECTED WITHIN THE BANK PREMISES THAT I AM INVOLVED,SO I WILL LIKE TO MAKE IT A SECRET AND PEACEFUL TRANSACTION.PLEASE COULD YOU ALSO ASSURE ME OF THE SECRECY.BECAUSE THIS TRANSACTION MEANS A LOT TO ME AND MY LIFE.IF YOU CAN PLEASE UNDERSTAND! SO ON THE INDICATION OF YOUR WILLINGNESS TO ASSIST AND JOIN ME IN THIS BUSINESS TO ARCHIVE THIS GREAT OPPURTUNITY,I WOULD WANT YOU TO FORWARD TO ME YOUR : FULL NAME: SEX: COMPANY: IF ANY FULL CONTACT ADDRESS: PHONE: CELL: FAX: CITY: STATE:ZIP CODE COUNTRY: OCCUPATION AND SO THAT ALL THE NECESSARY INFORMATION WILL BE SENT TO YOU ON THE ACCEPTANCE TO CHAMPION AND ARCHIVE THIS TRANSACTION WITH ME. N:B PLEASE YOU ARE ADVICE TO RESPONSE TO THE BOTH CONTACT BELOW/ HERE IS MY PRIVATE EMAIL ADDRESS : gambo_abudul2@myway.com THANKS, SINCERELY YOURS , DR Gambo Abudul. _________________________________________________________________ Testez Windows Live Mail Beta ! http://www.ideas.live.com/

DEAR FRIEND, I MAKE THIS APPEAL WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT ANY FACTS OR OPINION EXPRESSED BY ME ARE GIVING IN CONAFIDENCE AND SOLELY FOR YOUR PERSONAL NFORMATION AND USE. I AM DR. SAMI IBRAHIM ,THE MANAGER OF BILL AND EXCHANGE AT THE FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPARTMENT OF MY BANK. BEFORE I WROTE YOU, I PRAYED THAT YOU WILL BE A HONEST AND RELIABLE PERSON WHOM I CAN WORK WITH TO ACHIEVE THIS DEAL OF OUR LIFE.FROM MY SECTION IN THE BANK, I DISCOVERED AN ABANDONED SUM OF SIX MILLION EIGHT HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS ($6.8M) WITH ACCOUNT NUMBER 14-2558-5976 THAT BELONGS TO ONE OF OUR FOREIGN CUSTOMERS WHO DIED ALONG WITH HIS WIFE AND ONLY DAUGHTER IN A PLANE CRASH OF ALASKA AIRLINES FLIGHT NUMBER 261 WHICH CRASHED ON MONDAY, 31 JULY, 2000, 13:22 GMT 14:22 UK. WITH THE WHOLE PASSENGERS ABOARD. THE NAME OF THE DECEASED MAN WAS (MR. ANDREAS SCHRANNER FROM MUNICH,GERMANY). N.B.YOU SHALL READ MORE ABOUT THE CRASH ON VISITING THIS (WEBSITE) BEFORE YOU START WITH ME. BELOW IS THE WEBSITE. HTTP://NEWS.BBC.CO.UK/1/HI/WORLD/EUROPE/859479.STM IT IS THEREFORE UPON THIS DISCOVERY THAT I NOW DECIDED TO MAKE THIS BUSINESS PROPOSAL TO YOU AND FOR OUR BANK TO RELEASE THE MONEY TO YOU. YOU HAVE TO FOLLOW THE INSTRUCTION WHICH I WILL BE SEND TO YOU AS THE NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION TO THE DECEASED FOR SAFETY AND SUBSEQUENT DISBURSEMENT SINCE NOBODY IS COMING FOR IT AND I DON'T WANT THIS MONEY TO GO INTO OUR BANK TREASURY AS UNCLAIMED BILL. THE BANKING LAW AND GUIDELINES HERE STIPULATES THAT IF SUCH MONEY REMAINED UNCLAIMED AFTER SIX YEARS, THE MONEY WILL BE TRANSFERED INTO THE BANK TREASURY AS UNCLAIMED FUND. THE MONEY HAS NOW STAYED MORE THAN SIX YEARS AND I AM PREPARING DOCUMENTAION TO PROVE THAT THIS MONEY HAS BEEN TRANSFERED TO OUR BANK TREASURY. IT WILL BE BETWEEN ME AND YOU ONLY THAT WILL KNOW THAT THE MONEY IS NOT TRANSFERED INTO OUR TREASURE. THIS REQUEST OF FOREIGNER AS NEXT OF KIN IN THIS TRANSACTION IS OCCASIONED BY THE FACT THAT THE CUSTOMER WAS A FOREIGNER AND A BURKINABÉ CANNOT STAND AS NEXT OF KIN TO A FOREIGNER.IN APPRECIATION OF YOUR ASSISTANCE, I AM OFFERING YOU 35% OF THE TOTAL SUM. 5% FOR CONTINGENCIES (COST OF TRANSFER/OTHER CHARGES) LIKELY TO BE INCURRED DURING THE COURSE OF TRANSACTION, WHILE THE REMAINING 60% IS FOR ME.UPON RECEIPT OF YOUR REPLY.I WILL SEND TO YOU BY FAX OR EMAIL THE TEXT OF THE APPLICATION WHICH YOU WILL COMPLETE AND FORWARD TO OUR BANK ASKING FOR THIS MONEY TO BE PAID TO YOU AS THE NEXT OF KIN TO MR;ANDREAS SCHRANNER. PLEASE I WOULD LIKE YOU TO KNOW THE FOLLOWING INFORMATIONS.(1.) THIS BUSINESS IS HUNDRED PERCENT FREE FROM RISK.(2.)YOU WILL NOT FACE ANY MUCH QUESTIONS BECAUSE THE APPLICATION WILL BEAR THE BRIEF INFORMATION OF THE DECEASED WHICH THE BANK MAY LIKE TO KNOW.(3.) IF YOU WILL FOLLOW MY NSTRUCTIONS AND DIRECTIVES,THIS TRANSACTION WILL BE COMPLETED WITHIN A SHORT PERIOD OF TIME.(4.)YOU SHOULD KEEP THIS BUSINESS CONFIDENTIAL OR SECRET UNTIL THE FUND GET TRANSFERED INTO YOUR ACCOUNT FOR SAFETY AND SECURITY PURPOSE. FINALLY,CONTACT ME THROUGH MY EMAIL ADDRESS SO THAT WE WILL PROCEED WITH THIS BUSINESS IMMEDIATELY. MY REGARDS TO YOU AND YOUR FAMILY. YOURS FAITHFULLY, DR.SAMI IBRAHIM, _________________________________________________________________ Gagnez des pc Windows Vista avec Live.com http://www.image-addict.fr/

Dear Friend, As you read this, I don't want you to feel sorry for me, because, I believe everyone will die someday,and am contacting you because i really do need your help,and i want you to help me with all your effort and time for just seven to fourteen workings days of your time.I want you to be honest and truth full with me that you will help me with my last wish as a dying man. My name is Saeed Ahmed a merchant in Dubai, in the U.A.E. I have been diagnosed with Esophageal cancer.It has defiled all forms of medical treatment, and right now I have only about a few months to live,according to medical experts. I have not particularly lived my life so well, as I never really cared for anyone(not even myself)but my business. Though I am very rich, I was never generous,I was always hostile to people and only focused on my business as that was the only thing I cared for. But now I regret all this as I now know that there is more to life than just wanting to have or make all the money in the world. I believe when God gives me a second chance to come to this world I would live my life a different way from how I have lived it. Now that God has called me, I have willed and given most of my property and assets to my immediate and extended family members as well as a few close friends. I want God to be merciful to me and accept my soul so, I have decided to give also to charity organizations, as I want this to be one of the last good deeds I do on earth. So far, I have distributed money to some charity organizations in the U.A.E, Algeria and Malaysia. Now that my health has deteriorated so badly, I cannot do this myself anymore. I once asked members of my family to close one of my accounts and distribute the money which I have there to charity organization in Bulgaria and Pakistan,they refused and kept the money to themselves. Hence, I do not trust them anymore, as they seem not to be contended with what I have left for them. The last of my money which no one knows of is the huge cash deposit of Eighteen Million Dollars $18,000,000,00 in side two boxes that I have with a Finance/Security Company Abroad. I will want you to Act as my Beneficiary who will help me contact the security finance company on my behalf to discuss the terms and condition of getting this deposit out from thier custody and also helping me to dispatch it to the charity organisations. Reply to this email with your full names,contact address,tel number and fax to enable me ask my doctors lawyer to arrange for you a power of attorney that will give you full legal backing as my beneficiary. I have set aside 30% for you and for your time. Please kindly reply to my most confidential email if you are really interested in helping me please: saeedahmed631@yahoo.com oo.comGod be with you. Saeed Ahmed

My Dear, I am Mrs Aicha Ahmed, the manager of bill and exchange at the foreign remittance department Bank Of Africa. In my department we discoveredan abandoned sum of US$14.5M (fourteen million five hundred thousand US dollars) in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customer who died along with his family in the 2003 in a plane crash. Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless some body applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guide lines and laws but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behindfor the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I now decided to make this business proposal to you and release the money to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we don't want this money to go into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. The banking law and guidelines here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed after four years, the money will be transferred into the bank treasury as unclaimed fund. The request of foreigner as next of kin in this business is occasioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a Burkina cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. I agree that 45% of this money will be for you as respect to the provision of a foreign account , 5% will be set aside for expenses incurred during the business and 50% be for me. Thereafter, I will visit your country fordisbursement according to the percentage indicated. Therefore, to enable the immediate transfer of this fund to you as arranged, you must apply first to the bank as relation or next of kin of the deceased indicating your bank name, your bank account number, your private telephone and fax number for easy and effective communication and location where the money will be transfer. Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or email the text of the application. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch-free and that you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made for the transfer. You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this mail,Trusting to hear from you immediately. Yours faithfully. Mrs Aicha Ahmed. N/B: CALL ME AS SOON AS YOU RECEIVE THIS MAIL OR EMAIL Me. TEL:0022676743842. _________________________________________________________________ MSN Messenger : discutez en direct avec vos amis ! http://www.msn.fr/msger/default.asp

St.Thomas' Hospital, Lambeth Palace Road London SE1 7EH United-Kingdom. Tel: 447035900075. Dear Friend In Christ, I believe you will treat this mail with the fear of God. It is with tears that I am writing you this mail; I don`t need your pity, but love to my son. My mail may seem very painful and sorrowful, but there is more you can do in my request than to pity me, which is to show LOVE to my son. I was an orphan and do not wish my son to experience what i have been through on Earth after an automobile crash that nearly claimed my life. My name is Edward Brown, married to the late Juan J.Brown, who died with our two daughters in Indonesia on 26th of December 2004 during the Tsunami Disaster, after this Painful and sorrowful incident, my condition worsened and I was diagnosed of cancer, which got worst and I have been suffering from heart failure and hepatitis since. My friends ignored me due to my relationship with God on sickbed. My wife, our children and I have been in United Kingdom for a long time. We all were suppose to travel to Indonesia in December 2004, but my bad health, did not permit me to travel with them, which made me and my son stay behind while my wife and our two daughters traveled. If not, all of us would have perished in the disaster. My reason of writing you this mail is due to the sad news that came to me recently from the doctors. After my last diagnosed result, it was proved by the doctors that i may not leave for more than one month ahead, due to the damage the cancer have caused in my system unless I undergo an urgent surgical operation which my chance of survival is less than 10% according to the medical experts. As it stands, I have given to fate and have found God on sick bed. But i have a more concern problem, which is why I have contacted you. Please, this is about my son. Since it is now obvious that i will die, my son's future has been the greatest problem i have. I want you to take care of my son please. He is only 13years and we have no person here to take care of him if I die today. My friends for knowing God deserted me. I left some money in a deposit house at United Kingdom, which i intended to use for investment in Indonesia. I want you to take this money and my son. Use the money into a big investment, that you will manage until my son grows up to take over the investment. I will like you to take my son as your own son, give him the love we the parents would have given him. Do not let him feel the pains of being an orphan, give him good education, bring him up into a responsible man. Make him have the fear of God. Please do not refuse this task. I have no one else to help me out on this issue, I am an orphan who grew up without knowing God rather focused on wealth and otherwise, living a life of fantasy and doesn't care or know who God is. Do not pity me, rather take good care of and bring him up to be God fearing. As soon as I receive your reply including your personal details, all i will do is to authorize my bank to transfer the money to your account directly and i will also draw up my will in your favor. I will give the bank all the documents that is covering the deposit with the bank, i will transfer every power and right of ownership to you stating at my Will to enable you claim the deposit from the bank. It will be also included in the Will that you are the only person my son should be released to, if i die. All i need is your acceptance and assurance that you will not treat my son badly. I am writing you this mail with great tears and i pray you will be kind & honest with fear of God concerning this mail to you today. Please reply this mail immediately if you have the love and care of God at: help.ed_brown@yahoo.co.uk Thank you. Mr. Edward Brown +447045700928.

From: Mr Lami Kallon Investment assistance in your country. Attn Pls, How are you and the daily activities including your family? I hope everybody is fine. Before I proceed, may I humbly introduce myself to your good self, I am Mr Lami Kallon a citizen of sierra Leone in west Africa and son of the late minister of works who was killed as a result of the notable role he played during the current civil war going on in my country Sierra Leone. I got your contact through a reliable source regarding your trust worthyness, as such; I decided to ask for your assistance in this transaction that will remain secret and confidential at this stage. Before the death of my father, while he was on sick bed he confided in me and revealed to me about the money he deposited in a Security Company in Ghana; the sum of $25 million (Twenty five million USD) in the certificate of deposit I was made the next of kin. But since his death I am living in Accra, Ghana as a refugee. My late father earlier instructed me not to invest the money in Africa as a whole because of the unstable political and economic situation in Africa that I should look for trusted foreigner to be my foreign partner and beneficiary so that the fund will be invested in his/her country. I want you to stand as my foreign partner so that both of us can invest the fund together in your country. Please send me your private phone and fax number, as soon as you receive this mail, this will enable me send you the document relating to the deposit and the modality on how the fund will be transfer to you in your country. For your assistance you will be entitling to 10% of the total amount, while 5% will be set aside for all the expense you incurred during the process of the transaction. As soon as this is done, you have to prepare for concrete arrangement that will enable me join you in your country for the investment. Try as much as possible to keep this transaction secret and confidential at this stage. Thanks in anticipation for your kindly assistance. This is the number you will use to reach me.+233 27 619 8662 Best regard, Mr Kallon _________________________________________________________________ Don't just search. Find. Check out the new MSN Search! http://search.msn.com/

Content-Type: text/html Content-Transfer-Encoding: 8bit ATTENTION, SIR, I AM OF THE VIEW THAT YOU WILL BE OF TREMENDEOUS VALUE, ASSISTANCE, CONSENTING/ AGREEING TO BAIL ME AND ALSO, HELP ME SECURE A GREAT FORETUNE (MONEY) WHICH MY PARENTS ACQUIRED OVER PERIOD OF YEARS OF HARDWORK. I HAVE NO FAINTST DOUBT IN MIND THAT YOU WILL NOT ASSIST ME THIS DIFFICULT AND CRYING TIME. TO BE CANDID, I AM VANDE, THE SON OF THE LATE COTE'D HOLBORG HEAD OF STATE, GENERAL , MY PARENTS WERE KILLED IN THE HANDS OF REBELS LAST YEAR 2002 CIVIL WAR IN THE COUNTRY, WHICH STILL RAGES. I AND OTHER OF OUR SIBILINGS WERE FORTUNATE TO HAVE SURVIVED THE WAR, THANKS WITH THE ASSISTANCE OF FRENCH TROOPS EVACUATED US TO NIGERIA WHERE WE ARE ON TEMPORARY ASSYLUM, WITH THE SHOCK, KILLINGS, WITCH-HUNTING OF FAMILY MENBERS BY THE CIVILLIAN GOVERNMENT MAKES IT UNSAFE TO RETURN BACK. DURING MY FATHER'S REGIME AS HEAD OF STATE OF COTE'D IVORE, HE AMAZED GREAT WEALTH/FORTUNES TO THE TUNE OF EURO 10 MILLION (TWENTY MILLION EUROS ) WHICH HE PERSONALLY CONCEALED IN A DIPLOMATIC CASE AWAITING TO BE TRANSFERED TO A FOREIGN ACCOUNT IN EUROPE. BUT THE REBELS CAUGHTUP WITH HIM AND DIED WITHOUT TRANSFERING THE MONEY. I METICOUSLY CARRIED THE 10 MILLION EURO IN THE DIPLOMATIC CASE DOWN TO IRELAND, DEPOSITED THE MONEY WITH A SECURITY FIRM . I WAS ARRESTED AFTER 1 MONTH IN IRELAND , I'M NOT GUILTY , THERE WAS A MISSUNDERSTANDING , TO GET OUT OF JAIL I NEED 2200 EUROS TO PAY HERE. ALL I NEED FROM YOU IS TO HELP ME GET OUT OF JAYL AND I SWEAR TO GOD I WILL SEND YOU 2 MILION EUROS , I HAVE NOBADY TO HELP ME , IF YOU DONT HELP ME I WILL STAY HERE FOR 9 MORE YEARS , PLEASE HELP , YOU WILL GET YOUR MONEY . IF YOU WANT TO HELP ME YOU CAN E-MAIL ME TO : vanderstrongheart1982@yahoo.com I WILL OFFER YOU 2 MILION EUROS FOR YOUR PARTICIPATION I AM AWAITING STRONG RESPONSE AND WHEN GOD WILL PERMIT US TO MEET FACE TO FACE. I ANTICIPATE YOUR CO-OPERATION. REGARDS, VANDER

>From : Mrs. Shade lbrahim Chiang Rai, Thailand Request for assistance from Mrs. Shade lbrahim Dear sir, Compliment of the day, I decided to unfold our investment plan to you after going through your profile from your country trade jounal of which I was convince as to solicite for your assistance and help but before I proceed I will like to introduce myself to you for your refrence,, I am Mrs.Shade lbrahim the Wife of late Dr. Al-bahadili lbrahim from Trikit in northern, Iraq, ,My late husband was the former Director General of North Oil Company Ltd ( NOC ) www.noc-iraq.com located in ( KIRKUK ) northern city of Iraq during Sadam Hussain regime before the United State invassion of Iraq, He was captured and assasinated recently by shiite militants led by Moqtada Al-Sadr in the recent secterian killing that is going on in Iraq between Majority Shiites and Minority Sunis, Before his death he was able to confirm to us of an existence deposit of US$11,000,000.00 ( Eleven Million US DOLLARS ) which he secretly deposited cash in oversea Depository and finance security vault as a consignment through a diplonatic personel in Thailand for safekeeping . Presently I am Temporary living a political exile life here in Chiang Rai, Thailand therefor being under the protection of the United Nation High Commission on Refugee because our life in Iraq are no more gurranteed by the recent Iraq government due to daily killing of all top Suni important personalites, former government officers and their families ,Under this circumstances we have just decided to invest this fund in a profitable venture but being that we have no idea into any business before this time , Already my son Mr. Adamu have just arrived Bangkok, Thailand in respect of claiming the fund as the next of kin and we have just finalize every process with the security vault management along with the diplomatic personel on retreiving of the fund from the security vault custody but under our current status as a political refugee we are limited from handling such huge amount of cash as we can not operate a personal bank account of our own as a political refugee. For the above reason I decided to ask for an assistance and help from you as a foreign partner to enable us reach a long term investment partnership agreement under joint venture partnership to transfer this fund to your bank account in your country for investment purpose. 1 .I will offer 20% of the total fund as a reward for your assistance toward your help in transfering the fund to your bank account in your country for investment purpose. 2. I will map out 5% of the total fund to meet up any expences made during the transaction. 3. To reach a long term investment partnership agreement to entrust the Investment in your management and control for the benefit of both parties Kindly regard my contact to you through email as an althernative for the security of the transaction. For further information and procedure I will be expecting your immediate reply as soon as poosble as this will give us the upportunity to conclude all further arrangement on meeting each other and transfering of the fund to your bank in your country. thanks for your co-operation and hoping to see a good family relationship with you. Yours sincerely, Mrs Shade lbrahim,lbrahim's family.

FROM THE DESK OF MR.AHMED HASSANA THE SENIOR AUDITOR INCHARGE FORIEGN REMITTANCE UNIT, BANK OF AFRICA (BOA). OUAGADOUGOU BURKINA FASO. DEAR FRIEND, I PRESUMED THAT ALL IS WELL WITH YOU AND YOUR FAMILY.PLEASE LET THIS NOT BE A SURPRISED MESSAGE TO YOU BECAUSE I GOT YOUR CONTACT INFORMATION FROM THE INTERNATIONAL DIRECTORY FEW WEEKS AGO BEFORE I DECIDED TO CONTACT YOU ON THIS MAGNITUDE AND LUCRATIVE TRANSACTION FOR OUR PRESENT AND FUTURE SURVIVAL IN LIFE. MOREOVER,I HAVE LAID ALL THE SOLEMN TRUST IN YOU BEFORE I DECIDED TO DISCLOSE THIS SUCCSSFUL AND CONFIDENTIAL TRANSACTION TO YOU. I AM THE SENIOR AUDITOR INCHARGE OF FORIEGN REMITTANCE UNIT OF OUR BANK AND I DECIDED TO CONTACT YOU FOR THIS FINANCIAL TRANSACTION WORTH FOURTEEN MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND US DOLLARS (14.5M) FOR OUR PRESENT AND FUTURE SUCCESS. THIS IS AN ABANDONED FUND THAT BELONGS TO ONE OF OUR BANK FORIEGN CUSTOMERS WHO DIED ALONG WITH HIS ENTIRE FAMILY THROUGH PLANE CRASH FEW YEARS AGO. MEANWHILE,I WAS VERY FORTUNATE TO COME ACCROSS THE DECEASED FILE WHEN I WAS ARRANGING THE OLD AND ABANDONED CUSTOMERS FILE IN OTHER TO SIGN AND SUBMIT TO THE ENTIRE BANK MANAGEMENT FOR AN OFFICIAL RE DOCUMENTATION AND AUDIT OF THE YEAR AGAINST 2006. INFORMED CLEARLY THAT IT WAS STATED IN OUR FORIEGN BANKING RULES AND REGULATIONS WHICH WAS SIGNED LAWFULLY THAT IF SUCH FUND REMAINS UNCLAIMED TILL THE PERIOD OF FOUR YEARS STARTED FROM THE DATE THE BENEFICIARY DIED, THE MONEY WILL BE TRANSFERRED INTO THE TREASURY AS UNCLAIMED FUNDHOWEVER, IT IS NOT AUTHORIZES BY THE RULES GUIDING OUR BANK FOR A CITIZEN OF BURKINA FASO TO MAKE THE CLAIM OF THE FUND UNLESS YOU ARE A FORIEGNER NO MATTER THE COUNTRY. SO THE REQUEST OF YOU AS A FORIEGNER IS NECESSARY TO APPLY FOR THE CLAIM AND TRANSFER OF THE FUND SMOOTHLY INTO YOUR RELIABLE BANK ACCOUNT AS THE NEXT OF KIN TO THE DECEASED.WHEN THE FUND IS TRANSFERRED INTO YOUR ACCOUNT 35% WILL BE FOR YOU IN RESPECT OF ALL YOUR ASSISTANCE FOR THE TRANSFER OF THE FUND INTO YOUR ACCOUNT AND PROVISION OF THE BANK ACCOUNT WHERE THE BANK WILL REMIT THE FUND, 60% WILL BE FOR ME BEING THE PIONEER OF THE BUSINESS WHILE THE REST 5% WILL BE SHARED TO RESPECTABLE ORGANISATIONS SUCH AS CHARITY AND THE DESTITUDES HOMES ARROUND US IN THE WORLD. IF YOU ARE REALLY SURE OF YOUR TRUSTWORTHINESS,ACCOUNTABILITY AND CONFIDENTIALITY ON THIS TRANSACTION, CONTACT ME AND ACCEPT NOT TO CHANGE YOUR MIND TO CHEAT OR DISAPPOINT ME WHEN THE FUND IS TRANSFERRED INTO YOUR ACCOUNT.SO REPLY FOR THE ASSURANCE WITH YOUR TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBERS TO FACILITATE EASY COMMUNICATION. AS SOON AS YOU REPLY, YOU NOTIFY ME SO THAT I WILL LET YOU KNOW THE NEXT STEP AND PROCEDURE TO FOLLOW IN ORDER TO FINALIZE THIS TRANSACTION SUCCESSFULLY. I EXPECT YOUR URGENT COMMUNICATION. YOURS SINCERELY, MR AHMED HASSANA _________________________________________________________________ MSN Messenger : appels gratuits de PC à PC ! http://www.msn.fr/newhotmail/Default.asp?Ath=f

TICKET NUMBER: 0362728 LOTTO NL. INTERNATIONAL PROMOTIONS/PRIZE AWARD DEPARTMENT RESULTS FOR CATEGORY "A" DRAWS Sir/Madam, Congratulations to you as we bring to your notice, the results of the Second Category draws of THE LOTT NL.PROMO INT. We are happy to inform you that you have emerged as a winner under the First Category, which is part of our promotional draws. The results of the draws have been officially announced .Participants were selected through a computer ballot system drawn from 2,500,000 email addresses of individuals and companies from Africa, America, Asia, Australia, Europe, Middle East, and Oceania as part of our International Promotions Program. Your email address, attached to ticket number 0362728,with serial number 990-4289 and lucky number P-065377-H?22/a7 consequently won in the First Category. You have therefore been awarded a lump sum pay out of 1,500,000 (One Million Five Hundred Thousand Euros), which is the winning payout for Category A winners. This is from a total cash prize of 15,000,000.00 (Fifteen Million Euros) shared amongst the first Ten (10) lucky winners in this category. In your best interest to avoid mix up of numbers and names of any kind, we request that you keep the entire details of your award strictly from public notice until the process of transferring your claims has been completed, and your funds remitted to your account. This is part of our security protocol to avoid double claiming or unscrupulous acts by participants/no participants of this program. Please contact our paying bank immediately for due processing and remittance of your prize money to a designated account of your choice: NOTE: For easy reference and identification, find below your Reference and Batch numbers. Remember to quote these numbers in your correspondence with your paying bank. Also give them the following information. NAME TELEPHONE NUMBER AND FAX AGE ADDRESS OCUPATION Number: NM/BC921245/KY14 BATCH No: NM/207161/WOP. CONGRATULATIONS!!! Your fund is now deposited with the paying Bank. To begin your claims, kindly contact the paying bank with the below information: *********************************************** Union Credit Bank Contact person: Mr. Jan Van Dijk International Remittance Officer E-mail: unioczones@aim.com Tel: +31 614 990 140 Fax: +31 847 570 900 *********************************************** NOTE: All claims are nullified after 10 working days from today if unclaimed Congratulations once again from all our staffs, and thank you for being part of our promotions program. Yours Sincerely, Mrs. Tonia Van Smith Online co-Coordinator

PLEASE HELP ME Dear Friend,

You may be surprised to receive this letter, I got your contact through a desperate and personal search on the web for someone I could really trust as I have prayed over it and I wish to express my interest to handle this matter with you.

Let me introduce myself to you before I go further; I am Mr. mark Abdul the son of late Mr. Abdul Kosoko who was recently murdered in the land dispute in Zimbabwe. I wouldn't go much deep detailing the problem I am having in my own country Zimbabwe, but you can have a look on This web-site;http://www.rte.ie/news/2000/0418/zimbabwe. html, if you have the time you will understand the kind of brutal president we have.

Before the sudden death of my father, he foresees the looming danger in Zimbabwe and decided to make a deposit SUM OF$30 MILLION UNITED STATE DOLLARS(THIRTY MILLION US DOLLARS)in disguise as consignment in a box with a Security Company in European  . And he was forced to disclose this to me alone as his first son. And with faith, I am going to disclose the details to you,  hoping that you will understand me and keep the secret to yourself, and most importantly to stand as the beneficiary to this fund, so that non of my country people we have any reason to track this money back.

This money was deposited as family valuables due to the heat of the problem in Zimbabwe , so that the government will not try to confiscate the money if discovered. This amount was meant for the purchase of new machines and chemicals for the farms and also for the establishment of a new farm in Swaziland . The land disputes started when Zimbabwean President "MR. ROBERT MUGABE" introduced a new Land Act reform which wholly affected the rich white farmers and some few black farmers. This resulted to many killings by Zimbabwe war veterans and some lunatics in the society. In fact, a lot of people were killed because of this land reformed Act for which my Father was one of the victims. And because of this development I flew to Dubai to stay as a refugee.

From the studies I have been able to make in Dubai concerning the right of a refugee, a lot of question will arise if I make any attempt to claim this fund directly concerning my age. And for the fact that I will not like to stay permanently in Dubai due to there law of not issuing permanent resident to foreigners. I am looking forward to stay in a country that the law will give me full right with time. And to have a good guardian that is knowledgeable in business and investment. It is just on this background that I have contacted you.

Please, I need your assistance to transfer this fund to your trusted overseas bank account as soon as it is being claim from the Security Company. For your efforts and assistance, I have agreed to give you 30% of the total sum, while 10% is mapped out to re-in-burse all the expenses incurred in the course of this transaction and 60% will be for me and my family investment in your country under your kind control.

Note that this transaction is 100% clear and risk-free, as I have made every necessary arrangement for a successful deal base on the little advice my let father gave to me. The only thing am soliciting from you is the total assistance to make a claim of the fund on your name from the Security Company, and after which the money will be paid into your account in your country

I need your complete trust and assurance that my own part of money will be safe when transferred to your account. Kindly keep this business proposal highly confidential for security reasons. If you are interested in assisting me, Reply via the above email address and include your private phone and fax numbers. I will respond to you immediately. Looking forward to your urgent reply, God Bless.

Sincerely Yours, Mr. mark Abdul

Ahora también puedes acceder a tu correo Terra desde el móvil. Infórmate pinchando aquí.

Fred Gabby Senior Branch Manager, Citizens Bank Int'l Plc 119, Adeola Odeku, Victoria Island, Lagos Nigeria Office:00234-1-4769870 Mobile: 00234-8023605271 Dear Respectable One, REQUEST FOR A NEXT OF KIN BENEFICIARY - HIGHLY CONFIDENTIAL My special greetings to you and your entire family. I am Fred Gabby, recently promoted to the office of a Senior Branch Manager with Citizens Int'l Bank Plc. Late Engr. (Allan ), a National of your country, who is a contractor with the DEPARTMENT OF PETROLEUM RESOURCES VICTORIA ISLAND, LAGOS. Here in after shall be referred to as my client On 30 JAN 2000, my client,his wife, and their three children were involved in the Kenya airways flight with registration number 5Y-BEN which departed from Nairobi to destination Lagos and all family died in this fatal air crash on 30 JAN 2000, Since then I have made several inquiries to your embassy to locate any of my clients extended Relatives, this has proved abortive. After all these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to get in touch with the consul-General to locate any member of his family hence I contacted you. I have contacted you to assist in repatriating the money and property left behind by my client before they get confiscated or declared unserviceable by the bank where these huge deposits were lodged, particularly the CITIZENS INT'L BANK PLC Where the deceased had an account Valued at about ($15 Million United States Dollars) The Head Office has issued me a notice to provide the next of kin Or have the account confiscated within the next ten official working days. Since I have been unsuccessful in locating the relatives for over 5 years now, I seek your consent to present you as the next of kin of the deceased since you have the same last name so that the proceeds of this account valued at ($15 Million US Dollars) can be paid to you and then you and me Can share the money 50% to me and 50% to you and all expenses will be shared equal and this will be after tax is deducted by the (IRS) in your country. An attorney will be contracted to help us revalidate and notarize all the necessary legal documents that can be used to back up any claim we may make. All I require is your honest cooperation to enable us see this deal through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you and me from any breach of the law. Note, I recommend that you send your response together with your most private telephone number to enable me call you for more explanation if the need arises. Thank you. Faithfully yours in Christ, Fred Gabby. --------------------- ALICE SECURITE ENFANTS --------------------- Protégez vos enfants des dangers d'Internet en installant Sécurité Enfants, le contrôle parental d'Alice. http://www.aliceadsl.fr/securitepc/default_copa.asp

Content-Type: text/plain Message-Id: <20070314045652.B8006558023@cw03.calibra-web.de.calibra-web.de> Date: Wed, 14 Mar 2007 05:56:52 +0100 (CET) Content-Transfer-Encoding: quoted-printable =0D Dear friend, =0D =0D I apollogize in advance if this mail comes as an embarrassment because of= so many things that happens in our times. I am Isaac Baka, the site insp= ection director with the ministry ofworks and construction and I worked d= irectly with the Minister in charge of the Ministry here in Republic of S= udan.=0D =0D I awarded a contract to a firm worth several millions of dollars a few ye= ars ago. In the course of executing the project the firm discovered large= gold deposit in one of the construction sites. Being the site director I= collaborated with the firm in the mining of the gold on a mutual agreeme= nt to share the proceeds out of which I got a share of 7.5 Million. =0D =0D As a civil servant in this small war torn country, I cannot introduce thi= s funds into the banking system here considering my meager monthly income= as well as the code of conduct guidelines regulating civil service here = in my country, Sudan. Presently Sudan is engulfed in a civil crisis and a= s this crisis intensified by the day, I have decided to move this fund ou= t for any profitable venture. The fund will be moved out of Sudan under d= iplomatic cover as soon as we conclude all procedure.=0D =0D I therefore solicit for your co-operation to take delivery of this fund i= nto your custody for any profitable investment that will be mutually bene= ficial. I will be able to arrange all necessary procedures to ensure smoo= th movement of this funds until you are in control of it. =0D =0D Please let me know if you are interested by return mail to be sent to: (i= sbaka@myway.com, isbaka@sify.com). Also include your full names and conta= ct telephone number to enable me call you. I will provide you with more i= nformation as soon as you indicate appreciable interest to deal. =0D =0D Regards,=0D ISAAC BAKA.=0D

DEAR FRIEND, I am Mr.Joseph Poon Executive Director Of Operations of the Hang Seng Bank Ltd,Sai Wan Ho Branch,171 Shaukiwan Road Hong Kong. An Iraqi named Hamadi Hashem a business man made a numbered fixed deposit of (346,736,899.68 HKD) for 18 calendar months; this is valued to Forty Four million Five Hundred Thousand United State Dollars only in my branch. Upon maturity several notices was sent to him, even during the war,four years ago (2003). Again after the war another notification was sent and still no response came from him. We later found out that Hamadi Hashem and his family had been killed during the war in bomb blast that hit their home at Mukaradeeb where his personal oil well was. After furtherinvestigation it was also discovered that Hamadi Hashem did not declare any next of kin in his official papers including the paperwork of his bank deposit. And he also confided in me the last time he was at my office that no one except me knew of his deposit in my bank.So, Forty Four million Five Hundred Thousand United State Dollars is still lying in my bank and no one will ever come forward to claim it.What bothers me most is that according to the laws of my country at the expiration five years six months the funds will revert to the ownership of the Hong Kong Government if no body applies to claim the funds. My proposal, I am prepared to place you as the next of kin in a position to instruct HANG SENG BANK to release the deposit to you as the closest surviving relation. Upon receipt of the deposit, I am prepared to share the money with you in half. That is: I will simply nominate you as the next of kin and have them release the deposit to you. We share the proceeds FIFTY - FIFTY. I would have gone ahead to ask the funds be released to me, but that would have drawn a straight line in my involvement in claiming the deposit. I assure you that I could have the deposit released to you within a few days.I will simply inform the bank of the final closing of the file relating to Hamadi Hashem I will then officially communicate with my Bank and instruct them to release the deposit to you. With these:all is done. I am aware of the consequences of this proposal. I ask that if you find no interest in this project that you should discard this mail. I ask that you do not be vindictive and destructive. If my offer is of no appeal to you, delete this message and forget I ever contacted you. Do not destroy my career because you do not approve of my proposal. Should you be interested please send me your full names,Phone Number and current residential address and I will prefer you to reach me on the email address below.E-mail: josephpoon_enquiries@yahoo.com.hk and finally after that I shall provide you with more details of this operation. Your earliest response to this letter will be appreciated. I await your response. Mr.JOSEPH POON.

Attn:

URGENT BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP

I am Mr.Roland Bartic Director, project implementation with (LOC) (LOCAL ORGANIZING COMMITTEE FOR 2010 FIFA WORLD CUP IN SOUTH AFRICA) and a member of the Contract Tenders Board (CTB) of the above Committee.

Your esteemed address was reliably introduced to me at the South Africa Chamber of Commerce and Industry in my search for a reliable individual company who can handle a strictly confidential transaction, which involves the transfer of a reasonable sum of money to a foreign account.

This amount of money is total sum ofUS$13,500,000.00 (Thirteen Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars), already extracted from various contracts awarded by my Committee. As a result of over invoicing masterminded by the concerned officials, has been drafted to represent final payment for a contract that has been executed to the Committee last years back. The money is now floating in the suspense account of Federal Reserve Bank of South Africa awaiting claim by Foreign Partner which status we now want you to assume.

Now is the optimum period to consummate this transaction. Following the presidential directive to all parastatals to settle all outstanding debts owed to both local and foreign contractors. In my last meeting with the officials involved, it was unanimously agreed that 35% of the total sum will be given to you. 60% will be for my colleague, and me.While 5% will he used to reimburse the expenses that may be incurred in the processing of the transfer.

I assure you the transaction is 100% risk free as we have concluded every arrangement to protect the interest of every one involved. Likewise, all modalities for the successful transfer of this money have been worked out with the Federal Ministry of Finance and the Federal Reserve Bank of South Africa to facilitate the remittance of this money to your designated account.

However. I would want to believe that you are honest enough and will not raise any misgiving attitude in any aspect of the transaction, more importantly, you will keep this transaction very confidential so as not to tarnish the confidence reposed on these officials by the Government of South Africa.

lf this business proposal is of interest to you, then kindly contact me via telephone or email.

Meanwhile, your immediate response will be highly appreciated. Please treat this information as confidential.

Best regards,

Mr.Roland Bartic

Hello Dear, This mail might come to you as a surprise and the temptation to ignore it as unserious could come into your mind but please consider it a divine wish and accept it with a deep sense of humility. I am Mr. Usman Sankara, the manager in charge of Auditing department of Bank of Africa (B.O.A)Ouagadougou Burkina Faso in West Africa, with due respect and Regard, I have decided to contact you on a business transaction that will be very beneficial to both of us at the end of the transaction. During our investigation and auditing in this Bank, my department came across a very huge sum of money belonging to one of our deceased customer who died on July 30th 2002 of a ghastly motor accident and the fund has been dormant in his account with this bank without any claim of the fund in our Custody either from his family or relation before our discovery to this development. Although personally, I keep this information secret to enable the whole plans and idea be Profitable and successful during the time of execution, the said amount is Fifteen million three hundred thousand United States dollars(US$15.3m), as it may interest you to know, I got your impressive information on my search for a reliable partner, I contacted you to be my partner and person to be reliable and capable to champion a business of such magnitude without any problem. Meanwhile all the arrangement to put claim over this fund as the next of kin to the deceased, get the required approval and transfer this money to a foreign account has been put in Place and directives and needed information will be relayed to you as soon as you indicate your interest and willingness to assist me and also benefit your self to this great business opportunity, In fact I could have done this deal alone but because of my position in this country as a civil servant and we are not allowed to operate a foreign account and would eventually raise eye brow on my side during the time of transfer because I work in this bank. This is the actual reason why it will require a second party or fellow who will forward claims as the next of kin with affidavit of trust of oath to the bank and also present a foreign account where he will need the money to be re-transferred into on his request as it may be after due verification and clarification by the correspondent branch of the bank where the whole money will be remitted from to your own designation bank account. I will not fail to inform you that this transaction is 100% risk free, on smooth conclusion of this transaction, you will be entitled to 30% of the total sum as gratification, while 5% will be set aside to take care of expenses that may arise during the time of transfer, while 65% will be for me, please you have been advised to keep "Top Secret" as I am still in service and intend to retire from service after we conclude this deal with you. I will be monitoring the whole situation here in this bank Until you confirm the money in your account, and ask us to come down to your country for subsequent sharing of the fund according to percentages previously indicated and further Investment, either in your country or any country you advice us to invest in and all other necessary vital information will be send to you when I hear from you. I suggest you get back to me As soon as possible and also include your personal phone/mobile and fax numbers for easy communication. Yours faithfully, Mr. Usman Sankara The manager in charge of Auditing department of Bank of Africa (B.O.A) Ouagadougou Burkina Faso. _________________________________________________________________ Gagnez des écrans plats avec Live.com http://www.image-addict.fr/

TREAT AS URGENT PROFITABLE TRANSACTION DR.AZEM USMAN {MANAGER} DEAR FRIEND, FIRST I MUST SOLICIT YOUR CONFIDENCE IN THIS TRANSACTION, THIS IS BY VIRTUE OF ITS NATURE AS BEING UTTERLY CONFIDENTIAL AND TOP SECRET. THOUGH I KNOW THAT A TRANSACTION OF THIS MAGNITUDE WILL MAKE ANY ONE APPREHENSIVE AND WORRIED, BUT I AM ASSURING YOU THAT ALL WILL BE WELL AT THE END OF THE DAY. WE HAVE DECIDED TO CONTACT YOU DUE TO THE URGENCY OF THIS TRANSACTION, AS WE HAVE BEEN RELIABLY INFORMED OF YOUR DISCREETNESS AND ABILITY IN TRANSACTION OF THIS NATURE. LET ME START BY INTRODUCING MYSELF PROPERLY TO YOU. I AM AZEM USMAN THE MANAGER WITH THE BANK OF AFRICA , OUAGA.I CAME TO KNOW YOU IN MY PRIVATE SEARCH FOR A RELIABLE AND REPUTABLE PERSON TO HANDLE THIS CONFIDENTIAL TRANSACTION, WHICH INVOLVES THE TRANSFER OF HUGE SUM OF MONEY TO A FOREIGN ACCOUNT REQUIRING MAXIMUM CONFIDENCE. THE PROPOSITION: A FOREIGNER AN AUSTRALIA, LATE ENGR. STEVE MOORE (SNR.) AN BUESSINE MERCHANT WITH THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT OF BURKINA, UNTIL HIS DEATH YEARS AGO IN KENYA AIR BUS (A310-! 301) FLIGHT KQ431, BANKED WITH US AT BANK OF BURKINA , OUAGA AND HAD A CLOSING BALANCE AS AT THE END OF SEPTEMBER, 2000 WORTH US$30,000,000.00 (THIRTY MILLION UNITED STATE DOLLARS), THE BANK NOW EXPECTS A NEXT OF KIN AS BENEFICIARY. VALUABLE EFFORTS ARE BEING MADE BY THE BANK OF AFRICAN TO GET IN TOUCH WITH ANY OF THE MOORE'S FAMILY OR RELATIVES BUT TO NO SUCCESS. IT IS BECAUSE OF THE PERCEIVED POSSIBILITY OF NOT BEING ABLE TO LOCATE ANY OF LATE ENGR. STEVE MOORE (SNR.)' S NEXT KIN (HE HAD NO WIFE OR CHILDREN THAT IS KNOW TO US). THE MANAGEMENT UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF OUR CHAIRMAN AND MEMBERS OF THE BOARD OF DIRECTORS, THAT ARRANGE HAS BEEN MADE FOR THE FUND TO BE DECLARED "UNCLAIMED" AND SUBSEQUENTLY BE DONATED TO THE TRUST FUND FOR ARMS AND AMMUNITION TO FURTHER ENHANCE THE COURSE OF WAR IN AFRICA AND THE WORLD IN GENERAL. IN ORDER TO AVERT THIS NEGATIVE DEVELOPMENT SOME OF MY TRUSTED COLLEAGUES AND I NOW SEEK YOUR PERMISSION TO HAVE YOU STAND AS NEXT OF KIN TO! LATE ENGR. STEVE MOORE (SNR.) SO THAT THE FUND US$30 MILLION WILL BE RELEASED AND PAID INTO YOUR ACCOUNT AS THE BENEFICIARY'S NEXT OF KIN. ALL DOCUMENTS AND PROVES TO ENABLE YOU GET HIS FUND WILL BE CAREFULLY WORKED OUT. WE HAVE SECURE FROM THE PROBATE AN ORDER OF MADAMUS TO LOCATE ANY OF DECEASED BENEFICIARIES, AND MORE SO WE ARE ASSURING YOU THAT THIS BUSINESS IS 100% RISK FREE INVOLVEMENT. YOUR SHARE STAYS WHILE THE REST BE FOR MYSELF AND MY COLLEAGUES FOR INVESTMENT PURPOSE. ACCORDING TO AGREEMENT WITHIN BOTH PARTIES. AS SOON AS WE RECEIVE AN ACKNOWLEDGEMENT OF RECEIPT OF THIS MESSAGE IN ACCEPTANCE OF OUR MUTUAL BUSINESS PROPOSAL, WE WOULD FURNISH YOU WITH THE NECESSARY MODALITIES AND DISBURSEMENT RATIO TO SUITE BOTH PARTIES WITH OUT ANY CONFLICT. WHILE REPLYING FURNISH ME WITH YOUR PRIVATE FAX AND PHONE NUMBERS FOR EASY COMMUNICATION,BANK NAME,COMPANIES NAME AND ADDRESS. THE SHARING OF THE FUND ARE THUS: 20% FOR YOU THE ACCOUNT OWNER,70% FOR I AND MY ! TRUSTED COLLEAGUES AND THE REMAINNING 10% FOR EXPENSES FOR BOTH PARTIES. IF THIS PROPOSAL IS ACCEPTABLE BY YOU, DO NOT MAKE UNDUE ADVANTAGE OF THE TRUST WE HAVE BESTOWED IN YOU. BEST REGARDS, DR.AZEM USMAN (MANAGER). _________________________________________________________________ Avec Windows Live OneCare éliminez tous les virus de votre PC ! http://www.windowslive.fr/liveonecare/default.asp

One with Christ, It is by the grace of God that I received Christ,knowing the truth and the truth have set me free.Having known the truth, I had no choice than to do what is lawful and right in the sight of God for eternal life and in the sight of man for witness of God?s mercy and glory upon my life. I have the pleasure to share my testimony with you, having seen your contact from the Internet. I am Barrister Martinez Obe, the legal adviser to late Mr.and Mrs.Grieves Martins a British couple that lived in my Country Nigeria for 25 years before they died in the Bellview plane crash . They are good Christian, They so dedicated to God but They had no child till they died. Throughout their stay in my country, They acquired a lot of properties like lands, house properties, etc. As their legal adviser, before their death, They instructed me to write their WILL. Because they had no child, They dedicated their wealth to God. According to the WILL, the properties have to be sold and the money be given out to a ministry for the work of God, Orphanages and less privilegdes ones. As Their legal adviser, all the documents for the properties were in my care. They gave me the authority to sell the properties and give out the fund to the Ministries for the work of God. In short, I sold all the properties after their death, as they instructed And as matter of fact, after I sold all their properties, I realized more than $10,000,000.00 (Ten million US dollars plus),and what supposed to be the percentage interest of my right legal fee was firstly deducted by me out of the total amount realized from the sold properties, this was base on the initial agreement between me and the owner of the properties before their death. Therefore the total amount left to be invested into God's work as instructed by the owner, is $10,000,000.00 (Ten million US dollars) only. But Instead of giving the main fund out for the work of God as instructed to me by the owner before their death. I converted the fund to myself with the intention of investing the fund abroad for my personal use. I was afraid of putting the fund in the Bank, because I have to give account to the bank on how I got the money. I then packaged the fund in consignments and deposited the consignments with a security company. I did not want the management of the Security Company to know the content of the consignments; therefore I registered the content of the consignments as Gold Bars. Now, the security company believes that what I deposited with them was Gold Bars. I had encounter with Christ when Rev. Billy Graham was preaching on television concerning Ananias and Saphira in Acts 5:1-11. After hearing the word of God, I gave my life to Christ and became a born again Christian. As a born again Christian, I started reading my bible and one day, the Lord opened my eyes to Ezekiel 33: 18 and 19 where the word of God says: "When the righteous truth from his righteousness, and committee iniquity, he shall even die thereby. But if the wicked turn from his wickedness, and do that which is lawful and right, he shall live thereby". From the scripture, I discovered that the only way I could have peace in my life is to do what is lawful and right by giving out the fund as instructed for the work of God by the owner before her death. I have asked God for forgiveness and I know that God have forgiven me. But I have to do what is lawful and right in the sight of God by giving out the fund to the chosen ministry for the purpose of God's work as instructed by the owner before her death. After my fasting and prayers, I asked God to make his choice and direct me to a honest Christian but after my fervent prayer over it, then you were nominated to me through divine revelation from God, so these are how I received such a divine revelation from the Lord, how I got your contact information, and I then decided to contact you for the fund to be used wisely for things that will glorify the name of God. I have notified the Security Company where I deposited the consignments that contained the fund, that I am moving the consignment abroad and the security company has since been waiting for my authority for the consignment to leave my country and move to abroad. You should also forward to me your telephone and fax number for easy communication and to fax you the documents concerning the consignments. prompt response will be highly appreciated.you can contact me on my secured e-mail address martinezobe84@keromail.com Yours in Christ Barrister Martinez Obe.

My Dear, With all sincerity and humility it is with deep pains i write you this message of wishful assistance to my predicament. I am Mrs Jewel Taylor the estranged wife to the former president of Liberia who was asked by unanimous decision by the international community to step down from the corridors of power . I write you this mail under duress and as a result of my recent decision to better the lives of i and my children. I have made a decision which i know might not be good in the sight of man but the present situation has led me to this decision to better the lives of my children. Currently now i have decided to make do with the sum of $20m (Twenty Million United States Dollars)belonging to my husband in which i am a benefiaciary to, i have decided to relocate with your assistance to your private account the said sum. My decision was reached when i could not conceive the thought that after the United States Government has promised to let my husband go free based on the condition that he should step down Mr. Collin Powell stated in a press briefing that he would be indicted by the court in Netherlands to face charges on war crimes, this is what led to my decision as God Knows that i was never in support of his involvement in the indecent maltreating of innocent people in Politics. This decision is hard for me to make but i just have to make it for the sake of my children's future. Currently the said sum was lodged in a safety deposit box in a financial Institution which i will disclose to you as a matter of commitment to me and this plea for assistance. I currently have the deposit certificate and can draw up a change of beneficiary mandate to effect you as the beneficiary to the funds. I am a trained economist by profession and it is in this line that i will want you to take note that your services for assisting me will be compensated to the best of my ability. I have this to look forward to so i would like you to keep this project close to your heart just as myself pending when we reach the conclusive end of this project. I will want you as a matter of confidentiality to respond through this mail and also include your telephone number as well so that i can give you a call if the need arises as we are currently on political asylum now in west africa. Once i get your confirmation that you can be of assistance i will bring you into a clearer picture of the situation at hand. View this site to see a picture of me: http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/africa/2963086.stm I look forward to your response with great hope of assistance from your good self. I dont have access to phone call in the camp but you can reach my first son Chukky through this phone number+234803 060 3076. I remain Yours Truly, Mrs Jewel Taylor

ATTN: The Presidency,Federal Government Officers on Finance,Senate committe on Finacial Matters, Central Bank of Nigeria and Diplomatic Corps met recently on the present fiscal-reformations. It is known that, many Foreigners have lost money to Nigeria through: Fraud, Unpaid-Contract or others. The Bank First Bank of Nigeria PLC has been authorised to attend to all these foreign and international matters. The Bank is contacting you because, your email is among the beneficiaries, submitted to us by the Ministries concerned. Only your e-mail address is the only contact information we could retrieve for now from the past records of Stake-Holders who have not been cleared of one Transcation or the other. The outcome of the summit has prompted the Federal Government to empower only our Bank;First Bank of Nigeria PLC to Identify the owners of some funds yet un-claimed and pay them outright with no delay.The Files and all Documents relating to Foreign-Affairs has been handed over to our Bank. Please, reply this mail, so that we can proceed forwarding all relevant evidencies of the Money to you. Be informed that the Federal Government have approved the release of payments which has been in this bank for many years unclaimed because my boss Mr. Jacobs Ajekigbe, collaboration with the Governor of Central Bank of Nigeria (CBN) have refused to tell you the truth on how to claim your fund this is because he has been using the interest accumulated from your fund every year to enrich himself without your knowledge. I,John Aboh has been appointed by the Bank,s Management Authority to supervise this execise.We are now in operation finding the rightful owners of the funds that has accumulated in Nigeria for years.This execise covers all transactions ever had with Nigerians before or at present. My boss; Mr. Jacobs M. Ajekigbe, the Managing Director/CEO of this bank is now on compulsory leave and all power have been vested on me to make all international payments. I want to help you pull out this fund to your bank account using the easiest and the quickest method,which have not been made known to you before.By this method,you will open a domiciliary account with this bank (First Bank of Nigeria),your fund would be lodged into this dociliary account and your fund will be paid in directly to any bank of your choice. After the transfer, you will confirm the fund in your bank account within 5-hours same day. No Cost of Transfer (COT) and no stoppage from any Government departments as the transfer will be done within the bank alone and it is very safe. Confirm to me through this e-mail address: firstbngplca@hotmail.com your: Personal Information; Phone and Fax Number; Banking Information, where the money will be Trensfered into. Awaiting your quick response. Yours truly, JOHN O. ABOH FBN

>From The Office of The Director of International Relation,Access Bank Plc 22 Marina Street,Marina Lagos-Nigeria Dear, Please permit me to introduce my humble self to you. I am Mr. Harrison Ken the Director of International Relation with Access Bank of Nigeria Limited. I 'm 47yrs old and I got your email address on the Chambers of Commerce address list and my confidence reposed on you to contact you. I hope you read this message Carefully and reply me immediately,although we have not met before but I suggest that this transaction will bring us together. My dear, we have a customer from a your country but base here in Nigeria since over a decade now, his name is Mr. Hamilton Creek from Atlanta Georgia United State of America but reside here with his wife and his two children. Mr. Hamilton Has being banking with our bank for the past 4yrs some time October 2002. On 12th of August 2003 Mr. Hamilton was on his way to his house and unfortunately he ran into a Trailer truck load of Groundnut Oil and died immediately. Their car got burnt and Mr. Hamilton Creek and His entire family was confirmed died which no single soul was saved. The Board of Directors and the Management of Access Bank has mandated and Instructed me to look for Mr. Hamilton Creek relatives/his Next of Kin to come and claim Mr.Hamilton's Fund. Since August 2003 till date I have been looking for Mr. Hamilton Creek Relatives/Next of Kin to come and claim Mr. Hamilton's Fund which he Deposited with our bank. I have made a frantic effort to contact the American Embassy and after 3days the Ambassador told me that Mr. Hamilton Creek has no relation and no next of Kin.The Ambassador also told me that Mr. Hamilton used his first son as His next of kin but it is quite unfortunate that Mr. Hamilton Creek died with all his family members. The reason why I contacted you is this, Mr. Hamilton is dead and his only son whom supposed to inherit his properties and money also died With him. As at this moment, nobody or person[s] is coming to claim this Money from our bank. The board directors and management of our bank has told me that if nobody or person[s] apply for the claim of Mr. Hamilton's Fund, the bank will decleared Mr. Hamilton's Fund as unclaimed and it will send into the Federal Government of Nigeria Reserve Account, In order to avert this, I want you to stand as the Relation/relative of Late Mr. Hamilton Creek and to act as the Hamilton's relative so that late Mr. Hamilton Creek money which he deposited with our bank will be release to you. It might interest you to know that Mr. Hamilton has a Domiciliary Bank Account with our Bank and he has a total sum of US$52Million (Fifty two Million United States Dollars) and it is the exact amount which late Mr. Hamilton Creek has in his domiciliary Account and this money is still in his account as unclaimed money. This transaction is very easy and simple and it is 100% risk free. I'm the Director of International Relations with Access Bank of Nigeria Limited and the management/Board of Directors of the Bank are waiting for me to present to them the Relation or next of Kin to late Mr. Hamilton Creek, which I told them that I am still searching the next of kin to the deceased. Finally, if you are interested with this transaction, I will present you to the bank as the only next of kin to late Mr, Hamilton Creek and I will let the bank to know that you are the only right person to inherit Late Mr. Hamilton Funds and properties, and his Money US$52M(fIifty two Million United States Dollars) will be transferred into Your Own Account as late Mr. Hamilton Creek next of kin. Please if you are interested, Just email me on my direct private and secured Email Address for immediate commencement so that late Mr. Hamilton Funds will be credited Into your Account and all his Properties will be released to you either Through Courier Services or the Bank will Cargo all his properties to You in any were you want it. So reply me immediately and let me know what your decision and also feel free to ask any questions. Meanwhile we will share Late Mr. Hamilton Creek Funds 50-50 which you will take 50% of the US$52M. which is amounting to US$26M, (Twenty Six Million United States Dollars, while the Balance of the same amount will be mine. I will be waiting for your Immediate response, Thanks and have a nice day. Friendly Regards Mr. Harrison Ken. _________________________________________________________________ Message offline contacts without any fire risk! http://www.communicationevolved.com/en-za/

OFFICE OF THE DIRECTOR OF OPERATION INTERNATIONAL CREDIT SETTLEMENT, CENTRAL BANK OF NIGERIA ATTENTION: BENEFICIARY. THIS IS TO OFFICIALLY INFORM YOU THAT WE HAVE VERIFIED YOUR CONTRACT/ INHERITANCE FILE AND FOUND OUT THAT WHY YOU HAVE NOT RECEIVED YOUR PAYMENT IS BECAUSE YOU HAVE NOT FULFILED THE OBLIGATIONS GIVEN TO YOU IN RESPECT OF YOUR CONTRACT/INHERITANCE PAYMENT. SECONDLY WE HAVE BEEN INFORMED THAT YOU ARE STILL DEALING WITH THE NONE OFFICIALS IN THE BANK,AND ALL YOUR ATTEMPT TO SECURE THE RELEASE OF YOUR FUND PROVED ABORTIVE. WE WISH TO ADVISE YOU THAT SUCH AN ILLEGAL ACT LIKE THIS HAVE TO STOP IF YOU WISH TO RECEIVE YOUR PAYMENT SINCE WE HAVE DECIDED TO BRING A SOLUTION TO YOUR PROBLEM. RIGHT NOW WE HAVE ARRANGED YOUR PAYMENT THROUGH OUR SWIFT CARD PAYMENT CENTER HERE IN CENTRAL BANK OF NIGERIA, THAT IS THE LATEST INSTRUCTION FROM MR. PRESIDENT,CHIEF OLUSEGUN OBASANJO (GCFR) FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF NIGERIA,AND ECONOMIC & FINANCIAL CRIMES COMMISSION(EFCC) NIGERIA. THIS OFFICE WILL SEND TO YOU AN ATM CARD WHICH YOU WILL USE TO WITHDRAW YOUR MONEY IN ANY ATM MACHINE IN ANY PART OF THE WORLD, BUT THE MAXIMUM IS SEVEN THOUSAND DOLLARS PER DAY, SO PROVIDE THE BELOW INFORMATION TO THIS OFFICE. 1. YOUR FULL NAME 2. PHONE AND FAX NUMBER 3. ADDRESS WHERE YOU WOULD LIKE TO RECEIVE THE ATM CARD. 4. YOUR AGE AND CURRENT OCCUPATION KINDLY CONTACT THIS OFFICE, THE ATM PAYMENT DEPARTMENT(CBN). atmcreditdepartmentofcbn@yahoo.com ACCOUNT OFFICER MR. LEO STEVE THIS OFFICE HAS BEEN MANDATED TO ISSUE OUT ATMCARD VALUED $5,500,000.00 AS INITIAL PAYMENT FOR THIS FISCAL YEAR 2007. NOTE THAT BECAUSE OF IMPOSTORS, WE HEREBY ISSUE YOU OUR CODE OF CONDUCT, WHICH IS (ATM-Y2K6) SO YOU HAVE TO INDICATE THIS CODE WHEN CONTACTING THIS OFFICE BY USING IT AS YOUR SUBJECT. KIND REGARDS, ALHAJI MUSA S.D.BELLO HEAD AUDITOR INTERNATIONAL CREDIT SETTLEMENT CBN.

Dear Friend, I am Mr. Stark William, the senior credit officer of NATWEST BANK PLC.I have three more months in this office and as such i am informing you for a reliable partner concerning a project in this bank which will be of great benefit to our families. After the United States and Iraqi war, our client Hatem Kamil Abdul Fatah who was the deputy governor of Baghdad in Iraq and also business man made a numbered fixed deposit for 12 calendar months, with a value of £25,000,000 (Twenty Five Million British Pounds) only in my branch.Upon maturity several notices were sent to him, even in the first quater of this year. Again another notification was sent and still no response came from him. We later found out that the Deputy Governor has been assasinated in Baghdad. The websites below is a proof and verification of the news about his death: http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/pr/fr/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/3970619.stm http://www.uslaboragainstwar.org/article.php?id=6979 After further investigation it was also discovered that Hatem Kamil Abdul Fatah did not declare any next of kin in his official papers including the paper work of his bank deposit. And he also confided in me the last time he was at my office that no one except me knew of his deposit in my bank.So,the said amount is still lying in my bank as no one will come forward to claim it. Against this backdrop, my suggestion to you is that I will like you as a neutral person to stand in as the next of kin to Hatem Kamil Abdul Fatah so that you will beable to receive his funds with my aid as the insider. THE PREREQUISITE OF THIS PROJECT: I want you to know that I have had everything planned out so that we come out successful. I have contacted an attorney that will prepare the necessary documents that will back you up as the next of kin to Hatem Kamil Abdul Fatah,all that is required from you NOW is for you to provide me with your : 1.Full Names 2.Complete residential Address so that the attorney can prepare the documents with your name. After you have been made the next of kin,the attorney will also file in for claims on your behalf and secure the necessary approvals and letter of probate in your favor for the move of the funds to an account that will be provided by you. There are no risks involved in the matter as we are going adopt a legalized method and the attorney will prepare all necessary documents. Please endeavour to observe utmost discretion in all matters concerning this issue. Once the funds have been transferred to your nominated bank account we shall share in the ratio of 60% for me, 40% for you. Should you be interested, please send me your full particulars including your private phone and/or fax numbers for easy communication,and i will provide you with more details of this operation as well as my particulars. . Email:starkmail@yahoo.ie I AWAIT AN EMAIL IN RESPONSE TO THE ABOVE PROPOSAL. Kind Regards, Mr.Stark William.

MRS MARIA SOCORRO CREDIT ACCOUNTS OFFICER HEAD OFFICE EQUITABLE PCI BANK TWR. MKT AVENUE.COR.H.V DELA COSTA STR PHILIPPPINES . Good Day, Let me start by introducing myself,I am MRS MRS MARIA SOCORRO,CREDIT ACCOUNTS OFFICER EQUITABLE PCI BANK. I am writing you this letter based on the latest development at my bank, which I will like to bring to your personal edification. I am writing you this letter with so much joy and excitement even though my heart goes out to the very powerful and distinguished gentleman who I was fortunate to have worked for and extremely privileged to have known for numerous years.. I am a top official in charge of client accounts in EQUITABLE PCI BANK inside the philippines. In 2001, my client was going through a horrendous divorce in the United States Of America and was on the verge of losing most of his estate to his vicious and diabolical wife. As a result of this alarming predicament, my client came to me with a very brilliant idea. He transferred some funds, ten million two hundred thousand dollars(usd10.2m) to a fixed deposit account in my bank under an alias which only the two of us knew about as the confidentiality of the matter was necessary for his protection. Due to his untimely death in early 2002, the funds have been sitting in the account ever since and will continue to do so perpetually unless we do something about it. This is where you come in.I located you through an agency that helps seek people by their email.my client did not declare any next of kin in his official papers including the paper work of his bank deposit.Against this backdrop, my suggestion to you is that I would like you as a foreigner to stand as the next of kin to our client so that you will be able to receive his funds. I want you to know that I have had everything planned out so that we can come out successful. I have contacted an attorney that will prepare the necessary document that will back you up as the next of kin to my client.All that is required from you at this stage is for you to provide me with your Full Names and Address so that the attorney can commence his job.After you have been made the next of kin, the attorney will also file in for claims on your behalf and secure the necessary approval and letter of probate in your favor for the move of the funds to an account that will be provided by you.There is no risk involved at all in the matter as we are going adopt a legalized method and the attorney will prepare all the necessary documents.The allocation of our money will be as follows: 20%(US$2.02M) to you for your part in this, 75% for me and my partners and 5% for any unforeseeable expenses we may incur. I think this is extremely fair, as you have nothing to lose but just a little time, while on the other hand I am staking my flawless reputation among other things. And besides $2.02 million is no pocket change. Once you are approved, the entire transaction should take no longer than twelve business days after which we will go about our daily business, but just millions of dollars richer. As you can see this is easier than taking candy from a baby but mind you, trust is something that is developed over time and that is something that we do not have. So I have to let you know that it will highly unfeasible to try to run away with the money because even though only you can transfer money in and out of your account, the transfer can only be authorized by my department of which i happen to be thehead.The money will be transfered from my bank to an account you will provide. So please, there should be no room for greed because ten million two hundred thousand dollars can quench even the most insatiable desire for the almighty dollar. Again, i will be in charge of everything else. I will assume all responsibilities for this endeavor so you don’t have to worry about any legal ramifications, just what you will do with all that money. If interested,I would want you to send your reply to my private mail box: (m_socorro27@excite.com) Your urgent response is highly anticipated so please email me for more details on this transaction as soon as possible. This should be kept very secret and confidential… I believe you know. kind Regards Mrs. MRS MARIA SOCORRO esq (m_socorro27@excite.com)

From:Frank Jewell Smith & Williamson Private Banking Services Riding House Extension, London, Uk Dear Friend, I am Mr. Frank Jewell, the accounting officer-in charge of the Private investment section of the above named Finance house. I have decided to contact you on a business Transfer that requires confidentiality, trust and transparency,where both of us have a lot to Benefit, during my investigation and auditing in the Accounts section, my department came across a huge sum of money belonging to a deceased person, a foreigner who died On January 7, 2005 in a auto crash. This Fund has been dormant in his account in the private investment dept without any claim to this fund in our custody, either From his family or relation. The said amount is (7.5 million pounds)which is about ($15million US Dollars) As it might interest you to know, I got your contact through international business enquiry and my search for a trust worthy business partner that can handle a business of this magnitude. Meanwhile all arrangement to put claim to this fund in Your name as the bonafide next of kin to the deceased,And get the required approval to transfer this money to a foreign account, have been put in place. While The next line of action to conclude this transaction In the next 10 working days, will be relayed to you as soon as you indicate your interest in this Transaction.I must also inform you that upon the completion of this Transaction, you will be entitled to 40% of the total Sum as gratification, for your role and assistance, While the balance will be for me as the owner of the funds. Please, you have been advised to keep this to your self since I am still in service and intend to Retire after I conclude this project. I will be monitoring the whole situation here until you confirm the money in your account. Then, immediately, I shall come down to the country of your nominated account for subsequent sharing of the Funds according to percentages previously indicated and further investment. Please use this email address for security reasons: f_jewell0013@yahoo.co.uk Yours faithfully, Mr. Frank Jewell _________________________________________________________________ Get a FREE Web site, company branded e-mail and more from Microsoft Office Live! http://clk.atdmt.com/MRT/go/mcrssaub0050001411mrt/direct/01/

From: Mr Jeff Yukon. Address: #8 Mitchley Road Tottenham London N17 9HG Occupations: External Auditor Hello, Very Urgent And Confidential Do accept my sincere apologies if my mail does not meet your personal ethics although, I wish to use this medium to get in touch with you first because it's fastest means. I am an extenal auditor of a well known Bank here in the United Kingdom. In one of our periodic auditing I discorved a dormant accounts with holding balance of 52,000,000 (Fifty Two Million British Pounds) which has not been operated for the past three years. From my investigations and confirmations, the owner of this account, a foreigner by name Mr.Gregory .B.Wilson died in plane crash in July 19,2003 and since then nobody has done anything as regards the claiming of this money because he has no family members who are aware of the existence of neither the account nor the funds. I have secretly discussed this matter with a top senior minister official of the federal ministry of finance here and we have agreed to find a reliable foreign partner to deal with us, although due to his possition he did not want to take active part but as soon as you follow my instructions everything will be successfull because we will be working hand in hand with him. We thus propose to do business with you,standing in as the next of kin of these funds from the deceased and after due legel processes have been followed the fund will be released to your account without delay and we will use it for investment and to assist the less privelaged in the society because if we left the fund with the government it will be fortified for nothing and will be used to suppress the poor masses in the society. This transaction is totally free of risk and troubles as the fund is legitimate and does not originate from drug, money laundry, terrorism or any other illegal act. So you should provide me with your correct account detail where you will like the fund to be transferred even an empty account is ok. At the conclussion of the transfer you will take 35%,5% will be for any expenses both parties incurred in the process of this business and the remaining 60% will be for me. As soon as I hear from you and upon your strong assurance that you will not let me down once the fund goes into your account I will then start the processing of the transfer of the fund to your account without further delay. You should send the a/c information as stated below.......together with your telephone nos. both Home, Office & Cell phone for easier & faster communication. Bank Name........... Bank Address......... A/C Name.............. A/C Number............... Swift Code.................. Your Telephone................ Routing Number.................. State & Country................ I look forward to hear from you as soon as possible if you are interested. Yours, Mr Jeff Yukon.

Independent Committee of Eminent Persons (ICEP),London. Email:kcole444@yahoo.co.uk ATTENTION: I am a member of Independent Committee of Eminent Persons (ICEP),London. ICEP is charged with the responsibility of finding bank accounts in Switzerland belonging to non-Swiss indigenes, which have remained dormant since World War II. It may interest you to know that in July of 1997, the Swiss Banker's Association published a list of dormant accounts originally opened by non-Swiss citizens. These accounts had been dormant since the end of World War II (May 9, 1945). Most belonged to Holocaust victims. The continuing efforts of the Independent Committee of Eminent Persons (ICEP)have since resulted in the discovery of additional dormant accounts -54 ,000 in December, 1999. The published lists contain all types of dormant accounts,including interest-bearing savings accounts, securities accounts, safe deposit boxes, custody accounts, and non-interest-bearing transaction accounts. Numbered accounts are also included.Interest is paid on accounts that were interest bearing when established. The Claims Resolution Tribunal (CRT) handles processing of all claims on accounts due non-Swiss citizens. A dormant account of Hami Ramzy with a credit balance of 15,800,000 US dollar plus accumulated interest was discovered by me. The beneficiary was murdered during the holocaust era, leaving no WILL and no possible records for trace of theirs. The Claims Resolution Tribunal has been mandated to report all unclaimed funds for permanent closure of accounts and transfer of existing credit balance into the treasury of Switzerland government as provided by the law for management of assets of deceased benefi ciaries who died interstate living no wills). Being a top executive at ICEP, I have all secret details and necessary contacts for claim of the funds without any hitch. The funds will be banked in the Holland, London or Spain, being a safe for funds and we can share the funds and use in investment of our choice. Due to the sensitive nature of my job, I need a foreigner to HELP claim the funds. All that is required is for you to provide me with your details for processing of the necessary legal and administrative claim documents for transfer of the funds to you. Kindly provide me with your full name, address, and telephone/fax. For the fund to be transferred to a secure, numbered account in your name and country via any of the corresponding banks in London or Spain, of which you will be capable of accessing the funds gradually and transferring to your country and other banks of choice in the world. My share will be 60 percent and your share is 40 pe r cent of the total amount. THERE IS NO RISK INVOLVED, The Holocaust Claims Processing Office has put funds in Escrow awaiting submission of valid claims for necessary disbursement, I find myself privileged to have this information and this may be a great opportunity for a life time of success without risks. Thanking you in anticipation for your prompt response. Regards, Dr Kenneth cole. ___________________________________ The Student Zone http://www.thestudentzone.com

DEAR PARTNER, I AM MR. ABISHA ALLAHIM, THE BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER AT THE FOREIGN EXCHANGE DEPARTMENT OF INTERNATIONAL BANK OF BURKINA (IBB) OUAGADOUGOU IN BURKINA FASO. WITH DUE RESPECT AND REGARDS, I HAVE DECIDED TO CONTACT YOU ON A BUSINESS TRANSACTION THAT WILL BE VERY BENEFICIAL TO BOTH OF US AT THE END OF THE TRANSACTION.DURING MY INVESTIGATION AND AUDITING IN MY DEPARTMENT, I CAME ACROSS A VERY HUGE SUM OF MONEY BELONGING TO A DECEASED PERSON, A FOREIGNER WHO DIED IN A PLANE CRASH WITH HIS INTIRE FAMILY. REPLY ONLY TO MY PRIVATE E-MAIL mr_a_allahim001@yahoo.fr THE FUND HAS BEEN IN HIS ACCOUNT WITH THE BANK WITHOUT ANY CLAIM OF THE FUND IN OUR CUSTODY EITHER FROM HIS FAMILY OR RELATION BEFORE OUR DISCOVERY TO THIS DEVELOPMENT.ALTHOUGH PERSONALLY, I KEPT THIS INFORMATION SECRET WITHIN MYSELF TO ENABLE THE WHOLE PLANS AND IDEA BE PROFITABLE AND SUCCESSFUL DURING THE TIME OF EXECUTION. THE AMOUNT INVOLVED IS USD$10.500,000 (TEN MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND U.S DOLLARS.) MEANWHILE THE WHOLE ARRANGEMENT AND DIRECTIVES NEEDED TO PUT CLAIM OVER THIS FUND AS THE NEXT OF KIN TO THE DECEASED, WILL BE FORWARD TO YOU UPON YOUR ACCEPTANCE. INFORMATION WILL BE RELAYED TO YOU AS SOON AS YOU INDICATE YOUR INTEREST AND WILLINGNESS TO ASSIST ME AND ALSO BENEFIT YOURSELF TO THIS GREAT BUSINESS OPPORTUNITY. IN FACT I COULD HAVE DONE THIS DEAL ALONE BUT BECAUSE OF MY POSITION IN THIS COUNTRY AS A CIVIL SERVANT, WE ARE NOT ALLOWED TO OPERATE A FOREIGN ACCOUNT AND WOULD EVENTUALLY RAISE AN EYE BROW ON MY SIDE DURING THE TIME OF TRANSFER BECAUSE I WORK IN THIS BANK. THIS IS THE ACTUAL REASON WHY IT WILL REQUIRE A SECOND PARTY OR FELLOW WHO WILL FORWARD CLAIMS AS THE NEXT OF KIN TO THE BANK AND ALSO PRESENT A FOREIGN ACCOUNT WHERE HE WILL NEED THE MONEY TO BE TRANSFERRED INTO ON HIS REQUEST AS IT MAY BE, AFTER DUE VERIFICATION AND CLARIFICATION TO DESIGNATED BANK ACCOUNT. YOU CAN SEE THE WEBSITE BELOW COVERING THE PLANE CRASH BY CNN & BBC NEWS. http://www.cnn.com/2003/WORLD/africa/12/26/benin.crash http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/africa/3348109.stm I WILL NOT FAIL TO INFORM YOU THAT THIS TRANSACTION IS 100% RISK FREE. ON SMOOTH CONCLUSION OF THIS TRANSACTION, YOU WILL BE ENTITLED TO 40% OF THE TOTAL SUM WHILE 60% WILL BE FOR ME. YOU HAVE BEEN ADVISED TO KEEP TOP SECRET AS I AM STILL IN SERVICE AND INTEND TO RETIRE FROM SERVICE AFTER I CONCLUDE THIS DEAL WITH YOU. I WILL BE MONITORING THE WHOLE SITUATION HERE IN THE BANK UNTIL YOU CONFIRM THE MONEY IN YOUR ACCOUNT AND ASK ME TO COME DOWN TO YOUR COUNTRY FOR SUBSEQUENT SHARING OF THE FUND ACCORDING TO PERCENTAGES PREVIOUSLY INDICATED AND FURTHER INVESTMENT, EITHER IN YOUR COUNTRY OR ANY OTHER COUNTRY YOU MAY ADVICE ME TO INVEST IN. ALL OTHER NECESSARY INFORMATION WILL BE SENT TO YOU WHEN I HEAR FROM YOU. I SUGGEST YOU GET BACK TO ME AS SOON AS POSSIBLE STATING YOUR WISH IN THIS DEAL. PLEASE REPLY TO MY PRIVATE E-MAIL mr_a_allahim001@yahoo.fr BY INDICATING YOUR BANK ACCOUNT DETALS WHERE THE FUND WILL BE TRANSFERED TO. ALSO, SEND ME YOUR PRIVATE PHONE NUMBER FOR EASY COMMUNICATION. BEST REGARD, MR. ABISHA ALLAHIM _________________________________________________________________ MSN Messenger: appels gratuits de PC à PC ! http://www.msn.fr/msger/default.asp

THE PRESIDENCY DEBT RECONCILIATION COMMITTEE Tel: +234-1-765-8477 Fax: +234-1-555-9344 ATTN CONTRACT BENEFICIARY, IMMEDIATE PAYMENT OF YOUR FUNDS. #: GVRCBN/NNPC/FGN/MIN/006. I am the Director, Debt reconciliation Committee of the Federal Republic of Nigeria. I bring to your immediate notice and urgent attention that the Nigerian Government, The United Nations and the African Union have finally approved your payment. A woman by name Mrs. Janet White came to our office with an application letter stating that you have instructed her to be the beneficiary also that you told her to act as your Next of Kin to receive your payment in her account. We are writing to know if you at any time gave this woman the power of attorney to represent you also if you are aware that your payment of $15.5M will be transferred to the below account: Bank of America, 2201 C St. NW, Washington, D.C. 20520ABA Number: 114000653; Account Number: 4746363838; Account Name: JANET WHITE Account officer's Phone number: 202-624-4750 If you are not aware of the above, do immediately reconfirm your correct banking details so that funds can be transferred to your account without any further delay as we have instructed our London paying bank to effect transfer to the above account if we do not hear from you till the next four banking days from the day this message was sent. I wish to inform you that this approved amount has been processed and will be released to you as soon as you respond to this letter. Also note that from the record in my file, the approved amount for immediate transfer is $15.5 million dollars (Fifteen Million Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars). With due respect sir, do reconfirm the below details to avoid paying your Contract/Inheritance payment to a wrong account or beneficiary. Note that this payment is ready to be made into your account as soon as you confirm to us that you did not send this woman and reconfirm the below details. 1) Your full name and full address (2) Phone, fax and mobile #.3) Bank Name and address (4) Bank account number, Swift code etc where funds will be transferred to. As soon as this information is received, your payment will be made in cash payment or KTT wire transferred to your bank account directly from Central Bank of Nigeria or our London Paying Bank and a copy of payment slips sent to you for immediate confirmation through your bank. Do help us serve you better by responding to this message immediately. Regards, Dr. Paul A. Sule DIRECTOR DEBT RECONCILIATION COMMITTEE

The cream of the crop for 2007 - GET IN EARLY! DSDI IS SET TO ROCK YOUR PORTFOLIO! DSI Direct Sales, Inc. Symbol: DSDI Price: $0.04 There is a MASSIVE PROMOTION underway this weekend! This is hot, read the news and get on DSDI first thing Monday! LOOK FOR HUMIDITIES TO FALL TO THE TEENS AND SINGLE DIGITS SUNDAY AND MONDAY WITH VERY POOR RECOVERIES SUNDAY NIGHT AND MONDAY MORNING. ISSUED BY: 222 Issuing Weather Forecast Office Homepage Flood Statement Randolph (Arkansas) FLOOD STATEMENT NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE LITTLE ROCK AR 920 AM CDT SUN MAY 06 2007 . THE COMBINATION OF HEAT. BOAT AND AIRCRAFT OWNERS SHOULD CHECK MOORINGS AND TIEDOWNS AS NECESSARY. WATER LEVELS ARE HIGH IN THE IMMEDIATE VICINITY OF THE BRIDGE BUT NO SIGNIFICANT FLOODING IS OCCURRING. THEN BEGIN FALLING LATE TUESDAY. FROM EARLY SUNDAY MORNING THROUGH MONDAY EVENING. KLAWOCK AND HYDABURG. AREAS OF NORTH TO NORTHEAST WINDS 25 TO 35 MPH WITH LOCAL GUSTS OVER 50 MPH ARE EXPECTED THIS MORNING. BREEZY WITH SOUTHEAST WIND 15 TO 25 MPH. NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE METEOROLOGISTS DETECTED SCATTERED SHOWERS AND THUNDERSTORMS ACROSS PAWNEE AND OSAGE COUNTIES IN NORTHEAST OKLAHOMA. A WIND ADVISORY MEANS THAT WINDS OF 35 MPH OR GREATER ARE EXPECTED. WIND ADVISORY REMAIN IN EFFECT UNTIL 12 PM NOON ADT TODAY. ADDITIONAL ISOLATED TO WIDELY SCATTERED SHOWERS AND THUNDERSTORMS WILL BE POSSIBLE ELSEWHERE ACROSS NORTHEAST AND EAST CENTRAL OKLAHOMA. THE FIRE WEATHER WATCH REMAINS IN EFFECT DUE TO EXPECTED LONG DURATIONS OF RELATIVE HUMIDITY BELOW 35 PERCENT WITH DISPERSION INDICES ABOVE 75. LOCALLY BREEZY WITH EAST WIND 15 TO 25 MPH. STRONGEST WINDS IN EXPOSED AREAS NEAR CROSS SOUND AND ALONG OUTSIDE COASTAL AREAS. NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE METEOROLOGISTS DETECTED SCATTERED SHOWERS AND THUNDERSTORMS ACROSS PAWNEE AND OSAGE COUNTIES IN NORTHEAST OKLAHOMA. FROM EARLY SUNDAY MORNING THROUGH MONDAY EVENING. PELICAN 530 AM ADT SUN MAY 6 2007 . FIRE WEATHER WATCH IN EFFECT FROM MONDAY AFTERNOON THROUGH MONDAY EVENING. EXPECT WEST TO NORTHWEST WIND 15 TO 25 MPH. STRONGEST WINDS IN EXPOSED AREAS NEAR CROSS SOUND AND ALONG OUTSIDE COASTAL AREAS. THESE REGIONS INCLUDE THE MOUNTAINS AND INTERIOR PORTIONS OF SAN LUIS OBISPO COUNTY. ISSUED BY: 222 Issuing Weather Forecast Office Homepage Flood Statement Randolph (Arkansas) FLOOD STATEMENT NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE LITTLE ROCK AR 920 AM CDT SUN MAY 06 2007 . FOR THE FOLLOWING FORECAST LOCATIONS:. WINDS WILL DIMINISH SOMEWHAT SUNDAY AFTERNOON. NORTHWEST WINDS 5 TO 10 MPH INCREASING TO 10 TO 15 MPH BY LATE MORNING. FIRE WEATHER WATCH NOW IN EFFECT FROM MONDAY AFTERNOON THROUGH MONDAY EVENING. ADDITIONAL ISOLATED TO WIDELY SCATTERED SHOWERS AND THUNDERSTORMS WILL BE POSSIBLE ELSEWHERE ACROSS NORTHEAST AND EAST CENTRAL OKLAHOMA. MOSTLY CLOUDY SKIES ACROSS THE AREA WILL CONTINUE THROUGH THE MORNING. STRONG NORTHERLY WINDS. A WIND ADVISORY REMAINS IN EFFECT UNTIL NOON PDT TODAY. AND LOCALLY THE COASTAL AREAS OF VENTURA AND LOS ANGELES COUNTIES. WIND ADVISORY REMAINS IN EFFECT UNTIL 12 PM ADT TODAY. HIGH WATER LEVELS FOR COPPER RIVER TRIBUTARIES. THEN BEGIN FALLING LATE TUESDAY. PORT ALEXANDER 530 AM ADT SUN MAY 6 2007 . WIND ADVISORY REMAINS IN EFFECT UNTIL NOON PDT TODAY. STRONG OFFSHORE WINDS AND VERY DRY CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED TO DEVELOP TONIGHT AND TOMORROW MORNING. ISSUED BY: 222 Issuing Weather Forecast Office Homepage Flood Statement Lawrence (Arkansas) FLOOD STATEMENT NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE LITTLE ROCK AR 920 AM CDT SUN MAY 06 2007 . NORTHWEST WINDS 5 TO 10 MPH INCREASING TO 10 TO 15 MPH BY LATE MORNING. LIGHT WEST WINDS 5 TO 10 MPH THROUGH 10 AM. MOSTLY CLOUDY SKIES WITH ISOLATED SNOW SHOWERS AND AREAS OF FOG. THE NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE IN TALLAHASSEE HAS ISSUED THE FIRE WEATHER WATCH DUE TO A COMBINATION OF RELATIVE HUMIDITY BELOW 30 PERCENT. 0 FEET BY WEDNESDAY EVENING. GUSTS TO 35 MPH IN EXPOSED AREAS. VENTURA AND LOS ANGELES COUNTIES AND THE COASTAL VALLEYS OF VENTURA AND LOS ANGELES COUNTIES FROM EARLY SUNDAY MORNING UNTIL MONDAY EVENING. MOSTLY CLOUDY SKIES ACROSS THE AREA WILL CONTINUE THROUGH THE MORNING. MOSTLY CLOUDY SKIES ACROSS THE AREA WILL CONTINUE THROUGH THE MORNING. SOUTHEAST WIND 20 TO 30 MPH. AREAS OF NORTH TO NORTHEAST WINDS 25 TO 35 MPH WITH LOCAL GUSTS OVER 50 MPH ARE EXPECTED THIS MORNING. STRONG AND GUSTY NORTH TO NORTHEAST WINDS WILL AFFECT THE MOUNTAINS OF VENTURA AND LOS ANGELES COUNTIES AS WELL AS THE SANTA CLARITA VALLEY AND THE SANTA MONICA MOUNTAINS THIS MORNING.

FROM:MR.DAN WAHILI. AFRICAN DEVELOPEMENT BANK BURKINA FASO (ADB) OUAGADOUGOU-BURKINA FASO. DEAR FRIEND, IT WILL BE A SURPRISE FOR YOU TO RECEIVE THIS MAIL. WELCOME THIS LETTER IN THE NAME OF ALLAH. I AM MR.DAN WAHILI,THE DIRECTOR OF THE ACCOUNTS & AUDITING DEPT.AT THE AFRICAN DEVLOPEMENT BANK OUAGADOUGOU-WEST AFRICA. WITH DUE RESPECT I HAVE DECIDED TO CONTACT YOU ON A BUSINESS TRANSACTION THAT WILL BE BENEFICIAL TO BOTH OF US. AT THE BANK'S LAST ACCOUNTS/AUDITING EVALUATIONS,MY STAFFS CAME ACROSS AN OLD ACCOUNT WHICH WAS BEING MAINTAINED BY A FOREIGN CLIENT WHO WE LEARNT WAS AMONG THE DECEASED PASSENGERS OF AN AIRLINE CRASH ON 6TH NOV. 2003.SINCE THE DECEASED WAS UNABLE TO RUN THIS ACCOUNT SINCE HIS DEATH.THE ACCOUNT HAS REMAINED DORMANT WITHOUT THE KNOWLEDGE OF HIS FAMILY SINCE IT WAS PUT IN A SAFE DEPOSIT ACCOUNT IN THE BANK FOR FUTURE INVESTMENT BY THE CLIENT. SINCE HIS DEMISE,NOBODY,NOT EVEN THE MEMBERS OF HIS FAMILY HAVE APPLIED FOR CLAIMS OVER THIS FUND AND IT HAS BEEN IN THE SAFE DEPOSIT ACCOUNT UNTIL WE DISCOVERED THAT IT CANNOT BE CLAIMED SINCE OUR CLIENT IS A FOREIGN NATIONAL AND WE ARE SURE THAT HE HAS NO NEXT OF KIN HERE TO FILE CLAIMS OVER THE MONEY.AS THE DIRECTOR OF THE DEPT,THIS DISCOVERY WAS BROUGHT TO MY OFFICE SO AS TO DECIDE WHAT IS TO BE DONE.WITH THE FEW PERSONEL IN MY DEPT,WE DECIDED TO SEEK WAYS THROUGH WHICH TO TRANSFER THIS MONEY OUT OF THE BANK AND OUT OF THE COUNTRY TOO. THE TOTAL AMOUNT IN THE ACCOUNTS IS TEN MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND DOLLARS(USD 10,500,000.00).WITH OUR POSITIONS AS STAFFS OF THE BANK,WE ARE HANDICAPPED BECAUSE WE CANNOT OPERATE FOREIGN ACCOUNTS AND CANNOT LAY BONAFIDE CLAIM OVER THIS MONEY.WHILE WE WERE CONTEMPLATING ON WHAT TO DO,A FRIEND OF MINE WHO WORKS WITH THE CHAMBER OF COMMERCE AND INDUSTRY RECOMMENDED YOUR PERSONALITY TO ME AND ADVISED I SHOULD ASK YOU FOR HELP TO TRANSFER THIS MONEY OUT OF THE COUNTRY.THE CLIENT IS A FOREIGN NATIONAL AND YOU WILL ONLY BE ASKED TO ACT AS HIS NEXT OF KIN AND I WILL SUPPLY YOU WITH ALL THE NECESSARY INFORMATIONS AND BANK DATA TO ASSIST YOU IN BEING ABLE TO TRANSFER THIS MONEY TO ANY BANK OF YOUR CHOICE WHERE THIS MONEY COULD BE TRANSFERED INTO. I AND MY PARTNERS HAVE DECIDED TO GIVE AWAY FOURTY %(40%)TO YOU FOR YOUR ASSISTANCE AND TEN (10%) FOR ANY EXPENSES THAT MIGHT ARISE DURING THE TRANSACTION OF THIS TRANSFER.WE WANT TO ASSURE YOU THAT THIS TRANSACTION IS ABSOLUTELY RISK FREE SINCE WE WORK IN THIS BANK WHICH IS WHY YOU SHOULD BE CONFIDENT IN THE SUCCESS OF THIS TRANSACTION BECAUSE YOU WILL BE UPDATED WITH INFORMATION AS AT WHEN DESIRED. WE WILL PLEASE WISH YOU KEEP THIS TRANSACTION SECRET AS WE ARE HOPING TO RETIRE WITH OUR SHARE OF THIS MONEY AT THE END OF TRANSACTION WHICH WILL BE WHEN THIS MONEY IS SAFELY IN YOUR ACCOUNT. WE WILL THEN COME OVER TO YOUR COUNTRY FOR SHARING ACCORDING TO THE PREVIOUSLY AGREED PERCENTAGES.YOU MIGHT EVEN HAVE TO ADVISE US ON POSSIBILITIES OF INVESTMENT IN YOUR COUNTRY OR ELSEWHERE OF OUR CHOICE.MAY ALLAH HELP YOU TO HELP US TO A RESTIVE RETIREMENT.AMIN. PLEASE FOR FURTHER INFORMATIONS AND ENQUIRIES FEEL FREE TO CONTACT ME THROUGH MY NUMBER 00 226 78 84 92 06 FOR ORAL DISCUSSION. AM AWAITING FOR YOUR URGENT RESPONSE!!! THANKS AND REMAIN BLESSED. MR.DAN WAHILI _________________________________________________________________ MSN Hotmail : créez votre adresse e-mail gratuite & à vie ! http://www.msn.fr/newhotmail/Default.asp?Ath=f

Dear Friend, I am captain James .W. Brian in the US Marine Corps on Monitoring and Peace a keeping mission in Baghdad-Iraq. The reason why I am explaining my finding to you is to seek for your assistance to enable you contributes immensely to the actualization of my dreams. On the 18th day of March 2007, we were alerted on the presence of some terrorists hideouts in Haifa Street, a long thoroughfare of high-rise buildings built by Saddam Hussein here in Baghdad. After Immediate intervention by the Iraqi forces and ours, we were able to capture many foreign Arab fighters linked to al Qaeda in that operation and over 100 militants were killed on the process. Among the Arab fighters linked to al Qaeda two were interrogated by two of our intelligent investigators and I. They confessed that some of them are fighters for al Qaeda and some are for Ayman al-Zawahiri and they took us to some of their hideout which runs along the west bank of the Tigris River that cuts through the capital. When we invaded into the hideout, we recovered several guns, amour including some boxes among which two contains bullets, one filled with hard drugs (heroine) and the other two to my amazement contain some US Dollars which we assumed amounted to $23.2M after I and two of the intelligent investigators counted them and it took us over 4 hours to get it counted. I however instructed them to keep this in high secrecy so that we can have the money to our selves, they all agreed to the plan and they replied to me on how I can get this huge sum out of this country and I told them that ital&#8482;s no problem. This motivated me to connive with my best friend in our force who went with me and the two other officers to keep the boxes in a safer place. I am now in keen need of a "Reliable and Trustworthy" person like you who would receive, secure and protect these boxes containing the US Dollars for me untill my assignment elapses here. I assure and promise to give you 20% of this fund, however feel free to negotiate what you wish to have as your percentage in this deal. Please assure me of your keeping this topmost secret to protect my job with the US Monitoring and Peace-Keeping mission. please you can contact me with my private mailbox...... capt.james_brianusmarine5@yahoo.com My Sincere regards, Capt James Brian.(U.S MARINE)

-- From: Mustapha Benson Address: Banjul The Gambiaa Telephone Nos: 00220 9897219 Email: muspham6@hotmail.com Or muspham@safe-mail.net MANAGING DIRECTOR. Dear Sir, I am Mr Musatapha Accounts supervisor with National Bank,Freetown, Sierra Leone. I have urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. On June 6, 1999, a Foreign Diamond consultant/contractor with the Sierra Leonean National Diamond Corporation, Mr.Simon Kelly made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at SD$27,000,000.00, (Twenty-Seven Million Dollars) in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, I sent a reminder and finally I discovered from his contract employers, the Sierra Leanean National Diamond Corporation that Mr. Simon Kelly died from a rebel attack. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Simon Kelly did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of USD$27,000,000.00 has carefully/confidentially been moved out of my bank to a Finance security company in the Gambia for safekeeping. No one can ever come forward to claim it. According to Sierra Leonean Law, at the expiration of 8 (eight) years,the money will revert to the ownership of the Sierra Leone Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I want you as a Foreigner to stand in as the rightful owner of the money. I deposited it in a security company in two trunk boxes though the security company does not know the contents of the boxes as I tagged them to be photographic materials for export. In the circumstance, I want to present you as the rightful owner of the boxes in the security company so that you can be able to claim them with the help of my attorney. This is simple. I would like you to provide immediately your full names and address as well as your direct telephone and fax number so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents which will put you in the right place as the owner of the boxes. The money will be moved out for us to your country and share in the ratio of 80% for me and 20% for you. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the Attorney and this will guarantees the successful execution of this transaction on your behalf, please reply immediately via my email address. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction and swing into the necessary action while I confide in you hoping you will not betray me at last. Thanks and God bless Mr Musatapha ____________________ http://www.email.si/

FROM:RITA DOINK. INTERNATIONAL PROMOTIONS/PRIZE AWARD DEPARTMENT RESULTS FOR CATEGORY "A" DRAWS. Congratulations to you as we bring to your notice, the results of the First Category draws of THE HOLLAND CASINO LOTTO PROMO INT. We are happy to inform you that you have emerged a winner under the First Category, which is part of our promotional draws. The draws were being officially announced on the 12th of May, 2007.Participants were selected through a computer ballot system drawn from 2,500,000 email addresses of individuals and companies from Africa, America, Asia, Australia,Europe, Middle East and Oceania as part of our International Promotions Program. Your e- mail address, attached to Coupon numbers 8886088 consequently won in the First Category. You have therefore been awarded a lump sum pay out of 500,00000eur (Five hundred thousand euros), which is the winning payout for Category A winners. This is from a total cash prize of 5,000,000.00 Million Euros shared amongst the first Ten (10) lucky winners in this category. CONGRATULATIONS! Your fund is now deposited with the paying Bank.In your best interest to avoid mix up of numbers and names of any kind, we request that you keep the entire details of your award strictly from public notice until the process of transferring your claims has been completed, and your funds remitted to your account.This is part of our security protocol to avoid double claiming or unscrupulous acts by participants/nonparticipants of this program. Please contact your claims agent immediately for due processing and remittance of your prize money to a designated bank account of your choice. You are advised to contact the agents by email, phone or fax. Failure to do so may warrant disqualification.NOTE: For easy reference and identification, remember to quote your Coupon numbers in your correspondence with your claims agent. To file for your claim,please contact the fiduciary agent with your Coupon numbers, tel/fax numbers and full names. *********************************************** MR. FRANK UKREL. AMSTERDAM,THE NETHERLANDS. TEL: +31-626-415-585 FAX:+31-847-355-196. REPLY EMAIL:frankukrel@iwon.com *********************************************** All winnings must be notarized to complete the claim process; winners will be referred to a Foreign Transfer Manager,to have their winnings notarized. Congratulations once again from all our staff. Sincerely Yours, MRS. RITA DOINK. THE PROMOTION COORDINATOR

Dear Friend, I write to inform you of my desire to acquire estates or landed properties in your country on behalf of the Director of Contracts and Finance Allocation of the Federal Ministry of works and Housing in Nigeria. Considering his very strategic and influential position, he would want the transaction to be strictly as confidential as possible. He further want his identity to remain undisclosed at least for now, until the completion of the transaction. Hence our desire to have an overseas agent. I have therefore been directed to inquire if you would agree to act as our overseas agent in order to actualise this transaction. The deal in brief is that the funds with which to carry out our proposed investments in your country is presently in a coded account in the Nigerian apex bank and we need your assistance to transfer the funds to your country or any safe account outside your country in a convenient bank account that will be provided by you before we can put the funds into use. For this you shall be considered to have executed a contract for the ministry. The contract sum of which shall run into US$15.5Million of which your share shall be 30% if you agree to be our overseas agent. Your area of specialisation does not matter in this transaction, all that is required of you is a safe account and your willingness to assist us acquire estates in your country. As soon as payment is effected and the amount mentioned above is successfully transferred into your account, we intend to use our own share in acquiring some estates abroad. For this too, you shall serve as our agent . It might interest you to note that last year, a similar transaction was carried out with one MR. CHIENCHEN YU of Taiwan but after securing the payment approvals, and payment effected, MR.CHIENCHEN YU changed his numbers and addresses, and was no where to be found on our getting to Taiwan. That was how we lost US$7.5Million. So this time around , I will be with you before the remmittance is made into your provided account to avoid future occurrence and allow trust to play a very minimal role until performance is seen. You are requested to communicate your acceptance or otherwise of this proposal, through my email. After which we shall discuss in details the modalities for seeing this transaction through. If however, you are not disposed to assist, kindly destroy this letter in view of the confidentiality of the proposed transaction and interest of personalities involved. Thank you in anticipation of your co-operation. Best Regards, Dr.Mohammed Azeez.

FROM: DAVID KUBA. NO.10 ANDERSON STREET JOHANNESBURG, SOUTH AFRICA TEL: +27-83-9470181 FAX: +27-865173471 EMAIL: kubafamily001@yahoo.com ATTENTION: DIRECTOR /CEO. ATTENTION: DIRECTOR /CEO. STRICTLY PRIVATE AND CONFIDENTIAL You may be surprised to receive this letter from me since you don't know me personally, the purpose of my introduction is that, I am MR.DAVID KUBA,the first SON of MR.PEDRO KUBA,a farmer and leader movement for Democratic change (MDC)in Zimbabwe who was murdered in the land dispute in Zimbabwe. I was furnished with viable information from the International Trade Centre here in Johannesburg and I decided to write to you. Before the death of my father, he had taken me to Johannesburg to deposit the sum of US$40 M(FOURTY MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS),in a Security Company, as if he fore saw the looming danger in Zimbabwe. This amount was meant for the purchase of new machines and chemicals for the farms and the establishment of the new farms in Swaziland. This land problem came when Zimbabwean President MR.ROBERT MUGABE introduced a new Land Act which wholly affected the rich white farmers and some few black farmers.This resulted to the killing and mob action by Zimbabwean war veterans and some lunatics in the society. Infact, alot of people have been killed because of this land reformed Act for which my father was one of the victims. It is against this background, that I and my family who are currently staying in South Africa decided to transfer my father's money to foreign account since the law of South Africa prohibit a refugee (asylum seeker) to open any bank account or to be involved in any financial transaction. As the eldest SON of my father, I am saddled with the responsibility of seeking a genuine foreign account where this money could be transferred without the knowledge of my government who are bent on taking everything we have got. I am faced with the dilemma of investing this amount of money in South Af rica for fear of going through the same experience in future since both countries have similar political history. Moreover,the South African Foreign Exchange policy does not allow such investment as an asylum seeker. As a business man,whom I have entrusted my future and of my family in his hands,I must let you know that this transaction is risk free. If you accept to assist me and my family. will aid us in transferring the money into any account you will nominate overseas. This money I intend to use for investment. I have two options for you, firstly you can choose to have a certain percentage of the money for nominating your account for this transaction. Or you can go into partnership with me for the proper profitable investment of the money in your country. Which ever the option you want, feel free to notify me as I have also mapped out 5% of this money for all kinds of expenses incurred in the proccess of this transaction. If you do not prefer a partnership I am willing to give you 20% of the money while the remaining 75% will be for my investment in your country. Contact me with the above telephone number while I implore you to maintain the absolute secrecy required in this transaction. And no matter the level of transaction we are, you must call me on phone first before sending a reply. Please, You should keep this transaction secret and confidential. And send your fax and telephone numbers for easy communication. N/B.I would like you to furnish me with the following: 1) YOUR PRIVATE PHONE AND FAX NUMBERS. 2) YOUR FULL NAME. 3) YOUR FULL ADDRESS. THANKS FOR YOUR CO-OPERATION DAVID KUBA (FOR THE FAMILY)

Dear Sir/Madam, compliments of the day. i got your email address from the south African on line network without wasting your time let me go straight to the point. In my department we discovered sum of $20million Us dollars(Twenty-million Us dollars) in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customers Late MR.THOMPSON MORRIS Age 61 an American who unfortunately lost his life in the plane crash of Alaska Airlines Flight261 which crashed on January- 31- 2000, including his wife and only daughter. Since we got information about his death,we have been expecting his next of kin or relatives to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines. Unfortunately I learned that his supposed next of kin being his only daughter died along with him in the plane crash leaving nobody with the knowledge of this fund behind for the claim.It is therefore upon this discovery that I and two other officials in this department now decided to make business with you and release the money to you as the next of kin or beneficiary of the funds for safety keeping and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we don't want this money to go back into Government treasury asunclaimed bill. The banking law and guidelines here stipulates that such money remained after five years the money will be transferred into banking treasury as unclaimed funds. We agreed that 35% of this money will be for you as foreign partner, while the balance will be for my colleagues and I. I will visit your country for the disbursement according to the percentages indicated above once this money gets into your account. Please be honest to me. Note this transaction is confidential and risk free. As soon as you receive this email you should contact me through my e-mail address. Please note that all necessary arrangement for the smooth release of these funds to you as has been finalized. HOPE TO HEAR FROM YOU SOON. YOURS, LAWSON MNANDI. EMAIL:lawmnandi@yahoo.it

FROM THE DESK OF DR DINKA DOGON BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER . AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK . BURKINA FASO ANNEX. I hope this meets you in good health, My name is Dr Dinka Dogon the manager of bill and exchange at the foreign remittance department of African development bank , Burkina Faso Annex here in Ouagadougou, west africa. In my department we discovered an abandoned sum of Twenty-two Million United States Dollar US$22m dollars in an account, belonging to one of our customer Eng. Christian Eich ,Who died alongside with his entire family on Monday, 31 July, 2000 in a plane crash in paris. Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless some body applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidlines and laws but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I and my colleagues decided to make this business proposal to you and release the money to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we don't want this money to go into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. The banking law and guidline here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed after seven years, the money will be transfered into the bank treasury as unclaimed fund. The request of foreigner as next of kin in this business is occassioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a Burkinabe cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. Therefore, to enable the immediate transfer of this fund to your designated bank account ,you must apply first to the bank as a relation or next of kin of the deceased with a text of application that we will send to you, so we will like you to send to us your private telephone , fax number for easy and effective communication and location where the money will be remitted. Upon receipt of your reply, we will send to you by fax or email the text of the application . we will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch-free and that you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made for the transfer. You should contact us immediately as soon as you receive this letter. Trusting to hear from you immediately. Yours faithfully. Dr Dinka Dogon Bill & Exchange Manager, AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK (A.D.B.BF ANNEX ) _________________________________________________________________ Découvrez le Blog heroic Fantaisy d'Eragon! http://eragon-heroic-fantasy.spaces.live.com/

THANKS IN ANTICIPATION, I am Barr. Charles Brown, A Canadian Attorney based in Manchester, United Kingdom and the personal attorney to Late Mr. Mark Michelle a citizen of France. Late Mr. Mark Michelle was a private oil consultant/ contractor with the Shell Petroleum Development Company in Saudi Arabia before his death, hereinafter shall be referred to as my client. Unfortunate, my client with his wife and three children lost their life in plane clash in 2003. My several attempts to locate any of his relatives as directed by his Bank became void. I had make enquires with his country Embassy and non of his relatives have been traced. PROPOSITION: I decided to contact you purely on the personal conviction of trust and confidence that we can co-operate with each other and do a very lucrative business for our mutual benefits. I want you to give me the needed assistance by allowing me to present you as the next of kin to the deceased and the beneficiary to his estate. The deceased had a deposit valued presently at ($40,800,000.00) and his Bank has issued me a notice to provide his next of kin or beneficiary by will, otherwise the account would be confiscated. Already, i have marked out modalities for achieving my aim of appointing a next of kin as well as transfer the money out of this country, for us to share the money in the ratio of 53% for me and 35% to you, The 2% of the fund will serve as reimbursement of expenses both local and international any of us will make in the course of this transaction. While we shall collectively donate the remaining balance of 10% to Charity homes Organizations. It is my intention to achieve this transfer in a legitimate way, all i required is your honest co-operation, confidentiality and trust to enable us see this transaction through. This is a very legal business that I am very sure of its success and is absolutely risk free. If this proposal is acceptable to you, kindly email following informations to me; 1. Private telephone number and fax number. 2. Your residential address. Further details await you upon a positive response from you. I wait your reply. YOUR PROMPT RESPONSE IS HIGHLY APPRECIATED GOD BLESS YOU Yours faithfully, Bar. Charles Brown

CONFIDENTIAL PROPOSAL FROM. MR.MUHAMMD AMIN THE CHIEF AUDITOR INCHARGE, AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK (ADB). OUAGADOUGOU BURKINA FASO. WEST AFRICA. My Good Friend, How are you doing together with your family? I guessed all is well. My massage should not be a surprise proposal to you because i got your contact information from the international directory in few weeks ago before i decided to contact you on this magnitude and lucrative transaction for our future survival in life. Moreover, i have laid all the solemn trust in you before i decided to disclose this successful & confidential transaction to you. As i have said, I AM MR. MUHAMMD AMIN. THE CHIEF AUDITOR INCHARGE OF FOREIGN REMITTANCE UNIT, AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK OUAGADOUDOU BURKINA-FASO. Now i have the intent to contact you over this financial transaction worth the sum of NINTEEN MILLION, THREE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS ($19,300,000.00 ) for our future success. This is and abandoned sum that belongs to one of our bank foreign customers who died along with his entire family through plane crash disaster since few years ago. Meanwhile i was very fortune to came across the deceased file when i was arranging the old and abandoned customers files in other to sign and submit to the entire bank management for an official re-documentation and audit of the year against 2008. Be informed clearly that it was stated in our banking rules and regulations which was signed lawfully that if such fund remains unclaimed till the period of 6 years started from the date when the beneficiary died, the money will be transferred into the treasury as an unclaimed fund. As a honour and advantage bestowed to our foreign customers base on the rules guilding our bank, it was stated obviously that if you are not a citizen of Burkina Faso , you have the absolute authority to claim the fund hence you are a foreigner despite your differences from the country of origin of the deceased. So the request of you as a foreigner is necessary and legit to apply for the claim and transfer of the fund smoothly into your reliable bank account as the NEXT OF KIN OR EXTENDED RELATIVE to the deceased costomer. On the transfer of this fund into your account, { 39% } being ( US$7,527,000.00) will be your share in respect of the account provision and your assistance rendered during the transfer of the fund into your bank account,{ 52% } being (US$10,036,000.00) will be my share being the codinator and the pillar of the transaction while the rest { 9% } being (US$1,737,000.00) will be shared to the respectable Organisations Centers such as Charity Organisation, Motherless Babies homes, and helpless disabled people in the World. Now, if you are really sure of your trustworthy, accountability,confidentiality on this transaction, contact me and agree that you will not change your mind to cheat or disappoint me when the fund have getting into your account. Besides you should not entertain any fear because i am sure of the success as an insider in the bank. Please reply with the assurance, include your private telephone and fax numbers necessary for facilitate an easy communication in this transaction. As soon as you reply , give me a call through my private telephone number on ( 00 226 70437906 ) so that i will let you know the next step to follow in order to finalize this transaction immediately. I expect your urgent communication and my best regard to you and all members of your family. Mr_muhammd_amin@yahoo.fr Yours sincerely, mr. MUHAMMD AMIN _________________________________________________________________ Windows Live Spaces : créez votre blog à votre image ! http://www.windowslive.fr/spaces

DEAR FRIEND, PLEASE, REPLY TO MY PRIVATE E-MAIL f_remit_dept@latinmail.com I AM MR.HASSAN BILLY, BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER AT THE FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPARTMENT OF BANK INTERNATIONAL OF BURKINA (BIB) OUAGA-BURKINA FASO WITH DUE RESPECT AND REGARDS, I HAVE DECIDED TO CONTACT YOU ON A BUSINESS TRANSACTION THAT WILL BE VERY BENEFICIAL TO BOTH OF US AT THE END OF THE TRANSACTION. DURING MY INVESTIGATION AND AUDITING IN MY DEPARTMENT, I CAME ACROSS A VERY HUGE SUM OF MONEY BELONGING TO A DECEASED PERSON, A FOREIGNER WHO DIED IN A PLANE CRASH. THE FUND HAS BEEN DORMANT IN HIS ACCOUNT WITH THE BANK WITHOUT ANY CLAIM OF THE FUND IN OUR CUSTODY EITHER FROM HIS FAMILY OR RELATION BEFORE OUR DISCOVERY TO THIS DEVELOPMENT. ALTHOUGH PERSONALLY, I KEPT THIS INFORMATION SECRET WITHIN MYSELF TO ENABLE THE WHOLE PLANS AND IDEA BE PROFITABLE AND SUCCESSFUL DURING THE TIME OF EXECUTION, THE AMOUNT INVOLVED IS USD$9.5M, NINE MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND U.S DOLLARS.) MEANWHILE THE WHOLE ARRANGEMENT AND DIRECTIVES NEEDED TO PUT CLAIM OVER THIS FUND AS THE NEXT OF KIN TO THE DECEASED, WILL BE FORWARD TO YOU UPON YOUR ACCEPTANCE. INFORMATION WILL BE RELAYED TO YOU AS SOON AS YOU INDICATE YOUR INTEREST AND WILLINGNESS TO ASSIST ME AND ALSO BENEFIT YOUR SELF TO THIS GREAT BUSINESS OPPORTUNITY. IN FACT, I COULD HAVE DONE THIS DEAL ALONE BUT BECAUSE OF MY POSITION IN THIS COUNTRY AS A CIVIL SERVANT, WE ARE NOT ALLOWED TO OPERATE A FOREIGN ACCOUNT AND WOULD EVENTUALLY RAISE AN EYE BROW ON MY SIDE DURING THE TIME OF TRANSFER BECAUSE I WORK IN THIS BANK. THIS IS THE ACTUAL REASON WHY IT WILL REQUIRE A SECOND PARTY OR FELLOW WHO WILL FORWARD CLAIMS AS THE NEXT OF KIN TO THE BANK AND ALSO PRESENT A FOREIGN ACCOUNT WHERE HE/ SHE WILL NEED THE MONEY TO BE TRANSFERRED INTO ON HIS REQUEST AS IT MAY BE, AFTER DUE VERIFICATION AND CLARIFICATION TO DESIGNATED BANK ACCOUNT. I WILL NOT FAIL TO INFORM YOU THAT THIS TRANSACTION IS 100% RISK FREE,ON SMOOTH CONCLUSION OF THIS TRANSACTION, YOU WILL BE ENTITLED TO 35% OF THE TOTAL SUM AS GRATIFICATION, WHILE 65% WILL BE FOR ME PLEASE, YOU HAVE BEEN ADVISED TO KEEP TOP SECRET AS WE ARE STILL IN SERVICE AND INTEND TO RETIRE FROM SERVICE AFTER I CONCLUDE THIS DEAL WITH YOU. I WILL BE MONITORING THE WHOLE SITUATION HERE IN THE BANK UNTIL YOU CONFIRM THE MONEY IN YOUR ACCOUNT AND ASK ME TO COME DOWN TO YOUR COUNTRY FOR SUBSEQUENT SHARING OF THE FUND ACCORDING TO PERCENTAGES PREVIOUSLY INDICATED AND FURTHER INVESTMENT, EITHER IN YOUR COUNTRY OR ANY OTHER COUNTRY YOU MAY ADVICE US TO INVEST IN. ALL OTHER NECESSARY INFORMATION WILL BE SENT TO YOU WHEN I HEAR FROM YOU. I SUGGEST YOU GET BACK TO ME AS SOON AS POSSIBLE STATING YOUR WISH IN THIS DEAL. REPLY TO MY PRIVATE E-MAIL f_remit_dept@latinmail.com PLEASE ALSO, I WILL LIKE YOU TO VISIT THE WEBSITE OF THE CRASH BELOW: www.cnn.com/2003/WORLD/africa/07/20/kenya.crash/index.html www.news24.com/News24/Africa/News/0,,2-11-1447_1390626,00.html BEST REGARD, MR.HASSAN BILLY. ¡Vive la pasión del fútbol! Toda la Copa América, en Starmedia http://pan.segundosfuera.com/copaamerica/

My name is Sandra Williams from United Kingdom, I am 18 years old. My letter might come to you as a surprise due to the fact that we have not meet in person for the first time or even being in correspondence before, but I believe it takes just a day to know some either physically or by correspondence. I believe that it takes a day to know some one either physically or by correspondence. I got your email address from the internet and decided to seek for your urgent assistance as I am having a big problem with my stepmother since after the death of my father. some months ago my father died from Heart operation. I am making this contact to you in respect of 10, 000,000.00 British Pounds, which I inherited from my late father. My late father was an International OIL dealer. My problem actually started when my stepmother called me and said that I must submit to her and her Children the deposit Certificate of 10, 000,000.00 British Pounds, which my late father gave me as a proof that he really deposited the money in a bank, I refused to submit the Deposit Certificate to them because the money was legally "WILLED" to me by my late father before he died, but out of greediness they want to use intimidation to take away the Deposit Certificate from me and then claim the money on their own. since the death of my father, my stepmother and her Children has being Threatening to kill me if I do not give them the Deposit Certificate of the 10, 000,000.00 British Pounds, which I inherited from my late father for my future survival. They seized my International passport and bit hell out of me because of the Deposit Certificate, but I refused to surrender the Deposit Certificate to them because they also inherited majority of my late father's wealth including his companies. Their desire is to frustrate my life because I don't use to be in good terms with them because of past history concerning the death of my mother, I was told that my stepmother used her friend to poison my mother in other to become the only wife, so because of the story I heard about the death of my mother, I ran away from the family house in other to protect the deposit certificate and my life from my wicked stepmother and her Children whose desire is to take away my legal right and let me go as tray. Now, I need as urgent as possible a reliable and trustworthy foreigner who can receive this money for me in his or her country pending when I will arrange another International passport to visit the person in his or her country for investment as I wish to run away from the country in other to secure my life from my wicked stepmother and her children who are now hunting me like a prey. I wish to run to another country and settle down with the money as they use to say that prevention is better than cure, so I wish to protect my life for better tomorrow. At the present time, I am in a hiding place arranging myself for traveling outside the country. If you can help me in this my time of sorrow, I promise to reward you with 20% of the total sum, while 80% will be kept for me into your personal bank account pending my arrival to your country. Please help me to safe guide my only hope for survival. I am looking forward for your sincere and honest assistance to me. Reply to my private E-Mail Address: s_williams1989@yahoo.com.hk Sincerely, Sandra.

Dear Friend,   Permit the manner with which I am seeking your assistance but I am short of options and have no other choice. I am Jonathan Charles from the hospitality state ( Mississippi ), an army contractor attached to the US Military force in Iraq . The reason why I’m contacting you is to explain my findings to you and to seek for your assistance to enable you contributes immensely to the actualization of my dream.     I am attached to the US army for the sole purpose of reconstruction work in some parts of Iraq . As you know very well Iraq is gradually undergoing a rebuilding process in some parts and there is much need for reconstruction which was why I was invited. I evaluate the level of destruction and offer professional advice in line with the way they intend rebuilding and reconstructing damaged facilities. Work has been risky no doubt and challenging as sometimes we are faced hard on with armed insurgents where we lose some soldiers during confrontation. I have had my own share of losses as I lost a friend whom I have known for 12 years.   On the 27th day of March 2007, at about 11:00 hrs during a normal inspection routine along Haifa Street where there is long rough high-rise buildings which were built and occupied by the late Saddam Hussein when he was alive, I with other 3 soldiers proceeded to a marked site and as I commenced evaluation work while I was closely guided by soldiers, I discovered an unusual bulge in a cellar which I presumed to be a storage room, I decided to have a look at it, only for me to kick the metal covering and find a metal boxes (5 in number) piled on top one another which were locked with a padlock each with a sign written in each of them.   Upon forcing the boxes open, we discovered several guns, amour and some boxes amongst which two contained guns and bullets, one filled with hard drugs (heroine) and the other two to my amazement contained some US Dollars and kilograms of alluvial Gold, which we counted and discovered that the money in one of the boxes amounted to $9.2 Million. I believe the boxes owned and linked to the Al Qaeda and Ayman al-Zawahiri.   I however instructed them to keep this in high secrecy so that we can have the money and alluvial Gold to our selves, they all agreed to the plan of getting the money out of the country, but first we had to hide the money and alluvial Gold in some safe and untraceable location. We secretly kept the boxes in a safer place after which we handed over the drugs and the weapons to our superiors. I am now in desperate need of a “Reliable and Trustworthy” person like you who would receive, secure and protect these boxes containing the US Dollars and alluvial Gold for me until my assignment elapses here. We cannot afford to leave the boxes here in Iraq for any reason since Iraq is getting unsafe and dangerous everyday. We have no idea what could happen next as everything remains inconclusive at this point. I am fully aware of what your thoughts would be next, but on receiver of your response, I will send my picture as well as my Identity, for you to know whom you are dealing with.   I assure and promise to give you 15% of this fund and some quantity of the alluvial Gold, please assure me of your keeping this topmost secret within you so that my job would not be jeopardized.     My Sincere Regards, Jonathan Charles. You can contact me with my private email: jonathancharles01@yahoo.co.in   Get news, entertainment and everything you care about at Live.com. Check it out!

From: Barrister Gareth Jones Tel: +44 703 184 4817 Fax: +44 870 479 8201 DX: 77 LONDON CHANCERY LANE WC2 Email: barr.garethjones@fsmail.net Attn: Sir/Madam, My name is Barrister Gareth Jones, a lawyer in the Chambers of Nabarro Nathanson (Legal Practitioners) in London. I am writing this letter to you to intimate you of a pending transaction I want to execute with you privately. Anyway I got your contact through one of the Internet Reference Directories in my Chambers. One of my valued clients - Mr. Antonio Montoya died together with his lovely wife Late Antonio Montoya died on the Flight 11, a Boeing 767-200, which was enroute to Los Angeles from Boston during the terrorist attack on America back in 2001. I was his personal lawyer and the Executor of his Will. There are no further traces of any of his next-of-kin in his native Country. As his personal lawyer and Executor of his Will, I know late Antonio Montoya kept about GBP 9.2 million in the Vaults of a bank here in London. This money had been taken to the bank late on the evening of his departure to USA; hence the money was only accepted and registered by the bank while it was kept in the Vault waiting for Montoya's return, which was never to be. I have since confirmed with the bank that the money is still in the bank's vault. Ever since 2001 this money has been in this account untouched! Now, how do you come in and what is your business with all this? I am sure this is the question you would be asking me? Simple, As the personal lawyer to late Antonio Montoya and since vital document relating to this money is kept with my Chambers, I decided that I intimate you of this development, with your co-operation, I can present you to bank as the Next-of-Kin to the late Antonio Montoya. After proper verification of this Claim by the bank this money will be transferred to your bank account hence you come in as the Next-of-Kin to late Antonio Montoya. How do we do it? The document showing that this money is kept in the bank's vault is kept in my Law Chambers. I, as the lawyer and Executor of late Antonio Montoya's Will/Last Testament will put your name in this Will as the Beneficiary of this money kept in the bank's vault. I will submit the Will/Last Testament to the Bank to contact you and start processing transfer of this money to your bank account according to the last wishes of my Client - late Mr. Montoya for further administration to other members of the family. I am the Executor of late Montoya's Will. All I need to do is to re-make the late Mr. Montoya's Will/Last Testament to include your name as the beneficiary and submit same to the bank and introduce you, the bank writes you to confirm this, then transfer process starts without delays. I am the Executor of this Will and the Bank knows it too. The mode of sharing this money will be discussed when we agree to work together on this transaction. What do you think about this? While I look forward to hearing from you soon, absolute confidentiality and secrecy remain very important in this transaction. Thank you and God bless you. Barrister Gareth Jones.

FROM THE DESK OF DR ASINTHE NIGNAN.  BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER BANK OF AFRICAN . OUAGADOUGOU, BURKINA FASO. WEST AFRICA Dear  , how are you,first i will explain my self in brief for you before we proceed.I am the manager of bill and exchange at the foreign remittance department of BANK OF AFRICAN (BOA)  I am writing to Seek your interest over a business , In my department we discovered an abandoned sum of $15.5m US dollars (fifteen million five US dollars). In an account that belongs to one of our foreign customer who died along with his entire family in November 15th 2001 in a plane crash at abidjan cote'voire. Since we  got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless his next of kin or relative applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died along side with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I and two other officials in my department now  decided to excape with the fund,and as such we vial to make this business proposal to you so that my bank will release the fund into your account as the next of kin to our bank deceased customer for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for claims and we don't want this money to go into the bank treasury. Infact i know the fund will not even go into the bank treasury,but our top bank officials(directors)will only share it among themselves into their accounts. The Banking law and guideline here in burkina faso stipulates that if any customer account or property remains unserviceable or dormant,and unclaimed after five years, the account will be confiscated and transfered into the Bank treasury as unclaimed bill. The request of  foreigner as next of kin in this business is occasioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a Burkinabe cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. We agree that 30% of this money will be for you as foreign partner,inrespect to the provision of a foreign account,and your imense contribution to champion the course of transfering the fund to your  account.  10 % will be set aside forexpenses incurred by the both party during the business and 60 % would be for me and my colleagues. There after I and my colleagues will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentages indicated. Therefore to enable my bank transfer the fund into your account,i will send to you the text of application which you will send to my bank as next of kin to the deceased customer and that will be when you indicate your interest in the business, you must apply first to the bank as relations or next of kin of our bank deceased indicating your bank name, your bank account number, your private telephone and fax number for easy and effective communication and location where in the money will be remitted . Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or email the text of the application. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction  is risk-free and that you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required informations will be perfectly made for you to champion the course of the transaction with my bank without any hitch or risk . You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this letter. Trusting to hear from you immediately. Your’s sincerely, DR ASINTHE NIGNAN. BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER(BOA Hotmail to go? Get your Hotmail, news, sports and much more! Check out the New MSN Mobile

Dear Sir, With due respect, trust and humility, I write you this proposal believing that it will receive the most desired attention from you even as we have not had any previous correspondence, Although, I am constrained by insufficient information about you, but I will express in full the main objectives of this proposal . I am Mr.CHRIS ANDERSON Personal Aide and in-law to the former President of the Liberian Mr. Charles Taylor, who resigned his post due to pressure from the International Community in order to maintain peace in west African Region. His Excellency who is currently behind bars at a U.N.-backed court in Hague Netherlands, facing 11 counts of war crimes during the country's 1991-2002 civil war. Liberian Government In conjunction with Sierra Leone Government has agreed on June 20, 2006 for security reason to Hand him over to U.N War crime Special Court in Hague, Netherlands. His Excellency who was arrested on a boarder between Nigeria and Cameroun of which he instructed me to escape with all his vital documents so that he could face a U.N.-backed tribunal for war crime charges which he is now currently facing. but before this new unfolding events. Though our original plan was after successful crossing to Cameroun un-noticed, I will proceed to Accra Ghana totake the task of arranging for the immediate evacuation of the money in whish he deposited in the custody of Security Finance Company before it will be discovered by International Community or Liberian Government.See the website for more details http://jurist.law.pitt.edu/paperchase/2006/03/breaking-news-charles-taylor-captured.php http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/2963086.stm http://www.cnn.com/2006/WORLD/africa/03/29/taylor.nigeria/index.html http://somalinet.com/news/world/Africa/10893 His Excellency, while in jail has mandated me to secure the co-operation of a trust worthy and reliable firm or individual as fund managers to whom he will entrust certain amount of money to be managed within the period while he is in jail, on the terms as shall be agreed by both parties. The new government in Liberia lead by Mrs. Ellen Johnson-Sir leaf has initiated moves to probe Mr. Taylor’s governance while in office with a view of recovering his assets and deposits and repatriating such to the country as was the case with the Late Head of State of the Federal Republic of Nigeria, Gen. Sanni Abacha as advised by the International Community on Liberian Government. On the wake of hostilities in Liberia and the break out of war between the rebels and the allied forces, the Liberian government being under an arms embargo by the U.N could not import arms officially, so Mr. Taylor resolved to illegal arms deal from the West African Region of Ghana, which was transacted by cash monies, within this period, he succeeded in depositing a total sumof USD$115M only, in cash money derived from the arms dealing custody of Security Finance Company in Accra Ghana. Which is the trust company from where the arms deal was financed? we intends to execute a deed of conveyance of this deposit to a capable and trust worthy firm or individual who will immediately effect a change of beneficiary on the deposit and release it from the custody of Security Finance Company by way of terminating the deposit contract to avoid any trace and repatriation of the deposit by the new government in Liberia. Terms of the transaction shall be discussed and agreement entered into when you indicate your ability to handle and manage funds of this magnitude under a strict confidential understanding.. Please treat as most confidential due to the sensitive information given in here strictly to you. Yours sincerely CHRIS ANDERSON Personal Aide to the former Liberian President

Mr.Solomon Clarke, Bank of Scotland Limited, HBOS Treasury Services, 33,Old Broad Street, London EC2N 1HZ.     I am writing to seek your consent in a private and confidential matter regarding some funds unaccounted for in our bank here in London during the last 2006 business year. I feel quite safe dealing with you in this important business. Though, this medium (Internet) has been greatly abused; I choose to reach you through it because it still remains the fastest medium of communication.I have the courage to look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable for this important business believing that you will never let me down either now or in future.   Your major role would be to provide either an existing bank account or to set up a new Bank account immediately to receive this money and get 30% of the total funds as commission. There is practically no risks involved, the transaction will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect us from any breach of the law, it will be simply a bank-to-bank transfer, and all I need from you is to stand claim as the beneficiary(next of kin) so that my head office can order the transfer to your designated bank account under few working days.   I am Mr.Solomon Clarke, a regional manager of Bank Of Scotland Limited, and I write you this proposal in good faith; I am married with five lovely kids. It is my duty as the regional manager to send in financial report to my head office in the capital city at the end of each business year. On the course of the lAst year 2006 business report, I discovered the sum of Twenty six million eight hundred and fifty thousand  pounds  sterlings 26,850,000.00. The fund is of clean origin. The owner of this account is a foreigner, a program leader. Untill his death. I will provide all necessary information needed in order to claim this money. Hoping in God that you will never let me down now and in  future. ok!The Late Prime Minister, Mr. RafikBahaa Edine  Hariri.(November 1, 1944 - February 14, 2005), was a Lebanese self-made billionaire and business tycoon, and was five times Prime Minister of Lebanon (1992-1998 and 2000-2004) before his last resignation from office on October 20, 2004.The late Rafik Hariri died on February 14, 2005 when explosives equivalent to around 300 kg of C4 were detonated as his motorcade drove past the Saint George Hotel in the Lebanese capital, for more information please log on to (http://www.hariri.info/). Our head office is not aware of Funds and will never be aware of it. I have placed this funds on what we call escrow call account with no beneficiary and as an officer of this bank i cannot be directly connected to this money, hence i contacted you. If you accept to work with me I will appreciate it very much as you are the first and the only person I am contacting for this particular transaction.   We will start the first transfer with sixteen million pounds, upon successful transfer without any disappointment from your side, we shall re-apply for the payment of the remaining amount to your account. At this juncture i wish to tell you what prompted me to package this deal. I have a 9-year old daughter who has leukemia, disease of the blood, and she needs a bone marrow transplant or she will die. I want this transplanting to be done in any good children hospital in your country if there is one.   Once this fund is transferred into your account, I shall resign from my job and bring my family to start a new life in your country. I would be grateful if you would help me in looking out for good investment oppurtunities with my own part of the money in a very profitable business. I have worked for this bank for the past 15 years yet I have nothing to show for it, I really need your assistance to secure this fund as soon as possible.   Reply me immediately through my most private email address: solomonclarkeclarke@yahoo.co.uk  as soon as you receive this message so we,so that we can go over the details. Send also your Private mobile phone and fax nos: for more proper elaborrations.   Truly yours, Mr.Solomon Clarke.

DELETE button is history. Unlimited mail storage is just a click away.

Dear friend, I am Mr.BALA KABORE,personal assistant Branch Manager of Bank Of Africa(BOA)Ouagadougou Burkina Faso,West Africa. I want to inquire from you if you can handle this transaction for mutual benefits/life opportunity for you and me.The transaction is about seeking your consent to present you as the next of kin/ beneficiary of the US$4.3 million dollars,(four million,three hundred thousand united states dollars), and who is a customer to the bank where i work.He died in a Kenya plane crash 2003.The Fund is currently in a suspense account awaiting claim, the bank made a public notice that they are ready to release this fund to any of his relatives abroad.I am as convinced as believing that you will provide me, the very needed urgent assistance, hence a viable bank account by which we can effect the transfer of the fund.Because,due to our position as top bank officials, we are not allowed to operate a foreign account, that is why i needed you to assist me in providing a foreign bank where this FUND will be transfered for immediate disbursement according to the percentages.You can view this site to know more. http://www.eastandard.net/archives/cl/hm_news/news.php articleid=35537.THEREFORE,by virtue of its nature as being utterly CONFIDENTIAL, top secret should be maintained please!,because i am still in the active service i do not need any form of implication especially now i'm in the verge of my retirement to endanger my carear at last!. Since we got the information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless some body applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines and laws.In that regard, i decided to seek your consent for this prospective opportunity. Have it at the back of your mind, that the transaction does not involve any RISK, and does not need much engagement from you, since i am familiar with this kind of transaction being an insider. Necessary modalities will be worked out to enable us carry out the fund claim under a legitimate arrangement. I have resolved to offer you 30% of the total fund, 10% for sundry expenses that may be incurred during the process of executing this transaction and 60% percent for me.I will give you more details about the transaction when I receive your affirmative response,more clarification information. Contact me through my private e-mail address:(bala_kabore2003@yahoo.ca) . I'm waiting to hear from you soon. Thanks and God bless. Mr.Bala Kabore. _________________________________________________________________ Gagnez des pc Windows Vista avec Live.com http://www.image-addict.fr/

From: Mrs Farah al-Hashemi Address: Chiang Rai hospital 31-12 Chiang Rai - Lampoon Rd, ,Chiang Rai Thailand Dearest Beloved, Thank you for the attention beeing given to my mail.I am Mrs.Farah al-Hashemi, The wife of iraq military finance corps Chief, who was incharge of the payment of the military salary during his life service time . I am 58 years old, i am now receiving treatment in the hospital. It's quite obvious that I won't live Longer according to my doctor as i am sufering from my kidney transplant illness,this is because my illness has gotten to a very bad stage. My late husband died from the British and American attacks over my country ,and during the period of our marriage we had two male children Musa and Idris.After the death of my husband , I inherited some money which my late husband deposited with a Security Finance Company in Thailand for safety.The doctor has advised me that I may not live long, so I now decided to contact you to assist my two sons to claim this money From where it was deposited and guide them for investment as you are a potential business man. My family will be interested in doing business in your country, thefore i would like to seek your assistance and help.I am interested particularly in properties , but your advise on other areas of private sector would be highly appreciated, i am in believe that you would be of great help in guiding my two sons to a sucessful exploration of the investment potentials of your country , which guarantees good capital returns and human security .As a result of this, i can take you in confidence bassically due of the source of the fund , hereby believing that your assistance will be profitable to us. The amount in question is USD$12 Million .I will appreciate your willingness to carry this transactions the gratification remark which will be determined as soon as i hear from you i have maped out 20%, for your assistance and 5% would be used for the re-embursement of any expenses that is encurred during on the process of this transaction . Lastly, I honestly pray that this money when transferred to your country will be used for the said purpose of investing in the industry, because I have come to find out that wealth acquisition without Allah is vanity upon vanity. I await your urgent reply to enable me up-date you with more information and how to proced. Do feel free to ask me any question if you wish to as my husbands death has blocked every trace of this money from us,the documentations relating to the deposit of this fund are all intact with my first son for your verification . you can get back to me with this email farashemi@myway.com. I await to hearing from you soonest. Yours Sincerely. Mrs Farah al-Hashemi

Dear Friend I am Sir John Kempwelch one of the Director of HSBC Bank, London, United Kingdom. On the 2nd of January 2005, I received a call that one of my customer died in the Tsunami Disaster with his wife and only child while on vacation at Phuket Island in Thailand. Since then I have made several enquiries to locate any of my customer's extended relatives and until date have not succeeded. I have contacted you to assist in repatriating the money left behind by my client before it gets confiscated by our bank or declared unserviceable by our bank where this deposit is lodged. Now, the bank Directors has called a board meeting regarding this Fund. So my main motive right now is to share this great opportunity with you by presenting you as the Next of Kin to the Deceased since all his banking details are with me as his personal Account Officer. And the deceased Account valued at US$17.5M Since I have been unsuccessful in locating the biological relatives of my late client, I hereby seek your consent to present you to the bank as next-of-kin of the deceased since you are a foreigner, so that the proceeds of this account valued at US$17.5M can be transferred to you as inheritance and thereafter, you and I can share the money; 50% to me and 40% to you, while 10% will be donated to the Tsunami Disaster Charity Fund. We shall start the first transfer with US$5,000.000.00 (Five Million United States Dollars only), upon the successful actualization of the first transfer without any disappointment from your side, we shall re-apply for the payment of the remaining amount to your account. I have the original copy of Certificate of Deposit of the funds, which will be used to substantiate our inheritance claims. All I require is your consent and honest co-operation to enable us see the deal through. Furthermore, I guarantee that the transaction will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. Please contact me if you are interested immediately via my personal email:jkpw1968@yahoo.co.uk to enable us commence on the transaction. Best regards, Sir John Kempwelch. ___________________________________________________________________________ Mail enviado desde el servicio WebMail del Sitio Informática del Caribe - http://www.infocaribe.com.co

I have a new email address!

You can now email me at: mrs_herrina_robinson030@yahoo.co.uk URGENT REPLY. - Dear friend,My name is Mrs.Herrina Robinson. A citizen of the Republic of Sierra Leone I am the wife to Mr. Donald Robinson who worked with former President of Liberian. Mr. Charles Taylor, he was one of the special advisers of former president Charles Taylor, my husband was assassinated on the 29/03/2006 during the arrest of former President Taylor between the Nigerian and Cameroon boarder.I inherited a total sum of ($16, 000, 000, 00.US DOLLARS,SIXTEEN MILLION UNITED STATE DOLLRS) from my late husband, this money which is on Ceiled in a Metallic Trunk Box is deposited with a Security and Finance Company in a West African country called Accra Ghana. This Deposit was coded under a Secret Arrangement as a Family treasure. This means that the Security Company does not know the content of this Trunk box that was deposited in Accra Ghana under a diplomatic coverage for Safe keeping. My main purpose of sending you this mail is because of the way I found you and perhaps trust worthy to give you this priority of shipping the Box of Money to any address that you think is very secure and save in your country with your percentage which we shall discuss on soon. In fact, since the Death of my late husband, their family brothers have been seriously chasing me around with my Children.constant Treats because my husband is no more with me again they tried to suppress me so that they might have the documents of his landed properties and confiscate them, They have successfully collected all his propert ies, yet they never stopped there, they told me to surrender all the belonging account of my late husband, which I did, but I never disclose to them this deposit with the security, company in Accra Ghana. Because this is where my future stand and destiny lies upon.The family of my late husband never aware of the secret existence of this deposit which I made with the security company and they can never be aware of it. Out of fear of my late husbands family, and when the situation becomes uncontrollable because of pressure on me from the Government of the Republic of Liberian, I decide to look for a trust worthy person who could assist me retrieve this box of money from the security company for onward lodgments into his account for the purpose of future investment. Consider my situation’s a widow and come to my rescue. There is need for urgent action because I'm paying $20 dollars per day as a demurrage to the security company for safe keeping of this consignment. I will send you the Authorization Certificate information’s to call them in my next mail which is the Certificate of deposit that they gave on the very day when the box of money was deposited under their company. I give thanks immensely for your co-operation as I look forward to hear from you soon. Contact me through my current private Email:(mrs_herrina100@hotmail.com) I wish you All the best, And God bless. Regards, Mrs. Herrina Robinson.

Good day, I am Mr.Christopher Wilson, staff of Kleinwort Benson. I am contacting you concerning a deceased customer and an investment he placed under our banks management three years ago.I Would respectfully request that you keep the contents of this mail confidential and respect the integrity of the information you come by as a result of this mail. I am contacting you independently of our investigation and no one is informed of this communication. I would like to intimate you with certain facts that I believe would be of interest to you. In the year 2003, the subject matter; came to our bank to engage in business discussions with our private banking division. He informed us that he had a financial portfolio of Six Million United States dollars, which he wished to have us turn over (invest) on his behalf. I was the officer assigned to his case, I made numerous suggestions in line with my duties as the de-facto chief operations officer of the private banking sector then, especially given the volume of funds he wished to put into our bank. We met on numerous occasions prior to any investments being placed.I encouraged him to consider various growth funds with prime ratings. In mid 2004, he asked that the money be liquidated because he needed to make an urgent investment requiring cash payments in Helsinki- Finland. He directed that I liquidate the funds and deposit it with a security firm. I informed him that my Bank would have to make special arrangements to have this done and in order not to circumvent due process. Cash movement across boarders has become especially strict since the incidents of 9/11. I contacted my affiliate and made the funds available to the security firm. I undertook all the processes and made sure I followed his precise instructions to the letter and had the funds deposited with the security firm. The Security Firm is a specialist private firm that accepts deposits from high net worth individuals and blue chip corporations that handle valuable products or undertake transactions that need immediate access to cash. This small and highly private organization is familiar especially to the highly placed and well-connected organizations. In line with instructions, the money was deposited with the security firm. The deceased told me he wanted the money there in anticipation of his arrival from Norway later that week. This was the last communication we had, this transpired around 25th of November 2004.In June last year, we got a call from the security firm informing us about the inactivity of that particular portfolio. I made futile efforts to locate the deceased. I immediately passed the task of locating him to the internal investigations department of Kleinwort Benson.Four days later, information started to trickle in, apparently our client was dead. A person who suited his description was declared dead of a heart attack in canne, in Southern part of France.We were soon enough to identify the body and cause of death was confirmed. In his bio-data form, he listed no next of kin. In the field of private banking, opening an account with us means no one will know of its existence, accounts are rarely held under a name; depositors use numbers and codes to make the accounts anonymous. This investigation has for the past months been unfruitful, We've used our private investigation affiliate companies to get to the root of the problem. It is this investigation that resulted in my being furnished with your details as a possible relative of the deceased. According to practice, The Security Firm will by the end of this financial year broadcast a request for statements of claim to Kleinwort Benson, failing to receive viable claims they will most probably revert the deposit back to Kleinwort Benson.This will result in the money entering the Kleinwort Benson accounting system and the portfolio will be out of my hands and out of the private banking division.This will not happen if I have my way. What I wish to relate to you will smack of unethical practice but I want you to understand something. It is only an outsider to the banking world who finds the internal politics of the banking world aberrational. The world of private banking especially is fraught with huge rewards for those that occupy certain offices and oversee certain portfolios. You should have begun by now to put together the general direction of what I propose. There is Six Million dollars deposited in a security firm, I alone have the deposit details and they will release the deposit to no one unless I instruct them to do so. I alone know of the existence of this deposit for as far as my Bank is concerned. My proposal:I now seek your permission to present you as a next of kin to the deceased, as all documentations will be carefully worked to make you the beneficiary to the funds $6,000 000 00 (Six Million United states Dollar) ; I am prepared to place you in a position to instruct The security Firm to release the deposit to you as the closest surviving relation. Upon receipt of the deposit,I am prepared to share the money with you. That is: I will simply nominate you as the next of kin and have them release the deposit to you. We share the proceeds 60/40.I would have gone ahead to ask that the funds be released to me, but that would have drawn a straight line to me and my involvement in claiming the deposit. We can fine-tune this based on our interactions am aware of the consequences of this proposal. I ask that if you find no interest in this project that you should discard this mail. I ask that you do not be vindictive and destructive. If my offer is of no appeal to you, delete this message and forget I ever contacted you. Do not destroy my career because you do not approve of my proposal. I am not a criminal and what I do, I do not find against good conscience, this may be hard for you to understand, but the dynamics of my industry dictates that I make this move. Such opportunities only come ones' way once in a lifetime. I cannot let this chance pass me by, for once I find myself in total control of my destiny.These chances wont pass me by. I ask that you do not destroy my chance, if you will not work with me let me know and let me move on with my life but do not destroy me. I am a family man and this is an opportunity to provide them with new opportunities. There is a reward for this project and it is a task well worth undertaking. I have evaluated the risks and the only risk I have here is from you refusing to work with me and alerting my bank. If you give me positive signals, I will initiate this process towards a conclusion. I wish to inform you that should you contact me via official channels; I will deny knowing you and about this project. I repeat, I do not want you contacting me through my official phone lines nor do I want you contacting me through my official email account. Contact me only through the numbers I will provide for you and also through this email address. I do not want any direct link between you and myself. My official lines are not secured lines as they are periodically monitored to assess our level of customer care in line with our Total Quality Management Policy.Please observe this instruction religiously. Please, again, note that I am a family man, I have a wife and children. I send you this mail not without a measure of fear as to what the consequences, but I know within me that nothing ventured is nothing gained and that success and riches never come easy or on a platter of gold. This is the one truth I have learned from my private banking clients. Do not betray my confidence. Kindly send your response to my private email:christopherwilson77@yahoo.com I await your response. Mr.Christopher Wilson

My name is Quien Jelo I,m a single . I come from Sierra leone.dear I,m interesting to be your friend after seeing your profile details here as i want to relocate to your area soonest . I need to hear from you and have something important to discuss with you . I need your help over my fund clearance and transfer for investment and will write you in details once i hear from you. and i will send my photos and Details for you to know me properly once i hear back from you and need your direct private email MY DATAS: MY NAME: MISS QUIEN JELO MY AGE: 25 YERARS MY OCCUPATION: MEDICAL STUDENT BEFORE THE WAR STARTED AND IN LEVEL 2 MARITAL STATUS: SINGLE AND NO BABY YET NATIONALITY: SIERRA LEONE MY FATHERS DATAS: HIS NAME: MR. PATEL JELO OCCUPATION: EXPORTER OF GOLD DURST AGE BEFORE HIS DEATH : 52 NATIONALITY: SIERRA LEONE Amount deposited for us in the finance company is valued $9.5 which i need your help for the clearance and transfer into your country where i want to relocate and have a good life. can we talk about it.you can send me through my e-mail jelo_lover1981@yahoo.fr and phone to reach me is 00229-90988269 i want to relocate to your area and have decided to confide to u in details all about Me and my fund and need your help over the clearance and transfer over there which i want to relocate for living and investment and your kind help is required i trust you 100% and have confidence in you and you have all the qualities i need for the investment of our fund in good investment and i know you will be able to take good care of me and my younger brother and you will help us to control our fund after clearance into your account. meanwhile, i have told my brother all about you and i have also informed him that i have told you about our coming over to you and about our fund which i need your help for the clearance and transfer to into your account for investment. he asked me how can i trust you without even knowing you better, i told my brother that Am a child of God and God do not dissapoint and i was directed to contact you immediately i saw your profile. But firstly, i will like to tell you who am so that you will understand and comprehend my point clearly . My name is Miss Quien Jelo and am here in Benin Republic with my younger brother in a hotel called hotel colombo which we arrived two days now because of big war in that country called Ivory Coastr that lead to the death of my father ad mother living me and my younger brother alive and we are from Sierra Leone-Bo and lives in a country called Abidjan - Cote d'Ivoire but here in Benin Republic we entered as a result of the war in that country which lead to the death of my father and mother living me and david alone on earth.And here in benin republic we entered as a refugee though we are not in the refugee camp and that is why we have access to internet to talk to you. We came here recently and we are staying in a hotel. Please we need your assitance and help and that is why we are writting you now. Before the death of my father, he used my name to deposit some money as his next of kin in a FINANCE COMPANY HERE IN BENIN REPUBLIC. THE TOTAL AMOUNT DEPOSITED HERE FOR US IS VALUED AT $9.5 MILLION DOLLARS. And am standing as the beneficiary but cannot lay claim because here they do not allow refugees to operate account in the bank here and the finance company has contacted us to come and have our fund cleared . My late father was exporters of gold and diamond to european countries before his death. All i need from you is to help us get the total money transfered into your account for investment once we change the beneficiary in your name and favour as the person we authorise and empower for the clearance . WE NEED THE FOLLOWING TO ENABLE US CHANGE THE BENEFICIARY IN YOUR FAVOUR SO THAT YOU WILL BE STANDIND AS THE BONAFIDE AS WE EMPOWER AND THE FINANCE COMPANY WILL CONTACT YOU FOR THE TRANSFER. AFTER WE SIGN THE POWER OF ATTORNEY THAT WILL EMPOWER THEM TO RELEASE AND TRANSFER TO YOU AS INSTRUCTED AND AUTHORISED.I NEED THE FOLLOWING BELOW. YOUR FULL NAME YOUR ADDRESS YOUR TELEPHONE AND MOBILE ONCE WE RECEIVE ALL THIS AND YOUR TELEPHONE CALL ASSURING US YOUR READINESS AND WILLINGNESS TO HELP US CLEAR AND CLAIM OUR MONEY AND ASSURE US ALSO OF HELPING US TO INVEST OUR MONEY WHICH IS THE ONLY HOPE OF OUR LIVING AND YOU ARE NOT GOING TO BETRAY US ONCE THE MONEY ARRIVE IN YOUR ACCOUNT. WE WILL SUBMIT YOUR DETAILS FOR THE CHANGE OF THE BENEFICIARY IN YOUR FAVOUR TO ENABLE THE FINANCE COMPANY HAVE THE FUND TRANSFER AS WE AUTHORISE. GOD BE WITH YOU AS WE AWAIT YOUR POSITIVE DECISION TO HELP AND YOU CAN GET US ON PHONE NO: 00229-90988269 FOR DETAILS DISSCUSSION REPLY ME HERE PLEASE FOR EASY ACCESS: SEE THE WEBSITE BELOW FOR YOU TO UNDERSTAND OUR POSITION NOW http://www.rtici.tv/photo1.htm

To My Beloved Friend I am writing you this mail after several internal battles in me, if i am doing the right thing, as i have gotten your email ever since but i have been hesitating to write you. I don't want you to feel sorry for me, because, I believe everyone will die someday. My name is K I Bakri , a widower and a former oil investor in Dubai, in the U.A.E.I have been diagnosed with Ideopathic Pulmonary Fibrosis. This is a terminal illness that affects the lungs, it has no cure and i am destined to leave this world any moment from now. I have not particularly lived my life so well, as I never really cared for anyone(not even myself) but my business. Though I am very rich, I was never generous, I was always hostile to people and only focused on my business as that was the only thing I cared for. But now I regret all this as I now know that there is more to life than just wanting to have or make all the money in the world. I believe when God gives me a second chance to come to this world I would live my life a different way from how I have lived it. Now that God has called me, I have willed and given most of my property and assets to my immediate and extended family members as well as a few close friends. I want God to be merciful to me and accept my soul so, I have decided to give also to charity organizations, as I want this to be one of the last good deeds I do on earth. So far, I have distributed money to some charity organizations in the Sudan,Indonesia,Norway,Netherland. Now that my health has deteriorated so badly, I cannot do this myself anymore. I once asked members of my family to close one of my accounts and distribute the money which I have there to charity organization in United States of America, they refused and kept the money to themselves. Hence, I do not trust them anymore, as they seem not to be contended with what I have left for them. The last of my money which no one knows of is the huge cash deposit of Eight Million Five hundred Thousand Dollars($8,500,000) that I have with a Security Company abroad. What i want to do is to make you the next of Kin/Beneficiary of this diplomatic box kept with the security company and collect the money stashed in the diplomatic box , and thereafter distirbute the money to the less priviledged and hungry. MY health is failing and there is nothing much i can do towards achieving this last wish of mine,all by myself because of my bedridden state in the hospital. I have set aside 30% for your time,service and expenses. N.B:My beloved friend please if you can perform this task ,please do not hesitate to write me,telling me about your passion to help the less-fortunate. for a faster response God be with you K I Bakri bakrih10@dynamixmail.com

TASAKI-SHINJU MANUFACTURING COMPANY LTD. Trusty Kojimachi Bldg. 3-4 Kojimachi, Chiyoda-ku, Tokyo. 102-0083 Japan. Dear Sir/Madam, Our-Ref.Tasaki/24598/07 Your-Ref----- I am Mr. Tasaki Shinju, President of TASAKI-SHINJU MANUFACTURING COMPANY LTD. Tasaki-Shinju Company, Ltd. is a subsidiary of the world renown U.S. multi- energy producer Tasaki-Shinju, in Japan and Asian regions and are producing and marketing not only high quality specialty lubricants but also petroleum and energy products. We specialized in the Refrigeration Oils, Rubber Process Oils, metalworking Oils, Industrial Lubricants, Automotive Lubricants, etc. We are currently searching for representatives who can help us establish a medium of getting to our customers in the Canada/America and other nearby countries as well as making payments through you to us. Sunoco, Inc was established in 1954, Entering into a new era where the demand for continuous improvement and expansion is far beyond what was perceived and required just a few years ago, corporate entities are constantly striving for perfection, knowing all too well that tomorrow will be yet another challenge. With all the new horizons that unfold before us, the difficulty of venturing out into the unknown requires preparation, experience, creativity and motivation. We, TASAKI-SHINJU MANUFACTURING COMPANY LTD. take on the challenge and look to the expansion of our horizons with pleasure. You do not have to leave your present job for this one because this job offer will be on a part time basis as it comes once in a while and remuneration is on a percentage basis of 10% of the total amount you receive from my customers at any time on my behalf. The reason why I seek your assistance is that American and Canadian checks take a long time to clear here in Japan, thereby holding business down for my associates and me. Now I already have customers who are ready to remit cash to me. Please to facilitate the conclusion of this transaction if accepted, do send me promptly the following information below by My private at infoattasakijapan@yahoo.co.jp NAME....................................... RESIDENTIAL ADDRESS........................ AGE:....................................... STATUS:.................................... STATE/COUNTRY.............................. TEL/FAX.................................... NUMBERS.................................... COMPANY NAME............................... OCCUPATION................................. We would be glad to have you as one of our esteemed Representative in your location and be rest assured that adequate pecuniary and lucrative compensations will be given and other benefits follows. Upon appointment, you are allowed the opportunity of determining the method or mode through which you would be paid for your services as our Representative in any of these Regions. Regards, TASAKI-SHINJU President & CEO TASAKI-SHINJU MANUFACTURING COMPANY. TEL: +81=354=603=939 Fax: +81=936=631=610

FROM THE DESK OF STEVEN LEE PRIVATE EMAIL:stevelee373@sify.com URGENT INHERITANCE CLAIM GOOD DAY, I KNOW THIS PROPOSAL WILL COME TO YOU AS A SURPRISEEXPECIALLY WHEN YOU DO NOT KNOW THE WRITER,CONDSIDERINGTHE HUGE SUM OF MONEY INVOLVED WHICH COULD MAKE ANYAPPREHENSIVE. LET ME START BY INTRODUCING MYSELF TO YOU,I AM STEVEN LEE, THE HEAD OF ACCOUNTING DEPARTMENT OF MY BANK,WHERE AM PRESENTLY WORKING. I SAW YOUR CONTACT DURING MY PRIVATE SEARCH AT THE INFORMATION CENTRE HERE IN MY COUNTRY CHAMBER OF COMMENCE AND INDUSTRY AND I WANT TO BELIEVE THAT YOU WILL BE VERYHONEST, COMMITTED AND CAPABLE OF ASSISTING IN THIS BUSINESS VENTURE.FIRSTLY, LET ME EXPLAIN THE SOURCE OF THIS FUNDS ANDWHATYOU ARE EXPECTED TO DO. A FORIGNER LATE MOHAMED KAMALYASSER, OIL MERCHANT/CONTRACTOR, UNTIL HIS DEATH, OVER THE PAST YEARS AGO, WAS A VICTIM OF AN EGYPTIAN AIRLINE FLIGHT 990 PLANE CRASH. HERE IS DETAILS ABOUT THE PLANE CRASH.(http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/world/americas/502503.stm)THE DECEASED, MOHAMED KAMAL YASSER, BANKED WITH US AND HAS A CLOSING BALANCE AS A JULY 2000 WORTH $45M (FOURTY FIVE MILLION USD). WHICH MY BANK, NOW EXPECTES A NEXT-OF-KIN TO CLAIM AS THE BENEFICIARY OF THE FUNDS, EFFORTS HAS BEEN MADE BY MY BANK DIRECTORS TO GET INTOUCH WITH THE MR MOHAMED KAMAL YASSER\\\\\\\'S FAMILY OR RELATIVE BUT TO NO SUCCESS BASED ON THE PERCEIVED POSSIBILITY OF NOT BEING ABLE TO LOCATE MOHAMED KAMAL\\\\\\\'S NEXT-OF-KIN, THE MANAGEMENT UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF OUR CHAIRMAN AND THE BOARD OF DIRECTORS ARE MAKING ARRANGEMENTS FOR THE FUNDS TO BE DECLARED UNCLAIMED AND CHANNELED TO AN UNKNOWN ACCOUNT. IT IS BASED ON THIS THAT WE HAVE CONTACTED YOU TO STAND AS THE NEXT-OF-KIN OF LATE MOHAMED KAMAL YASSER SO THAT THE FUNDS WILL BE RELEASED AND PAID INTO YOUR ACCOUNT AS THE BENEFICIARY AND THE NEXT-OF-KIN TO THE DECEASED. ALL DOCUMENTS, AND PROOF TO ENABLE YOU GET THE FUNDS HAVE BEEN CAREFULLY WORKED OUT AS WE HAVE SECURED FROM THE DIFFERENT OFFICES CONCERNED FOR THE SMOOTH TRANSFER OF THE FUND TO YOUR NOMINATED ACCOUNT.IT HAS BEEN AGREED THAT THE OWNER OF THE ACCOUNT WILL BE COMPENSATED WITH 30% OF THE REMITTED FUNDS, WHILE WE KEEP 65% AND 5% WILL BE SET ASIDE TO OFFSET EXPENSES BOTH LOCALLY AND INTERNATIONAL. IF THIS PROPOSAL SATISFIES YOU, PLEASE REACH ME THROUGH MY DIRECT EMAIL ADDRESS FOR MORE INFORMATION AND ALSO SEND ME YOUR CONTACT TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBER INCLUDING YOUR CELL PHONE NUMBER FOR QUICK AND EASY COMMUNICATION.I AWAIT YOUR URGENT RESPONSE, ALL THE BEST AND GOD BLESS YOU. PLEASE EMAIL ME ON THIS MY PRIVATE EMAIL ADRESS:stevenlee373@yahoo.com FOR SECURITY REASON. YOURS FAITHFULLY, STEVEN LEE.

Dear friend, This letter must surprise you because we have never meet before neither in person nor by correspondence, but I believe that it takes just one day to meet or know someone either physically or through correspondence. I got your contact through my personal search, you were revealed as being quite astute in private entrepreneurship, and one has no doubt in your ability to handle a financial business transaction. I am Mr. Liu Yan a transfer supervisor operations in investment section in Bank of China Ltd. Secretariat of the BOCHK Charitable Foundation 13/F. Bank of China Tower, 1 Garden Road, Hong Kong I have an obscured business suggestion for you.Before the U.S and Iraqi war our client General Mohammed Jassim Ali who work with the Iraqi forces and also business man made a numbered fixed deposit for 18 calendar months, with a value of Nineteen million Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars only in my branch. Upon maturity several notices was sent to him, even early in the war. Again after the war another notification was sent and still no response came from him. We later find out that General Mohammed Jassim Ali and his family had been killed during the war in a bomb blast that hit their home.After further investigation it was also discovered that General Mohammed Jassim Ali did not declare any next of kin in his official papers including the paper work of his bank deposit. And he also confided in me the last time he was at my office that no one except me knew of his deposit in my bank. So, Nineteen million Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars is still lying in my bank and no one will ever come forward to claim it. What bothers me most is that, according to the to the laws of my country at the expiration 3 years the funds will revert to the ownership of the Hong Kong Government if nobody applies to claim the funds. Against this backdrop, my suggestion to you is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand as the next of kin to General Mohammed Jassim Ali so that you will be able to receive his funds.I want you to know that I have had everything planned out so that we shall come out successful. I have contacted an attorney that will prepare the necessary document that will back you up as the next of kin to General Mohammed Jassim Ali, all what is required from you at this stage is for you to provide me with your Full Names, private phone number and Address so that the attorney can commence his job. After you have been made the next of kin, the attorney will also fill in for claims on your behalf and secure the necessary approval and letter of probate in your favor for the transfer of the funds to an account that will be provided by you with my guidiance.There is no risk involved at all in the matter as we are going adopt a legalized method and the attorney will prepare all the necessary documents. Please endeavor to observe utmost discretion in all matters concerning this issue. Once the funds have been transferred to your nominated bank account we shall discuss the percentage issue on your reply.If you are interested please send me your full names, private phone/fax and current residential address. Kind Regards Liu Yan. N:B Your earliest response to this letter will be appreciated. Please make sure you contact me on my private email: info.liuyan@yahoo.com.hk

From: Mr Usman Zongo  African Development Bank (ADB) Ouagadougou , Burkina Faso .   Dear Friend, I Am The Manager Of Foreign Remittance And Exchange Dept At African Development Bank (ADB). Burkina- Faso, West Africa .   In my department we discover an abandoned sum of Usd$12.6m Dollars (Twelve Million, Six Hundred Thousand Us Dollar). In an account that belongs to one of our foreign customer who died alongside with his entire family in a plane crash the year 2001 that took the whole life of the passengers on board.   Since we got information about his death, the bank have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because the bank cannot release it unless someone applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicating in our banking guideline, but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation that knows about the account information died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I now decided to make this business proposal to you and for the money to be release to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased, since nobody will ever come for it, we do not want this money to go into the treasury of the bank as unclaimed bill or fund.   The bank law and guideline here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed after six years, the money will be transferred into the bank treasury account as unclaimed fund. The request of foreigner as next of kin in this transaction is occasioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a citizen cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. In subsequent disbursement of the money, I agree that 40% of this money will be for you in respect of the provision you made by standing in the claim as next of kin,10% will be set aside for expenses in cure during  the transaction on taxes that will arise and 50% would be for me. As soon as the money hit into your account I will come over to your country for disbursement according to the percentages indicated above.   To make the claim, you will first of all apply to the bank by sending a text of application which I will send to you for you to fill and send to the bank. In the application you will indicate your bank account, your private fax and your private telephone number for easy and effective communication.   Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by email the text of application which you will send to the bank. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch free and you do not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made for the success of the transfer. You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this letter.   Hoping to hear from you immediately.   Thanks. Usman Zongo Get news, entertainment and everything you care about at Live.com. Check it out!

Vincent Cheung Foreign Operations department Hang Seng Bank 11/F Hang Seng Wanchai Building, 200 Hennessy Road, Wanchai Hello, I am Mr Vincent Cheung, of the Hang Seng Bank 11/F Hang Seng Wanchai Building, 200 Hennessy Road, Wanchai . An Iragi named Fadi Basem,a business man made a numbered fixed deposit of (346,736,899.68 HKD) for 18 calendar months, this is valued to Fourty Four million Five Hundred Thousand United State Dollars only in my branch. Upon maturity several notice was sent to him, even during the war, four years ago (2003). Again after the war another notification was sent and still no response came from him. We later found out that Fadi Basem and his family had been killed during the war in Gunfire that hit their home at Mukaradeeb where his personal oil well was. After further investigation it was also discovered that Fadi Basem did not declare any next of kin in his official papers including the paper work of his bank deposit. And he also confided in me the last time he was at my office that no one except me knew of his deposit in my bank. So, Fourty Four million Five Hundred Thousand United State Dollars is still lying in my bank and no one will ever come forward to claim it. What bothers me is that according to the laws of my country at the expiration five years six months the funds will revert to the ownership of the Hong Kong Government if nobody applies to claim the funds. My proposal, We are prepared to place you as the next of kin in a position to instruct HANG SENG BANK to release the deposit to you as the closest surviving relation. Upon receipt of the deposit, we am prepared to share the money with you on to be agreed on percentages. That is: I will simply nominate you as the next of kin and have them release the deposit to you. I would have gone ahead to ask the funds be released to me, but that would have drawn a straight line in my involvement in claiming the deposit.I assure you that I could have the deposit released to you within the coming weeks. I will simply inform the bank of the final closing of the file relating to the late customer, I will then officially communicate with my Bank and instruct them to release the deposit to you. With these: all is done. I am aware of the consequences of this proposal. I ask that if you find no interest in this project that you should discard this mail. I ask that you do not be vindictive and destructive. If my offer is of no appeal to you,delete this message and forget I ever contacted you. Do not destroy my career because you do not approve of my proposal. You may not know this but people like myself who have made tidy sums out of comparable situations run the whole private banking sector. I am not a criminal and what I do, I do not find against good conscience, this may be hard for you to understand, but the dynamics of my industry dictates that I make this move. Such opportunities only come ones way once in a lifetime. I cannot let this chance pass me by, for once I find myself in total control of my destiny. These chances wont pass me by. I ask that you do not destroy my chance, if you will not work with me let me know and let me move on with my life but do not destroy me. I am a family man and this is an opportunity to provide them with new opportunities. There is a reward for this project and it is a task well worth undertaking. I have evaluated the risks and the only risk I have here is from you refusing to work with me and alerting my bank. I am the only one who knows of this situation, good fortune has blessed you with a name that has planted you into the center of relevance in my life. Lets share the blessing. If you give me positive signals, I will initiate this process towards a conclusion. I wish to inform you that should you contact me via official channels; I will deny knowing you and about this project. I repeat, I do not want you contacting me through my official phone lines nor do I want you contacting me through my official email account. Contact me only through the numbers I will provide for you and also through the email account that i will provide therein in this email. Further more be informed that the fact that you are a foreigner gives you the privilege to stand in as my deceased client beneficiary as my deceased client had no relation all his family died with him during the war and I can not use my relations because its not accepted here in Hong Kong. Also I am very confident that we will be able to establish the trust that is needed to complete this deal and all that I need from the time been is your willingness and commitment so that we can end this in the next two weeks. What you need to understand about this transaction is that I will make sure that it passes through all international banking laws regards to this I will give the transaction the proper documentation that is required to perfect the finishing. Your only obligation in this transaction will be to set up the offshore accounts that can accommodate these funds and I will give you more light later once you agree to partner with me. Like I said before there is no risk involve as it will pass through international banking laws and all documents related to this transaction will be sent to you by post for your perusal and trust. I do not want any direct link between you and me. My official lines are not secure lines as they are periodically monitored to assess our level of customer care in line with our Total Quality Management Policy. Please observe this instruction religiously. Please, again, note I am a family man, I have a wife and children. I send you this mail not without a measure of fear as to what the consequences, but I know within me that nothing ventured is nothing gained and that success and riches never come easy or on a platter of gold. This is the one truth I have learned from my private banking clients. Do not betray my confidence. If we can be of one accord, we should plan a meeting, soon. Should you be interested I will prefer you to reach me via email. Your earliest response to this letter will be appreciated. I await your response. Mr.Cheung mailcheung001@yahoo.com

Attention please Compliments to you; I sincerely apologize for the intrude into your private life, however I have a serious project which I believe would be of interest to you and for this reason I reached out to you. I am Barrister Kenneth Obi. I worked as an attorney to an Oil Servicing company {CEDRY INCORPORATED} from 1980 to 1996 when the company liquidated. Cedry liquidated and folded as a result of mismanagement and feud amongst the directors. On the 11th of June 1986, the company secretary and I took a LIFE ASSURANCE POLICY for the Chairman of the company for a period of TWENTY YEARS, which is from June 1986 till June 2006. This LIFE POLICY was taken from a reputable Insurance Company here called STANDARD TRUST INSURANCE PLC. The premium for this Life policy was paid upfront by the Cedry because it is a long-term policy. In 1996, Cedry was folded but Standard Trust Insurance Company did not terminate the Life Policy we took for the Chairman because we did not apply  for cancellation or termination of the Policy. On December 2006, I got a letter from Standard Trust Insurance notifying me that the LIFE POLICY we took for Cedry Chairman was due and that I should come to their office for further discussions. I went to their office and they told me that they have Three Million Dollars accrued over a period of twenty years to pay to the Chairman of liquidated Cedry as SURRENDER VALUE for the Life Policy the company took for him. The Insurance Company knew that Cedry was folded and they asked me to provide the Chairman or his relative to receive the money. Since 2006 till date I have searched for the Chairman without success. I went back to tell the Insurance Company that the Chairman is very old and senile to the extent that his sight is very bad and that he cannot do anything for himself as he is almost a vegetable. The Insurance Company told me to get any of  the Chairman’s relative with his authorization to claim the surrender value for him. I have resolved to get any person or any person bearing same name as the Chairman to stand as his relative to receive the surrender value. If we don't claim this money,  no one would and the money would be retained in the coffers of the Insurance Company as their profit. I feel it is rather appropriate that we team up and claim this money and use some percentage of it to help the poor and the less privilege in our society than allow the Insurance Company to retain it as profit. I contacted you in trust believing that you will not run away with the money if it enters your account. The Insurance Company have very high respect and regards for me and will be obliged to released the Surrender Value to whoever I present to them as heir to the Chairman. I will obtain for you all that is required to execute this transaction successfully. I have in my file some documents for the existence of the Cedry and the Life Policy. I will send to you once you indicate your interest. I will also send a claim application specimen to you, which you will fill and send to the Insurance Company for the release of the surrender value to your account. Your share for assisting in this transaction will be One Million Dollars. If you cannot execute this transaction for any reason, please introduce someone who is capable and I will reward you with Fifty thousand dollars after the transaction. Reply urgently if you are interested to execute this with me.   Regards, Barrister Kenneth Obi More photos; more messages; more whatever – Get MORE with Windows Live™ Hotmail®. NOW with 5GB storage. Get more!

Attention, Do not be offended if by any way this email is offensive to your personal being; well,my name is John Davids, I work with a reputable organisation here in London-England. I am contacting you based on investing certain amount of monies on properties allocation. For the fact that you do not know me does not mean you should discard this email, rather it gives a room why you and I should be business partners. Please note here that this venture is not in any form, way or likes with whatever you might have heard, neither received nor been through before. However, my main reasons for contacting you is to seek and reach a mutual agreement with you, thus needing your assistance in conveying certain amount of monies to you in your country; most of the monies would be utilized judiciously mostly on Properties. This fund - US$38 Million which came to my notice after going through series of abandoned files of foreign account holder at my organisation; the peculiar file that got my attention was that of a Russian; Stoitckov Huroni, who I did some research on and found out he was an Oil tycoon from Tomsk, Russia. According to my findings, the deceased has been a reputable client to this organisation; After much findings on this Multimillionaire business oil tycoon, I decided to take it upon myself and find out much about this man; I found out he has no living relatives! I also discovered that he actually died in Jail due to his brutal arrest by the Russian President, Vladimir Putin; I decided to take this issue up and I met with some colleagues; we thus decided and agreed to transfer the fund into an escrow account pending till we find a trustworthy person or good firm with great business margin whose account we will transfer this fund for mutual. Reasons for this steps is to avoid a situation where at the end of this quarter, the top executives of this organisation will confiscate the account and diffuse this money among themselves because the President of Russia had made it known any foreign organisation accommodating funds of his political rivals would have herself to blame. We also discovered the Russian President, Mr. Putin has held up and seized all monies lodged in foreign account by his political rival, and one of such people was the unfortunate Mr. Huroni. What we intend to do upon your acceptance is to use you as a Next of Kin of late Mr. Stoitckov Huroni and transfer this fund into your account and of which you would be greatly awarded in kind for your participation. Having stated the above, it will interest you to know that, there is no risk or whatsoever involved in this transaction hence we have perfected all modalities to make this a success while requesting for a catalogue of properties for sale in your country, for our study. Should you be interested therefore, do contact me through my email address – lloyds-tsb@web2mail.com else ignore this message! You would be given more details upon your acceptance to be a foreign partner!!! Best Regards, John Davids ******************************************************************************* ***************** CONFIDENTIALITY NOTICE: This electronic message contains information which may be legally confidential, discrete and/or privileged and does not in any case an offensive to your person . The information is intended solely for the individual or entity named above and access by anyone else is unauthorized. If you are not the intended recipient, any disclosure, copying, distribution, or use of the contents of this information is prohibited and may be unlawful. If you have received this electronic transmission in error, please reply immediately to the sender that you have received the message in error, and delete it. © 2007 Lloyds TSB Bank ******************************************************************************* *****************